Ladybug and Cat Noir have saved Paris once again.
And once again, Marinette tries to find time to complete her magic box.
What's the magic box for, Marinette?
To keep all my heart's secrets.
All your secrets?
So you write everything you do in that notebook?
Oh, yes. Is there a problem?
Yeah, like what if someone finds out you're Ladybug... also, someone could find out you're Ladybug.
That will never happen. Just take a try Tikki.
And it worked.
The other day, Mr. Bourgeois was elected mayor of Paris, starting his fourth term.
Here's Mr. Bourgeois with his daughter in public.
Oh, look at Chloé, as if she's the mayor of Paris. Oh, speaking of which, the class president election is tomorrow.
What's wrong with that, Marinette?
Because Chloé is going to run too.
She's someone who thinks of herself the most, and the students the least.
Well, then you should run.
I'd like to, but with my duties as Ladybug... and I already have homework.
True, but if you believe in something enough, you fight for it.
Better to try and fail than not try at all.
Maybe.
Don't put yourself down, Marinette.
Armand D'Argencourt, Bourgeois's main opponent... and your fencing teacher at François Dupont High School, was crushed at the polls.
In fact, D'Argencourt got the fewest votes in Paris history.
I'm about to be late for school.
Again.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
Chloé is announcing her candidacy for class president.
And her running mate will be Sabrina.
Any other candidates?
Hmm.
Yes, who?
Uh, no.
Oh, sorry, I was on the bus... Oh, my throat is dry.
Chloé is running again.
How long has she been class president?
Since kindergarten?
Why don't you run?
You'd be a great president.
No way.
I'm constantly dealing with Chloé.
Alright.
I'll give you all until noon to think about running.
Don't ever do that again.
I hate being treated like that.
What are you girls doing?
What did Chloé say to you this time?
She wants to go out with you?
No, she told everyone I'm afraid of spiders.
They told me that if I run... they'll kick me out of the scrapbooking club.
But I love those stickers, decorations, glitter.
I don't even care about being a candidate.
What's your excuse?
I'm too busy.
With what?
Sleeping?
Oh no, but uh, well, if no one else is going to run... maybe...
Alright, any other candidates against Chloé and Sabrina?
Since Chloé and Sabrina are the only candidates, I guess there's no need for a vote.
So Chloé and Sabrina... I'm running!
Great.
By tomorrow, you'll need to prepare a campaign speech and work on your presentation.
Then the election begins.
I can't believe this.
Yes, let's hear the big surprise of your campaign.
How will you introduce yourself?
Introduce myself?
I have no idea, but I can't believe I raised my hand.
You're amazing, Marinette.
Speak bravely.
This is incredible.
Thank you.
If you win, can we get more comfortable seats?
These are so hard I can't focus on the lesson.
Also, pink ones. And if we could listen to music while studying in the library, that would be even better.
Actually, I don't know.
Of course, Juleka.
Adrien, you're voting for Marinette, right?
Sure, but it depends on her speech.
I have to run a really good campaign.
I've seen my father win every election.
And I can follow in his footsteps.
I know how to win.
With the best campaign, right?
Nonsense.
The secret to winning in politics is always to destroy your opponent's reputation.
Comfortable seats, library music, like Juleka said... I'm writing down everyone's problems.
Now I need to add these to my campaign speech.
I'm proud of you.
I'm sure you'll win.
You'll be a great president.
They're counting on me to beat Chloé.
Even Adrien... You noticed, right?
Marinette, the battle has begun.
What?
What's going on?
Chloé gathered the whole class at City Hall for an election party.
Plus, there's a Jagged Stone concert.
Are you serious?
Jagged Stone is my favorite pop star.
I love him.
Of course, everyone loves him.
Absolutely.
She's trying to buy votes by giving out autographed photos.
No way, not before I have my say.
See you.
I'm coming in, Chloé.
Hello.
Marinette borrowed my geometry book, but I need it.
Marinette isn't here.
I need to attend to my customer.
But if it's no trouble, you can go up and get it from her room yourself.
Oh, no problem.
Thank you.
Nice move.
I have to go.
That last move you saw was invented by my great ancestor, Darkblade.
Darkblade?
In ancient times, Darkblade seized Paris and ruled oppressively.
But then the people, bought with money from a wealthy Frenchman, united and overthrew him.
That wasn't so long ago, and my ancestors' flag once flew over Paris.
Is that why you entered the election, Mr. D'Argencourt?
To avenge your ancestors?
Nonsense!
Where is this coming from?
Nadia Chamack, don't be offended, it's news.
How do you comment on your historic defeat that everyone is talking about?
Hey, excuse me, how did you get into the school?
Come on, get out of the studio.
Hey, stop, come back here!
Class is over here.
A wimp and a klutz are running for office.
But I will present the most suitable candidate to the public.
Fly away, my little akuma.
Take hold of this defeated warrior.
Mr. D'Argencourt, to quote the rumors...
They say you're a stubborn, rusty relic of a bygone era.
What do you say to that?
They're slandering me.
Why are you bothering with such ridiculous questions?
Get out of here, you nuisances.
Darkblade, in exchange for these powers I give you, you will capture Ladybug and Cat Noir for me.
When my ancestors' flag flies once again over Paris City Hall... then I will consider my revenge complete.
We're curious, what you just transformed into in front of the cameras... Darkblade, Lord of Paris.
What?
Now, become my knights.
Soon my army will be ruthless and invincible.
We must lay siege to City Hall and take the throne back from that wretch Bourgeois.
A medieval nutjob has arrived.
Time to transform.
Plagg, claws out!
Great!
A monster that can join our conquest.
To battle!
Come on, to battle, my knights!
The people want Bourgeois to rule, not you, D'Argencourt.
I don't care about the people.
And D'Argencourt has been defeated.
Not Darkblade, you fool!
Chloé, I'm inside.
What was I supposed to look for?
Anything.
As long as it's embarrassing.
Wait, I had one of these.
Could it be?
A yo-yo?
Or a screwdriver?
Of course not, you half-wit.
It has to be a really bad photo.
Or an ugly dress.
Look around a bit.
How about a diary?
Wow.
So when you really want something, you can find it.
Sabrina.
Welcome, everyone, to the official launch of Chloé's election campaign.
And special thanks to world star Jagged Stone for supporting Chloé.
And when you vote for me, you'll get tickets to Jagged's next concert.
I'm going to be great.
Autographed photos?
Yes.
I got one for you too.
Sorry, I couldn't help myself.
What?
No, I'm not falling for that.
But if you vote for me, I might forgive you.
Are you serious?
How did you not notice that move?
Catch them!
Don't waste a single minute.
To City Hall, immediately!
City Hall, huh?
You go ahead, I'll catch up.
Oh, where have you been?
You got the diary, right, Sabrina?
I got it.
Sort of.
What is this?
When I took the diary, this weird box trapped my hand inside it.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Who am I kidding?
Don't you realize you're being bribed?
Concert tickets are great, but this isn't how you solve the class's problems.
So what's in your campaign, Marinette?
Well, instead of new seats, I thought we could put cushions.
Your cushion would be pink.
And I also thought about the library music.
With headphones, of course.
That's incredible.
You're already acting like class president.
But unfortunately, you won't win this.
Let's talk.
Oh, you took my diary from my room.
If you don't drop out of the election, all your secrets will be exposed.
Don't!
I mean, what secrets could they be?
Ha, we'll find out soon.
But first, I need to find a saw.
Everyone listen up.
Darkblade is about to speak.
Anyone who doesn't listen goes to prison.
Finally, my flag will fly over this kingdom.
Bourgeois, you wretch.
Come and fight me.
What is he saying now?
Basically, he's going to kill us.
Please make an appointment with my secretary.
Submit to Darkblade.
Or face my wrath.
To battle!
Catch them!
Kids, aren't you tired of metal music?
Cat Noir, quick!
Good warm-up.
To battle!
Is that the sound of my crazy fans?
I can control them.
Stay out of this, Luka.
Okay, okay.
I get it, you love me, but please don't fight.
Are you an enemy warrior?
I don't understand.
No way.
What are we going to do?
Quick, to the door.
Enough, Chloé.
Everyone kneel before Darkblade.
You will all obey.
Chloé, what are we going to do?
What's the class president going to do?
If you vote for me, I might give you an answer.
But tomorrow.
We can't wait until tomorrow.
Then tough luck.
Ask someone else.
Well, we need to talk.
What are you going to do now?
I need to help Cat Noir, but I also need to help the students.
You have to trust your instincts.
Ivan, lock the door.
Close all the windows too.
Hurry.
Nino, Juleka, Rose, Mylène, Alya, you're with me.
Good girl.
That's how the future class president is raised.
Well, I was going to say the same things to you.
Sabrina, Ivan, Kim, go close the door.
Move forward.
We need to barricade the entrances.
Quick.
I hope they haven't done anything bad to Cat Noir.
Time to retreat.
Look, we need to get out of here right now.
This way.
I'll catch up from behind.
I'll close the windows tightly and come.
Now they'll be safe.
The only ones left.
Out of the way, you garbage fools.
Cat Noir.
I'm here.
Sorry, Cat Noir.
I had to take care of the people inside.
Actually, I was doing just fine on my own.
But it's good to see you, of course.
Scutum formation.
Great.
Useless jesters.
Let go.
Why are they jumping into the moat?
Looks like not all of them can jump.
The flag.
I hope so.
When my own coat of arms replaces this flag, I will be the sovereign.
The akuma must be in the sword.
So how do we get the sword?
I need to get close to him.
Cat Noir must not get the pennant.
Jesters, that didn't affect me at all.
Thanks to the Sword of Darkness, everyone within the borders of this kingdom now belongs to me.
Bow to your king!
Soon you will join me too.
You pathetic insect.
There it is. A bit tricky.
You fool.
Cat Noir and Ladybug will soon face their cursed fate.
We are about to become dark knights.
To battle! >> Lucky Charm!
Okay.
I hope Darkblade is ticklish.
Now you'll see.
You can't do evil anymore, akuma.
Come on, give up the evil.
That's it.
Fly away, little butterfly.
Miraculous Ladybug.
Pound it!
I have to go, see you.
Our duel isn't over yet, my Ladybug.
When our battle ends, I will win.
You were great, Marinette.
You proved that you can be both Ladybug and class president.
It wasn't easy, but I'm glad I tried.
Because if I hadn't tried, I wouldn't have known I could do it.
Where have you been, Marinette?
Hiding under a rock?
You're so funny, Chloé.
I transformed too.
I became a knight.
Yeah, me too.
What a nightmare, right?
Since everything is over, give me back my personal belongings.
I honestly have no idea what you're talking about.
Please take this.
Thank you.
Do you have an explanation, Chloé?
I told you.
I didn't take her diary.
I don't appreciate you blaming me.
Then how do you know there was a diary inside?
Well... Sabrina told me.
It was all her idea anyway.
Not nice.
We know no one is going to vote for Chloé now.
You'll be the new class president.
Let's not rush, Alya.
See, she doesn't trust herself.
She's already giving up.
No, I'm not.
I want to be elected fairly.
Not because you don't want Chloé, but because you want me.
I don't want to make promises I can't keep.
And I can't give you everything you want.
But I am resourceful and I know my priorities.
I listen well, I can multitask.
I truly believe in being your president.
And most importantly, I believe in myself.
So, votes for the new president, votes for Marinette.
What are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
What good are you?
By majority vote, Marinette is our new class president.
And Alya is elected her running mate.
You can help me deal with Chloé.
If we put our minds to it, we can accomplish anything.
I've got your back.