Hello. Ladybug and Cat Noir saved Paris
once again. Jand Park was recently
turned into a terrifying magician under a spell
and was about to destroy the Eiffel Tower
in a cloud of smoke.
Oh dear, you don't look well. Take me to the doctor,
Marinette. But Tikki, where am I going to find
a doctor? I know someone. I'll tell you where to go,
but what will I say? You're a secret,
he'll get suspicious if he sees you and ask questions.
Besides, there's someone else who'll ask a lot of questions:
my teacher. I'm late again. Tikki,
shall I take you after school? What do
you say? Thank you. Internal combustion
is the exothermic chemical reaction of fuel
and oxidizer, reaching high temperatures,
at atmospheric pressure. Today, Prince Ali,
heir to the throne of the Kingdom of Achu,
is making a trip to Paris to launch
a toy donation campaign for sick children
at Paris City Hospital. How
handsome he is, and his heart is as good as gold.
Look, I want to write him a letter
expressing my admiration and respect for him.
Ah, Marinette. What's your excuse this time?
Did you get accidentally locked in the bathroom again?
Of course not. No, I had to take my, um,
dog to the doctor because he ate my sweater.
Oh, he could get very sick. Thank you, Rose.
But I don't think our class needs any more odor.
I thought someone brought a fish sandwich,
but actually it's just Rose's perfume.
Using a cell phone inside is forbidden.
Collect your remaining belongings and go
to the principal's office immediately.
Did you see that? That's what happens
when you play with flammable substances in the chemistry lab.
And don't forget that tomorrow
I will test you on laboratory safety.
Dude, you're like twins. Neither of you can
make it to school on time. Since Adrien
missed chemistry class, wouldn't it be nice
if someone gave him the notes he couldn't take?
You're right. So, should I give him the notes?
Uh, no, I can't. I, uh... Sweetie, I'm definitely
not buying these excuses.
I think I'm getting sick. Then talk
less. I don't feel well at all. Don't worry,
Tikki, it won't take long.
Hey, are you okay? Is something wrong? Uh, yes. I'm
fine.
Adrien. Sabrina, what is Prince Ali doing today?
They said he's giving out toys to children. Huh.
I guess this is a plush toy. Whose could it be?
The Prince has never seen anything like it, and
when he sees me, Prince Ali will have forgotten
all about the sick children.
Did you say Prince Ali, or did you just mean
him? None of your business. The Prince's father's
hotel is the only hotel fit for princes,
and I will be the first to meet him. How lucky.
But please, could you give him this letter from me?
Of course.
How thoughtful of you to do this.
Did you really believe that?
Do you think I would take this smelly thing with me?
Tikki! Ah, Chloé, wait, that's mine. Not
anymore. It's mine now.
Whenever I see a broken-hearted princess, I know
her well.
Every rose has its thorn.
Fly, my little akuma, and evilize her.
Dear princess, I am Hawk Moth. From now on, your secret
weapon will be your perfume. No one will be able to resist it,
especially Prince Ali. All I ask in return
is that you bring me Ladybug and
Cat Noir's Miraculous. I'm coming,
my prince.
Hello, I'm from Chloé Bourgeois'
class and I must see her. Are you
her friend? Am I her friend? You must be joking.
I mean, we're just in the same class, that's all. If you're not
her friend, you can't come in. Yes, I am
Chloé's friend.
We're very close.
Chloé doesn't have any friends. So,
are you not going to let me in? No.
He usually eats sushi. The top floor Royal
Suite, you mean? Prince... Ah, it's not important.
You're spoiling me, really.
No, no. That's better.
Ha, pizza? Ugh, don't bring that poor people's food
any closer.
I've come to see Prince Ali. Ah,
what's going on today? Do you have a date with the Prince?
No need. I am a princess myself.
I am a princess. Listen, kid.
You don't speak to a princess like that.
At your service, Princess Fragrance. That's much
better. Now, where is my handsome prince?
I shouldn't keep him waiting.
In honor of your visit to Paris, I have personally arranged
a fireworks display over the Seine River
just for you.
The fireworks will be launched from this boat.
Thank you. How do you say it in your language?
This is wonderful. First, it must fit
into the Prince's busy schedule. There is very little time
for fun. His Majesty is a responsible
person.
Ali, if you'll permit me, let me introduce you
to my own princess.
Chloé. Prince, I brought you a very special
gift for the sick children.
I've never seen anything like it.
How kind of you. You're spoiling me, but
it was a lovely thought of mine. Isn't that right?
Yes. As I was saying, didn't you hear me?
Nadja, don't be surprised. This is just the news.
Prince Ali, what can you tell us about this official
visit to Paris?
It's wonderful to be here. Prince Ali, this, uh...
Uh, where is that smell coming from? Ah, like rotten fish.
It's not from me.
But is it from me?
We are at your service, dear princess. And who
are you? I am Princess Fragrance, and I have come here
for you. Very soon you will be my Prince Ali.
Who is this now? Plagg, Plagg, let's go.
Paris is in trouble. I haven't finished my meal.
Plagg!
Claws out! Quickly, this way!
This place is extremely secure, our door
is made of steel. What is this chaos here?
There's not a single person following the schedule.
What is this now?
Run! You will come to the scent of my eternal love!
Are you serious? Who are you?
Mother of... I can't take it anymore. You can't be
a superhero now. There are two of them.
You cannot escape my scent!
Seize them, dear princess!
At your service! They're all bewitched. Quick,
close the door! But isn't that your father?
What do I care? Close it, I said!
At your service, dear princess.
Can we get some fresh air?
Plagg, absolutely not. You cannot take it from me!
Emergency evacuation! Everyone downstairs!
This is too dangerous for the Prince.
You're right. Safety first.
Prince, can we measure the window? This fish
smells bad even to me.
We have nine minutes to get to the hospital.
The Prince's schedule is very tight. What?
We can't go to a hospital right now. We need to get
Prince Ali out of Paris.
How nice to see you. What a great honor.
I will take you, and we will seal our love!
Cat Noir's gone. Ladybug! Ha!
I'll find him. Tikki?
Tikki, I was so worried. Marinette, you're worse
than I thought. We need to go to a doctor.
We don't have any time. You have to transform.
Forget about me.
No. I won't make the same mistake again.
We have to get you to a doctor.
She'll get better soon, won't she?
One who burns with impatience cannot drink
hot milk. What does milk have to do with it?
Silence, please.
I'm checking the energy.
You said a breed of cat? Is it really a cat?
Yes, a rare hairless flying cat from the Kingdom of Achu.
It was given to me as a gift
when I won a dance competition
during a childhood trip to the Kingdom of Achu.
Oh, that was a long time ago. Yes,
quite. It's done now. Your cat's health
is restored.
Ah, thank you! Thank you so much!
You are a magician, sir. How did you do that?
Secrets of ancient China.
Like your secret.
Tikki, I'm so, so sorry. You were very sick
and I don't know what I'd do without you.
You couldn't be Ladybug, for instance.
I know. But I'm serious, Tikki, you're more
to me than just a kwami.
I know.
The bridge goes that way. They must have gone there.
While they're in the car,
we must act quickly, no time to lose.
Tikki, spots on!
I can't wait for us to be together,
my prince. Servants, the love lock!
With this, our love will be eternal.
Prince, I am entirely at your service,
Princess. The love lock!
Hold it right there, you stinky thing!
Use Cat Noir to reach Ladybug.
Servants, attack! And bring me her earrings!
Stop it, Cat Noir. You are mine, Ladybug.
Give me your Miraculous!
Why make our love eternal when you could be taking over Paris?
This can't be happening. I need to put an end to this
before something happens to me too.
See? That's what happens
when you play with flammable substances
in the chemistry lab!
It didn't come.
You missed!
Yes, finally you dropped it!
Give me your Miraculous! Cataclysm!
I never liked this city. There are too many people
after us. Let's go far away from here.
Come on, my prince. Were you leaving for somewhere far away?
But the party's just
getting started. You've ruined everything.
And I will ruin you! Lucky Charm!
A balloon? What am I going to do with this?
You can't escape now, Ladybug. Give up!
No more evil-doing for you!
Akuma, let go of the evil!
That's it. Goodbye,
little butterfly.
Miraculous Ladybug!
What am I doing here? Where is
Ladybug?
Our whole schedule is ruined. We'll be late
for everything. But where is the Prince?
Wait a minute. Where am I?
How did I get here? Prince
Ali, and who are you? Never mind, I'll leave you
to chat with your fan for a bit.
See you later. I know you help sick children
around the world, and I have to say,
you are the kindest person
I have ever met in my life.
Really? I think so.
You are kind. Luckily, I'm fine too.
Aren't I? Let's pick up where we left off.
There's no need, Miss Rose.
I need to go see the children at the hospital.
Let's hurry a bit, or else
my assistant will be lost. Goodbye.