So, with flowers or without flowers?
Uh, with flowers.
Are you sure it's not better without flowers?
You look perfect either way.
I mean, you don't celebrate your 20th wedding anniversary every day, right?
Marinette.
Huh?
Could you come here please?
So?
What?
I trimmed my mustache.
Is it too short?
Should I shave it all off?
You look great, Dad.
Except for one thing.
Thank you.
No problem, Dad.
You're going to be late.
Don't forget, Ms. Chamack is coming to pick up the Eiffel Tower cake in 30 minutes.
I'm counting on you.
Yeah, yeah, don't worry, it's super easy.
Mm-hmm.
Wow, they've been married for twenty years.
Isn't it beautiful, Tikki?
Time flies when you're having fun.
And it stands still when you're doing homework.
Hey.
Marinette's family is one of the girls I hang out with.
Yeah, I remember.
They make the best bread in all of Paris.
Couldn't you have made a little effort to dress more appropriately?
What do you mean?
I took off my hat.
But this is a special day, you know.
What?
It's just a birthday.
No, this is a special birthday.
This family heirloom was made by one of our ancestors years and years ago.
It passes from one generation to the next on every 15th birthday.
And today, the day has come for it to be passed down to you, sweetheart.
That's really sweet, Dad, but I already have a watch.
It's synced to my smartphone.
But sometimes there's more than meets the eye.
I mean, our ancestors were a bit... ahead of their time.
Of course, if you'd rather I got you a new pair of rollerblades instead, I'd understand.
No, Dad, I'd love to take it.
This is amazing, thank you.
Are your friends waiting?
Yeah, but I don't want to leave you.
It's fine.
No, no, you can go.
Look, take good care of this, okay?
You can do this.
Just remember the formula.
Think, Marinette, think.
Maybe I could think if you weren't distracting me with your encouraging words.
Hello, Alya, what's up?
What?
The bet between Alix and Kim?
No, of course I didn't forget.
I even made the poster.
I know everyone's counting on me.
Five minutes?
No problem, I'm already on my way.
I'll be right there.
But Marinette, we have to wait for Ms. Chamack to pick up her cake.
She'll be here in twenty minutes.
I told them I'd handle the poster and they're all counting on me.
Plus, Adrien is going to be there.
You can never make it to Trocadéro in five minutes.
It's way too far.
Not too far for Ladybug.
Tikki, spots on!
Looks great.
Impressive, isn't it, Marinette?
You picked the wrong side to support.
Looks like Alix is a no-show.
Probably scared to race against an athlete like me.
You spoke too soon, Kim.
Your ridiculous bet is about to end.
I'm gonna make you eat my dust, meathead.
You can't challenge me.
My neck is thicker than your legs.
Is that a good thing?
Let's review the rules.
Two laps around the fountains.
About 500 meters.
The first one to cross the line will be declared the winner.
If Kim wins, Alix gives him her rollerblades.
If Alix wins, Kim can't make another bet until the end of the school year, unfortunately.
We're sick of these stupid bets.
Enough already.
No more bets.
On your marks, get set... Hold on.
Scared already?
Can you hold this for me, Alya?
I don't want to think about it during the race.
No, girl, I can't.
Guard it with your life, okay?
It's a family heirloom, but... Marinette, take this.
I need to record the race for my blog.
On your marks... get set...
Go!
Come on!
But she asked you to look after it.
I need to hold the watch.
Huh?
Need a hand?
Yeah, thanks.
You should be careful, no matter how magnificent you are.
About holding things.
Final lap.
Magnificent at holding things?
Adrien.
Let's see what you've got there.
Is this some kind of old box or something?
Careful, that's Alix's.
If it's Alix's, it's probably useless.
Give it back to Adrien, Chloé.
Fine.
Yes.
I want a rematch.
That first pause threw me off.
Did you do this?
I had to record the race.
So I gave it to Marinette.
She gave it to Adrien.
Chloé took it from him and dropped it.
Then you ran over it.
My dad gave this to me for my birthday.
This watch was a family heirloom.
It was an accident.
We didn't mean to damage it.
Besides, I had nothing to do with it.
You're all guilty.
Ah!
Alix, wait!
Way too much drama over one little push.
We still have time.
Hide, Tikki.
Such disappointment, frustration, and negativity... how it thrills my heart.
Fly away, my little akuma, and evilize her.
Enjoy your meal.
This is Ms. Chamack.
Hello, yes?
Yes, I know you want the cake immediately.
My daughter is home, she must be upstairs.
I'll call her right away.
Maybe we can fix it.
This watch was amazing, unique.
It can't be fixed.
There has to be a way to restore it.
But how?
Like going back in time and changing the future?
Let me know when you figure out how to do that.
This can't be good.
Hello, Dad.
Hello.
I am Hawk Moth.
I'm giving you the power to take revenge on those who wronged you and to go back in time to fix the future.
But when the time comes, I will ask for a favor in return.
Deal, Hawk Moth.
Oh, I have to go, Dad.
I can't keep Chamack waiting.
She's listening to music.
Weird.
Run!
Stop, Alix, what are you doing?
My name is Timebreaker now.
And I'm going back in time to save my watch.
And I'm going to use you to do it.
Go back in time?
What did you do?
Why is he disappearing?
I needed his energy.
Besides, that guy with all the bats was super annoying anyway.
He deserves to disappear forever.
And so do you.
We need to transform now.
Tikki, spots on!
Yes.
Time out, Timebreaker.
Please help me.
I'm so bad at this.
Please, I'm begging you.
No.
Sweet thing.
Always thinking of others before yourself.
Wait a minute.
Before everyone disappears forever... I have to get rid of that akuma.
Where is that cat?
What?
Time to transform.
Plagg, claws out!
Come on.
A minute and a half.
You won't be able to stop me where I'm going, Ladybug.
Let me guess.
We're playing tag and you're it.
Exactly.
Don't let her touch you.
You missed by just a second.
No!
She sure doesn't waste any time, does she?
The more people she freezes, the further back in time she goes.
If we can't stop that akuma, the kids frozen in time will never come back.
Get a grip on yourself.
Now Timebreaker, seize her Miraculous, in her earrings.
Cat Noir, no.
Wow, six minutes with one touch.
He must have nine lives.
I have to go, the past awaits me.
Timebreaker, the Miraculous.
Get Cat Noir's ring before he disappears.
Just try it and see.
Calm down, Hawk Moth.
I have a very good plan.
Be patient.
Come on, come on, come on!
What happened?
What just happened?
Wow.
We went back in time, didn't we?
What do you have there?
Careful, that's Alix's.
What does it do?
Is this some kind of old box or something?
If it's Alix's, it's probably useless.
Give it back to Adrien, Chloé.
My watch.
Chloé, put the watch down.
No!
Ladybug, this time it's your fault.
I need more energy.
I have to go even further into the past.
Ladybug, it's all Ladybug's fault.
Could this be possible?
Am I seeing double in my future?
Or should I say double trouble?
Fly away, my evil akuma.
Savor this poor soul.
I can't explain now, but I'm you from a few minutes in the future.
She's right.
I can feel it.
She's you from the future.
Crazy.
Listen.
I know this is unbelievable, but trust me.
I mean, trust yourself.
And Dad is going to call me.
I mean, he's going to call you in two minutes.
He's not happy because Ms. Chamack is waiting for you at the bakery door.
The cake.
But I, I still... have time?
That's what I thought.
Ms. Chamack came early.
Now go and handle the cake situation.
Don't worry.
Ladybug will handle this alone.
How do I get myself into these crazy situations?
Let's go.
Cat Noir, I don't have time to explain.
We have to capture Timebreaker's akuma.
My life depends on it.
Which life?
I have nine.
I'm serious.
The akuma is in her rollerblades.
We have to release it.
Am I seeing double?
Something else I don't have time to explain.
The energy from both of them is more than enough for both of us to go back in time.
I want my watch.
Let's do this.
Whatever you do, don't let either of them touch you.
Take the Miraculous, Timebreaker.
If we work faster, these two can't stand against us.
Then let's gather energy first, then we destroy them.
Just a second, coming.
No problem, thanks.
Everything's fine.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Mission accomplished.
I think you meant mission one.
And now there's mission two.
Tikki, spots on.
Yes.
We have enough speed now.
Let's show Ladybug and Cat Noir what we've got.
Once we take their energy, we'll have time to go back and catch them.
And get our watch.
And you thought we were chasing them.
Need a hand?
Thanks.
They're so fast on those skates.
And unstoppable when they're on the ground.
What if they weren't on the ground?
Two Ladybugs.
I think I'm in heaven.
Plan changed.
We'd better go back in time.
Less of them there.
Works for me.
Let's not fail this time.
They're planning to go back in time.
Lucky Charm.
Got any ideas?
Let me try to buy some time while you figure this out.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Of course.
Let's freeze her while we pass by.
We're going too fast.
We can't stop.
Now.
Come on.
No more evil-doing, little akuma.
Time to de-evilize.
Gotcha.
Goodbye, little butterfly.
Miraculous Ladybug.
Pound it!
I believe this is yours.
Awesome.
How did you fix it?
Thank you.
I shouldn't have given it to someone else to look after.
It was my responsibility.
My fault.
Responsibility isn't something to take lightly.
I should have known.
You're absolutely right.
I'll be more careful next time.
Thank you, Ladybug.
Oh, man.
I was just getting used to there being two Ladybugs.
And now you'll have to get used to there being no Ladybug.
I have to go before I transform back.
One day she'll be mine.
It's only a matter of time.
You managed to escape me this time, Ladybug and Cat Noir.
But one day, whether in the past, present, or future, you will be destroyed.
And I will take your Miraculous.
I will be unstoppable.
So, did you have a nice anniversary?
Yes, of course.
But we had a close call this time.
Yes.
I'm very sorry I kept Ms. Chamack waiting.
Next time, wait for the customers in the bakery.
And not in your room listening to loud music.
Got it.
I promise I won't mess up again.
Good.
Because your mother is absolutely right.
And we trust her.