In most fairy tales, the prince kisses the princess
and breaks the spell. Who can tell me why?
Because only love can conquer hate. Very
true, Rose. Technically, that logic only
applies to 7% of fairy tales.
Thank you, Max. That's enough, Adrien.
I hope what you're writing is related to the lesson.
Can you repeat what I just said?
"That's why in fairy tales, the prince
kisses the princess to break the spell. Because only
love can conquer hate." Very good, Adrien. Listen,
everyone, don't forget to read Charles Perrault's Sleeping Beauty
tonight. And Happy Valentine's
Day. Alya, you go. I'll meet you outside.
Okay.
Hello. Could you sign this, please? Oh, come on,
I hate signing
photos. It's not for him, it's a petition
to protect hamsters.
They're so
creepy. So, are you looking for something? Maybe
a nice outfit to wear?
I was looking. Don't pay any attention to them, they
don't deserve it. You're so right, Tikki. Your hair
as dark as night, your eyes as blue as glass.
I wonder who you are beneath that
strong personality. We see each other every day.
I wish you were mine. Together
our love could be real. Please, will you be
my valentine? Wow, a real love poem!
I wonder who he's talking about. Hair as dark
as night, eyes as blue as glass. That's
you! Me? Don't be silly. There are tons of pretty girls
at school with black hair and blue eyes. Yeah,
but "blue as glass." Hmm. What does he mean
by "strong personality"?
It's a poem. He knows who you are
and wants to get to know you better. Marinette,
he's talking about
you! Are you serious? Plagg?
Not really,
right? Don't you think? Absolutely.
Yeah. We should go somewhere else.
Operation Valentine's Day is on!
According to my in-depth research and
comparisons on online shopping sites,
this jewelry is among the most popular gifts.
This is great, Max. This will really come in
handy. Love is like baseball,
right? You either make a plan or you
strike out. Yeah. Kim? Nice metaphor.
That's really nice. Is this for me? No, Alya,
the recipient of this jewelry has already been determined,
and keep your mouth shut, okay? Great, who's got
a crush? I wonder who this girl is. She's very pretty.
Kim? I'm sure she'll be thrilled. Technically,
I haven't asked her yet. What if she
says no? She'll say yes. Kim! Definitely do
something! Kim! Show yourself! Don't hold back!
Operation Valentine's Day continues.
Her path is marked in yellow. Yours is
in red. If you run at 25 km/h,
you'll get there 4.5 minutes before her.
Stop there, wait, and
look northwest. That's the most romantic
spot in Paris. Go, go, go! Thanks,
guys. I know someone who loves giving advice
but never does anything for himself.
Let's go. You're right, I should have told him. What?
I'm going to do it.
I'll tell him. I can even give him a card,
write it. Yes, yes. Operation Valentine's
Day. Aw, that's so sweet. Dream as much as you want,
girls, but that boy is
mine. To Chloé, the most wonderful girl in the world
and my one true love. Signed, Adrien.
It's not
enough. Dear
Adrien, dear
Adrien... I don't know how to write love letters,
I'm a complete disaster.
Only when you call yourself a disaster... Calm down, Marinette, I'm kidding.
Think of Adrien and write
what comes from your heart.
That's it, Adrien's letter! Why didn't I think of that?
I'll respond to Chloé.
Marinette, look at this! Come on, it's great! Oh,
thank you, thank
you! That's great. Don't forget to sign it!
Hmm. This is a good sign. Ladybugs bring luck,
especially in love. Really, ma'am?
Is that so? Yes, especially you know
ladybugs well. Oh, do I?
Why? Where did that come from? Since ancient times,
ladybugs have been a symbol of love,
guiding hearts to happiness.
It was on my blog this week. Did you read it,
honey? Yes, of course.
Absolutely. I mean, she has eyes, legs,
arms... Who cares? How can you be in love with
a bug? You don't even know who she is.
You know nothing about love. Sure,
I'm in love with Swiss cheese, and French cheese too.
Oh, poor thing is so sad he can't write a poem
to his masked lover. I don't need to write a poem
when I can just tell her.
I love you. Gross! Because of you,
it's all gone.
Gone.
Almost... Here it is. Solid gold frame.
Send this to Le Grand Paris Hotel, and make the bill
out to "Daddykins." Oh, I mean, Mr.
Bourgeois. Ah! What are you doing here? I,
I... You...
Will you be my valentine?
I wonder... Don't move!
Don't! First, everyone needs to
see this. Here, take a look. But my heart belongs
to someone way more amazing than you. Love
hurts so much, doesn't it?
Valentine's Day... The day of love, and of course, fools.
Full of dreams, and full of
disappointments too, of course. My evil
akumas, today is a day full of wickedness.
Fly, my little akuma, and evilize
her. Dark Cupid, I am Hawk Moth. With the power
I give you, your arrows will destroy love
and friendship. But in return, you will do me
a favor. Of course.
Neither love nor friendship can escape me.
No one will fall in love!
Disgusting
flowers! Drop
me! Wonderful. Very soon, Cat Noir and
Ladybug will meet their new
match. Shh, girls. Thanks,
Dad. Come on, Marinette, before you give up,
do
it. Yes,
I did it! Chloé? Since when do you text
us?
I don't know. Look at that witch! I'm the one who told her
to do it. I didn't know she was talking about
him. No way. I hope
Adrien doesn't do the same thing to
you. Hey, girl, calm down. I was just
kidding, sort of. Adrien
wouldn't do that. What is this?
May all hearts
be broken!
Take that! Are you serious? You're not my friend,
you're evil! She's going to die laughing
when she sees this.
Take that! What did he do
to her? I've seen this jewelry before. Whose
brooch is it? It must be because of an akuma.
This is not good. We have to
find him. Alright. Spots on!
I never said 18 karat! These are 24 karat,
they won't match my gold toilet at all!
Incompetents!
Ladybug, stop! Who? Me? No, I'm Dark
Cupid. I will never stop! If I can't find
love, then no one will!
Okay, Dark Cupid, I get it. Chloé really hurt
you, but you can't take out all your anger
on Paris. Yes, I can! And I won't stop
until everyone's heart is broken.
Say adios to your loved ones, because
from now on, you'll hate them!
If you want to keep destroying love,
you'll bring me Ladybug's Miraculous,
otherwise I'll take back your
powers. Are you still after me? Miss,
we need to talk. I have to wait, I promised
myself I'd tell her as soon as I see
Dark Cupid.
Ladybug, I, I... Watch out,
Cat Noir! Ladybug, I'm disgusted
by you! Cat Noir, stop it! You're
nothing! Ladybug, I don't want you,
I hate you!
Ladybug, finally! Where have you been?
You help him and get Ladybug's
Miraculous right away! I'll help you defeat Ladybug,
but you'll give me her Miraculous
in return. That's no problem
at all.
Yes, dealing with the cat will be easy.
You need to get out of here! Your friend Kim turned into
Dark Cupid, and I have no idea what he'll do
if he sees you here. Me? Well, what
could he possibly have against me? Hmm,
think about it. Aah, because of this? Everyone's going crazy
to get one of these. Of course, Adrien,
the handsome boy in class, and super rich too.
Obviously, he's perfect for me. That's not what the
poem said.
Ah, Daddy! Run, Chloé!
Run! Well, well, Ladybug, I'm not going to
fight you. Cat Noir, forget friendship,
there's no need for it. You're not my friend
anymore!
Why are you so full of hate, Cat Noir? Because
hate conquers all! I've got some terrible news
for you: Hate doesn't conquer all, love
does! The prince kisses the princess and breaks the spell,
only love can conquer hate! Stop stalling!
Fight? I'll do better than that.
Here, kitty kitty. Give me
a kiss!
Missed! Come on! Stop! Oh, come here, kitty
kitty!
Come on, you can't escape me!
Chloé!
Help! Happy Valentine's Day, Chloé.
Now you'll get what you deserve. Ah, my hair!
There's nothing worse than going out with bad hair.
First Ladybug wrinkled it when she pulled it,
and now you've completely ruined my hair!
This couldn't be a worse day!
I can't believe it! I'm not going to waste this arrow on you.
Your heart is evil and dark enough, there's no room
for love.
How dare you speak to me like that?
Huh, why are you just standing there? Help
me! You think I'd help a coward
like you?
First, everyone get a taste of
this! No, no, don't worry, I'm not a fan
of this either.
I can't believe I just did that.
Both of us... Let's see how you handle this,
you ugly
thing! Cat?!
Who? I've always wondered what would happen
if I used Cataclysm on
someone. Lucky
Charm! Huh? A candy apple? What am I supposed
to do with this? Think,
Ladybug!
Hey! I've got a special gift for you!
Looks like you're stuck with
the problem, Ladybug.
And now for the kitty.
Cat Noir and his Miraculous,
with pleasure. I'll finally find out
who you are, Ladybug. Your little secret
will now be known
by everyone. What? What am I doing
here? There's no time! The brooch at school!
Cat Noir, catch the brooch! Catch it! No,
sorry, I need this. Happy Valentine's
Day. Oh, you really shouldn't have.
No more evil-doing for you, little
akuma! Let go of the
evil!
Gotcha! Goodbye, little butterfly. Miraculous
Ladybug!
What am I
doing? What are you doing here? Oh, I have
no idea.
None. Pound it! Pound it? Oh, wait, Ladybug,
I have something to tell you. Look, I kissed you, but
it was supposed to break the spell. Wait, kiss me? What
kiss? No, I just... Watch out,
Cat Noir, my face is glowing.
Oh, so is yours, I think. I'm about to turn into
a pumpkin, and I'd really rather not
see that.
Gross Ladybug, gross! Happy
Valentine's Day. Hey, heart... Is there any chance I can
take back my mail? That was ages ago. Ages ago? You know, I realized
that even with all this hate, love
still wins. But if I'm going to win Adrien,
he needs to know my true feelings.
Today is a big
day. Ladybug, can you believe all those horrible,
thoughtless things you said? Do you think
this is funny?
Huh? What's the problem? You've got tons of
cards and postcards from fangirls. Just pick one
and go. Wait a minute, did someone respond to my poem?
But I threw it away! "Your hair shines
like the sun, your eyes are green
like olives. When I look at you, I wonder
what your deepest wish is. Yes, my love,
I will be yours. Our love will be real,
we'll be together forever, my heart belongs
to you." If she writes as beautifully as you,
she must be your soulmate.
It's not signed.
Ah, I wonder if it came from
Ladybug. Ah!
Oh, come on! What do you mean "I don't remember"?
I don't know if I signed it or not.
Just as I was writing it, a ladybug landed on me, then
there was your blog and stuff, and after that,
it's a mystery. I can't believe you! The girl literally
didn't sign it. I love you, but sometimes you're
a total scatterbrain. Aren't you?