Welcome to the most beloved
game show!
It's The Big Challenge!
Please welcome our next contestant!
All right, Nino, both our student
and...
This is truly something great.
Would you like to take a look
at the system we've prepared for you?
Am I in detention? But why?
Rack your brain a little, Marinette.
You were absent Monday morning class.
I was in the study hall.
You weren't in the study hall
Friday afternoon either.
Right, I was in gym class.
You can never be where
you're supposed to be.
The only way for us to know where you are
is for you to stay here.
You're in detention.
But I had invited Nino —
my friend was counting on me.
Our audience has selected
your challenge:
Paris Mayor André Bourgeois.
Thank you for joining us, sir.
Do you think Nino has a chance?
Zero. I hate dancing.
The last time I was on a dance floor,
Madonna was still a baby, kid.
Nino is your friend, I know,
but as long as these unexplained
disappearances continue,
things can't go on like this.
Great. Are they wrong though?
How could they know you're skipping class
to save the world?
Being a superhero in secret
means getting detention at school too.
But I don't think it's fair —
it's just not right.
But look, if Nino wins,
you won't be in detention next week —
you can go and watch him.
Yeah, but Adrien was there today.
The Big Challenge... What an
interesting show.
A program where negative emotions
can come into play.
So many bad things could happen.
Are you serious? How can you say that, Alya?
I'm sorry, but I understand
your father, Marinette.
You're never where you say you'll be,
you're always late,
you mysteriously disappear somewhere.
It's almost like you have another life.
Come on, Alya, you're being a bit silly,
please.
Wait here.
No problem.
Victory! Nino succeeded in his challenge.
You were nodding your head to the beat —
anything else?
That counts as dancing too.
What? That's not right.
Well, my neck was itchy,
that's all. That's it.
Scratching your neck to the rhythm
of the music is also a dance.
Nino, congratulations.
You'll be back here next week
for your next challenge.
And now our next contestant is coming up.
Welcome, Simon Grimault.
That was amazing, dude!
Hey Grimault. You hypnotize people
with cards and make them do
whatever you want, right?
Sure. Yes, I'm a hypnotist, but I can't
make a living from this talent.
And today's challenge:
Simon will use his abilities
to convince an unwilling star
to come onstage.
Now let's hear everyone's applause!
Gabriel Agreste!
What kind of show is this?
I was told I'd be giving an interview, man.
Show your trick, Grimault.
Let's see if you can use your hypnosis
to convince Mr. Agreste
to come onstage.
I told you, I'm a shy hypnotist.
What does that make you?
Interesting, isn't it, Gabriel?
Very funny.
The show is terrible,
and so are the contestants.
Hypnosis? Never.
This is my father.
That's right. It seems Mr. Agreste
is refusing the challenge.
Game over.
But this is unfair!
You didn't even give me a chance!
Yes, humiliation and anger are the very factors
that can turn a loser into a winner.
Fly, my little akuma,
and infect him with evil.
I am Hawk Moth. From now on,
your name is Simon Says.
I will make you the world's
most successful hypnotist.
And when the time comes,
you will help me in return.
Of course, what do you say?
Do we have a deal?
Simon Says... Simon says yes.
Simon says the show isn't over yet.
What's going on?
Silence! You're all pathetic.
You're all chickens.
Simon says stop!
Simon says act like pigs!
I have to go, Alya. Have fun.
I'll babysit now, Tikki.
What am I going to do?
I'm in detention.
You have no choice, you have to transform.
But we need to be more careful.
Take the pillow from under the blanket.
Not bad.
Tikki? Spots on!
Gabriel Agreste refused my challenge.
He'll pay for it. Tonight at midnight
he'll be entertaining us all in this studio.
Gabriel, I'm coming for you, father.
Too risky. But I have an idea.
Good luck.
Simon Says: Give me those cards
and be quiet, Cat Noir.
I'll deal with you.
Simon says drive everyone away!
Even if I don't always land
on all fours, I always bounce back.
Should I have an army?
Simon says: You are all soldiers!
Simon says: Search all of Paris!
My army, find Gabriel Agreste!
We need to be careful. As you taught me,
size doesn't matter.
Ladybug, hello. Are you okay?
I'm fine, but my friend is
somewhere inside. I'll find him.
Cataclysm!
Hello, Ladybug.
That's enough! Cataclysm!
Good to see you too, Cat Noir.
Sorry, I mistook you for Simon Says.
I saw him — he has a massive army with him.
He must be after Gabriel.
We need to reach him before the army does.
Cat Noir, you're about to transform back.
Let me check on Nino's friends
one last time.
Forget it, they've definitely been hypnotized.
But he's my friend.
You're right, maybe he can hide.
You go look for him.
Then let's meet at Gabriel's house.
See you there.
Finding him will be child's play.
Claws out! Hide, Nino!
Adrien! Buddy, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Hello? Hello? Are you really okay?
I'm fine, really. But we need to go
to my house right away —
my father is in danger!
Let's go, we'll meet Cat Noir there.
Nathalie! Where's my father?
He's in trouble. He already knows.
Good evening, Ladybug.
Dad, you need to leave —
the hypnotist Simon Says is after you.
What? Should I run from a madman? Never.
But father, he's very dangerous —
who knows what he might do to you!
Go to your room now,
you've had enough excitement for today.
Nathalie, make sure
they don't go outside.
I apologize on behalf of my son, Ladybug.
He's just like his mother —
a bit too dramatic.
But he's quite right too.
Simon Says is dangerous —
you're in danger as well.
With you here protecting me,
what could possibly happen to me?
Are you sure your father
isn't some kind of robot?
According to him,
I understand nothing about anything.
Dude, your room is bigger
than a small stadium.
Please make yourself comfortable —
I'm going to take a shower.
Right now? What can I say —
I'm a model.
Why does my father never listen to me?
Claws out! How perfect...
What? I don't understand —
my son is a perfect child, isn't he?
Yes, perfect. I mean, I don't know him
very well, but it seems that...
I noticed your earrings before —
they're really quite fascinating.
May I take a look?
Excuse me. Cat Noir! Where were you?
I... I was keeping Simon Says busy.
And Cat Noir — I couldn't hold him off for long.
He's on his way and there's a huge crowd.
Seal all the exits —
they're coming from every direction.
Do as I say —
activate the defense systems.
Everything must be locked down.
Lockdown successful.
How do you know this system so well?
In a house like this? I guessed.
They can't get in —
this house is as solid as a fortress.
Simon says: Destroy it!
The strain is too much.
The system won't hold.
Seal the entrances and exits —
we'll operate the controls together here if needed.
I'll help with the outer defense.
You hide somewhere.
This place is safe.
Stop telling me what to do!
Just do what I say!
Pretty grumpy. Reminds me of someone.
I don't think this is a good idea.
Simon Says: "Gabriel is here."
Yes, but don't forget our deal.
Ladybug and Cat Noir should be nearby.
When you face them,
fulfill our agreement —
take their jewelry,
their Miraculouses.
It will finally be over.
Simon says: I will defeat them!
Ladybug, what's going on?
Let's move somewhere safer.
Where's Adrien?
He was taking a shower.
Right now? Well, he is a model.
Take Nino to the garden —
I'll handle Adrien. Leave the remote with me.
Adrien?
Yes? Maybe we should go?
It's dangerous — very dangerous.
Can I get dressed first?
Of course, go ahead.
Sure, sure, get dressed and we can go.
Absolutely. Where's my son?
He's coming — he's with Ladybug.
Ha! This is my mother —
on her 17th birthday. She was a beautiful woman.
You have the same eyes.
Stay here. Oh, what's all this?
Is this love or something?
Ha? What do you say?
I need to help.
Claws out!
Are they coming again?
I've got you, Cat Noir!
Yes, that was great.
Welcome to the new episode of The Big Challenge!
Hello everyone again — I'm Simon Says.
Audience, I kept my promise —
here is Gabriel!
Simon says: You are a butterfly!
Fly, fly, fly, fly!
Come on, fly!
Fly! We have to save Mr. Agreste.
Butterfly, I'm going to destroy you now.
The akuma must be in one of those cards —
but which one?
There are so many of them!
Ladybug, Cat Noir —
give me your Miraculouses
and he can be saved. Now give up!
In your dreams. Lucky Charm!
Just a yo-yo? But I thought
it had some magical use.
We can figure that out later. Ha?
Simon says: Your yo-yo is useless!
Simon Says: "Your staff
is useless too?" I don't think so.
I won't give you any more chances to speak.
Simon Says.
Fly, come on, fly!
He's heading for the roof —
we have to stop him.
I can't do this alone.
If we can free Simon,
we can save Mr. Agreste too.
Then we can't waste any more time.
But without my yo-yo —
how are you going to beat him?
Simon says: It's over!
Follow me.
Cataclysm!
Miraculous Ladybug!
This can't be — the yo-yo wasn't working.
That one wasn't. But this one works.
Yo-yo! You won't be able to do
any more evil, little akuma!
Bye bye, little butterfly.
Pound it!
Fist bump! Seems your touch
sensor stopped working.
Sir, if you were my Ladybug...
Actually, Cat Noir, you're not wrong.
Your face...
You'd better leave now.
Running away like a cat on a rooftop.
Until we meet again,
Mr. Agreste.
We'll see you too.
I've never seen your face before.
That's because there's a lot about me
you haven't noticed.
I'm so glad everything worked out.
Welcome back to the number one
game show!
It's The Big Challenge!
Last week our DJ friend Nino
completed the big challenge.
Now we're hearing from him again.
Come on up, DJ!
It looks like you haven't
been late at all this week, my boy.
That's wonderful — well done.
You can join your friends on set.
I'd rather watch from here.
Mom won't mind, I think.
Tonight the challenge level
has been raised a bit.
Nino will need to make not one
but two celebrities dance.
But now you get to choose who.
This should be a cinch —
I'll choose two people
I think won't turn me down:
Ladybug and Cat Noir.
Actually, I'm a bit tired — I should catch some sleep
so I won't be late for school tomorrow.
And after all, I shouldn't let my grades slip.
You'll fill me in, of course, darling.
I honestly don't understand
that girl sometimes.
But we'd better not push it.
There's nothing harder than going to school,
as you know.