Thanks to Mr. Bourgeois' generosity, we are conducting
the fieldwork required for our work experience
at the Grand Paris Luxury Hotel. Each of you
will gain experience from any job
you can perform within the
hotel.
Whether you pass or fail the course will be determined
by the work you
complete.
I know who my father assigned to whom. Obviously,
the one who gets to spend the whole day with Adrien.
This is going to be the worst day
of my life. It must have been overlooked.
Dad. Thank you, sweetheart. Yes, you'll be sorting
trash in the garbage collection area.
Sweetie. And Marinette's assignment is...
Well... Wow.
Hey!
I'm sorry, but this is a luxury hotel,
not a disco. Dad, that man is Jagged
Stone! A rock star who has sold millions of albums
and is super famous. He's also incredibly
rich. Mr. Stone, welcome to the Grand Paris Hotel.
I am Mayor Bourgeois, and I own this
luxurious establishment. In fact, we can say it's
the most luxurious hotel in Paris. How may I
be of service? How do you think? I didn't come here
to admire the lobby. Jagged wants
the most luxurious suite we have.
And Fang needs a real bathtub. Don't give him
a tiny water bowl like the one across the street.
We have every amenity here, Mr. Fang. We even have
a state-of-the-art
gym. Fang is my
crocodile, Stone. I'm sure we can accommodate
all his needs. So, would he like
a bubble bath, perhaps? A croc doesn't like
bubble baths, it dries out his
scales.
No way, is that him again? Do you remember me, Mr. Stone?
Vincent Aza! I need to take a photo and show everyone
that we're friends. Come on,
please, I'm your biggest fan. Look, I know you've been
to my last 36 concerts, but we are not
friends.
There! Huh? Did you not hear that? Do you still
not understand? No
photo. Gotcha now! Don't let me see you
near him again, or you'll never get your camera
back.
I sense a growing hatred and anger. A perfect
prey for my little evil akumas. This rage
will not subside.
Fly, my little akuma, and evilize
him. Pixelator, I am Hawk Moth. I offer you the chance
to capture your hero's smile.
But in return, you will give me something
in return. Of course, don't forget. Yes!
Mr. Bourgeois. Marinette, you still haven't told me what
job I'll be doing. Yes, of course. Yes, well... Fetch and carry.
I've written down this job for you, sweetie.
What's that? Fetch and carry? I guess it's not as bad
as the trash
job. Ah, Jagged Stone needs new glasses for his concert
tonight. Red, white, and blue,
with an Eiffel Tower design on them.
Can you find them? We'll find them. Marinette
handles these things. She'll take care of it for you,
don't worry. Your job is to meet
the needs of the guests, whatever
they may be. Whatever they may be! Now go on,
off you go! Go fetch.
Come on. I think this will do. Now I can go back
to the hotel and hang out with Adrien. And Chloé
and them? If you haven't noticed, these look nothing like
what Mr. Stone asked for. Well, Tikki,
there are red and white Eiffel Towers all around.
If you do your job right the first time, you'll have it
easier later on.
Where are the Eiffel Towers? Right over there.
You're joking, right? What is this?
Are you trying to ruin my career?
Jagged, the glasses you wanted aren't here. Do I look
like I care? Go find those glasses for me!
Great, now I'll be even further away
from Adrien. Unbelievable! That's what I was telling you,
you need to do your job properly the first time,
Marinette. Ah, you're right, Tikki.
Now I get it. Those glasses must be
somewhere around here. Be creative. Oh, right!
Well? Couldn't you do it? I'm not surprised.
Don't even think about slamming the door on your way out.
Excuse me, sir, can I help you?
Look into the
lens. Photo!
Look who's here! I'll handle
this. Adrien, watch and learn.
Excuse me, can I help you? You cannot stay
in this hotel. My father only accepts the most important
celebrities. Like me, I mean. How
nice! My name is Pixelator, I'm your biggest fan.
Is that so? Oh, you flatter me. Do go
on. Let's take a photo, madam.
Chloé. Of course. Be careful, Chloé, look at the
lens.
Chloé! What is this? What just happened? Hmm,
I think we've entered some sort of digital space.
What do you mean, digital space? I don't know
exactly, but I don't think it's a good thing.
Whatever, I can handle this. Leave it to me.
Dad!
Dad?
Ah, where did I put it? Ah,
there it is! But those glasses are pink. They won't be pink
for long. They'll either be the most amazing glasses
in the world, or the ugliest glasses
in history. Ms. Bustier will grade me on this,
won't she? Don't worry, I'm sure
Jagged Stone will love them.
Or maybe
he won't. I still can't reach my dad. How can there be
no phone signal here? This is ridiculous! Hmm, this path
has no end. There's no door, no wall,
nothing. So we're stuck here?
I mean... Just the two of us? No, there must be
a way out
somewhere. I hope.
Of course, Adrien!
Chloé is probably doing something fun with him
right now. I'm stuck here all alone, without Adrien.
Marinette, this is not the time. You need to try and find
Jagged Stone's glasses. Okay?
Jagged Stone!
What? Look at the lens! I'll get them
to him. Can't you give them to him now? He's resting
right now. I'm trying to
get him to let me scratch his belly. Got it, thanks.
I hope Mr. Stone likes this. If you work hard,
you'll get your
reward. And who are you? Look at the lens!
Time to transform. Alright.
Spots on! Hello! Time for a photoshoot.
How did you get in here? I didn't have
a photoshoot scheduled. Fang, attack!
See you later.
Crocodile
Fang! Who are you? My name is Pixelator, your biggest fan,
Mr. Stone. Can I call you Jagged?
No. I'm going to immortalize
you. I'll be your only fan. You'll be mine
forever! Now
look into the lens, Jagged. It's you. I've heard a lot
of pathetic things about you. Look at the lens!
Where did they go? If you want Jagged, you have to find
Ladybug. I don't have time to deal with
Ladybug. Oh yes you do, you have plenty of time.
Okay, okay. Just tell me what you want.
And I want a great photo of your Miraculous.
I want your powers. Now listen to me very carefully:
I can't stay here, I have a concert tonight. Don't
worry, you'll make it to your concert. And you'll
even get to wear your awesome
glasses. Look, while I go catch this Pixelator,
you stay here and don't let anyone
see you. Ladybug, is this safe? This is
a school. Yes. The person Pixelator is obsessed with
is in a
school. I mean, school is a nice place, isn't it?
This is ridiculous. I'm not dealing with this.
First, this crazy fan kidnaps me,
then a weird superhero attacks me.
And wait! What else do you know about this fan?
He came to all my concerts this year.
He also sent me tons of letters,
I threw them all away. He also followed my mom
when she went to bingo. How
terrible! It's not that bad, just a bunch of old
ladies getting together to have some fun.
Vincent! I found the address. You're not going to leave me
here, are you? I mean, isn't school
just great?
Plagg! I need to find a place to transform.
Oh, come on, what's the
rush? I gotta pee. I'll look for cheese until you get back.
You stay here, it could be very
dangerous. Dangerous? What, are you
scared or something? Scared? Me? Never,
ever.
No way! Ah!
Wonderful! Let the photoshoot begin!
Amateur! This is too much!
What? What
is this? Ladybug!
What are you doing
here? Ladybug! Do you remember
me? I'm your biggest fan. Please, please
get us out of here! This place is horrible.
I mean, it's horrible when you're not here. I guess
so. I'm here, Ladybug,
help
us! What happened to you? It's terrible. That
man took our picture and then trapped us
in here. We were just minding our own business.
I'm sure Cat Noir is already on his way
over there.
Excuse me, sir! Sir, would you like to give an interview
to the host of the Voice of the Villains
program?
I will continue taking photos until Jagged Stone
comes here himself. Where are you, Jagged? Your biggest
fan is waiting. All I want is one
photo. Otherwise, very soon the people of Paris
will each become a single
frame.
This is awful! I have to do what Pixelator says.
No, you can't be serious. That place is too
dangerous. Danger? Who
cares? Jagged Stone wouldn't miss a chance
to be on TV. Think about what this could do
for my career.
Do it! We sure do love taking photos,
apparently.
Ha!
Yeah! Bravo, that was great! I've been waiting
for you, Ladybug.
Look at the lens!
I have a proposition
for you. If you release those innocent people,
I'll make sure you get a photo with Jagged Stone.
Okay?
No, don't listen to her. She's trying to trick you.
Why should I trust you, Ladybug?
Because you have no other choice. I'm the only one
who knows where Jagged is. Alright, how about I release
half now, and the other half after the
shoot? Do we have a deal? Okay,
it's a deal. You'll
be waiting a while. Ah, buddy, you scared me. Uh,
could you cover for me, Nino? What have I been doing
all this time?
What do you think? If you ask me, I'd say
someone got akumatized. I think you're right,
but where's the akuma? Plagg,
claws out! I did my part, here you go,
Ladybug. Now bring me Jagged Stone.
Pixelator, I know the akuma is in your glasses.
Stop wasting time!
Yes, there!
Cat Noir! Thanks for stopping
by. This isn't going to work, is it? What about our deal?
I told you she was playing you.
Capture them all, quickly! I want your
Miraculous!
Together.
Again?
When the cat's away, the mice will play.
Are you ready to become immortal? Really.
I can't wait! Look into the lens! Hello,
Pixelator, the person you wanted a photo of
is finally here.
Finally, you've shown
yourself. Get out of here,
quick! I'm the one you wanted all along,
aren't I? Here I am, in the flesh.
Look at the
lens! Wait, wrong side. I'm more handsome
from over here. Stop, the light is wrong.
Is this better, or smaller? Got it, this
is better. Come on, hurry up!
Lucky
Charm!
Huh? Face powder? Yes, that's it! Now I'm
ready. Don't move, look at the
lens! No, don't! Wait! Cataclysm!
Yes! Come on, open your
eyes. Ready?
What? How? But... Huh?
Next time, it won't take this
long.
No more evil-doing for you.
Akuma, let go of the evil!
Gotcha! Goodbye, little
butterfly. What happened to me? Where am I?
Pound
it! Thank you for this work experience day,
Mr. Bourgeois. I'm sure none of us
will forget this for a long time.
Yes, I, well... Wait, I almost forgot. Stone has
a concert tonight, so as a thank you
for the students' efforts, I am giving each of you
a ticket.
This is ridiculous! I mean, completely
ridiculous. Goodnight,
Paris! This is the first concert I've ever been to
in my life. It was amazing.
Yes, amazing! I dedicate this song to the girl
who saved my life. This one's for you,
Ladybug!