Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, Adrien!
Plagg, get that stinky Camembert away from my nose right now!
Marinette, don't forget to clean your room
after school today. Mom, it's Friday and I'm already
doing something with Alya.
Alright then, I'll clean it. But don't blame me
if I come across anything... personal.
Okay, I'll do it. I'll
do it. Have a good day, sweetie. Happy birthday!
I mean, have a good
day. Here's my schedule, Adrien.
Thanks, Nino. Hey, did your dad get back to you about my
birthday party? Oh, he doesn't think it's a good idea.
Of course he doesn't. Happy birthday!
Adrien. Really? Has your dad always been this
boring? Doesn't he know what it's like to be young and
just want to have fun? Honestly, I'm sure he was
boring back then too. At least we tried. It's your birthday,
buddy. Be persistent. You can do it.
You can do it. I can do it. I can do it.
You know what? I'm going to have a talk
with your dad. Don't waste your time, he won't
change his mind. I can't.
I can't. Enough, girl! You've been putting this off
all morning. The time has
come.
Hello? Wait, am I seeing what I think I'm seeing?
Don't tell me today is Adrien's
birthday!
I have to do everything myself. Seriously, what good
are you?
I... I wanted to make you a gift. I mean, give you a gift.
I made it, right here.
Happy
birthday! Yeah, thanks.
Did you get the gift I sent
you? No. What? Those delivery guys... I'm sure they went
to get help because it was so heavy,
the lazy bums. I'll make sure you get it
tonight.
Get back in there. Don't be a coward,
Marinette.
What did you actually get him? I didn't. Did you get him something?
It better be amazing and not be late.
Come on.
You can do it. I have to go.
The shoot... Why can't you say what I want you to say,
instead of what you want to say? Exactly.
Apparently, I have some business to settle
with Adrien's father.
This mailbox won't open. Ring the doorbell.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me. What if Adrien answers?
Ha, yeah, um...
Hello, I'm in Adrien's class
and did I mention
that? Put it in the
box. Thank
you. I hope he likes it. You sent the note,
right? Oh, what are we going to do with you?
Who was that? Nathalie. One of Adrien's friends
brought him a gift for his birthday. Did you
remember to get him a gift from me? But you didn't
ask me to. Of course I did. Yes, Mr. Agreste,
I'll take care of it.
Good. Yes, um...
Hello. He'll be here any
minute. Adrien isn't home yet. I came to see
you. What? Me, sir?
Yes, that's right. I know you don't want Adrien
to have a party, but today is his birthday,
man. I mean, sir, it's all he wants.
No, this is final. But that's
awful. He never fails his classes, he does
whatever you say, photoshoots, fencing, Chinese,
piano... Nino, you're here. I would do anything
for my best friend. Cut us some slack, dude.
I mean,
sir, please.
Forget it. It's really okay.
Listen, man, I've decided what's best
for my son.
In fact, I've decided you're a bad influence and
you're no longer welcome in my house. Leave,
now. Dad, he was just trying to do something nice
for me.
Goodbye. Wait. I'm sorry, my dad is really
stubborn. I think it's best not to get in his
way. That's not fair. It's harsh, it's not
right. Thanks anyway.
But Dad, please! No, it's not playtime. You have
things to
do. Adults always ruin everything. He wants to help
his friend but feels powerless. How
frustrating. It won't take long for that frustration
to turn into
anger.
Fly, my little akuma, and
evilize
him. My name is Hawk Moth. Yours is
the Bubbler. I will help you deal with these mean adults.
But all you have to do is get me something
from Ladybug and Cat Noir. Yes,
Hawk Moth.
No adults means total freedom. That's
awesome.
Out of
bounds! Watch out, run! Run, run,
run! Help!
Perfect! Adrien must have gotten his gift.
What did you say, dear? I can't wait
to go back to school
this afternoon,
Mom.
Mom? Dad? Dad? Their parents... Hmm, it must be
another akuma. So we have to find this new villain
immediately.
Tikki?
Spots on! And now it's party time! Today is your lucky
day, little ones! The adults are on vacation today.
Have as much fun as you can. No work, no homework,
no complaints! Just fun!
What, are you kidding? Don't worry, our parents
will come around, I'll make sure of it. In the meantime,
you take care of
them!
Wow, this is going to be a birthday to remember!
Lunch break's over.
Hooray! Nathalie, Dad!
Huh?
Hawk Moth. Hello, birthday boy! Guess what, your dad is gone
and while the cats are away, the mice will play.
Nino, the Bubbler, has gathered all your friends
for one single purpose:
To celebrate! Yes!
Yes, let's get this party started! Yeah!
Come on, people, I brought you here to have fun!
Dance, or I'll send you up to the sky
with the adults! It won't be long before
Ladybug and Cat Noir come to meet their
fate.
What's wrong with you? Relax, you're having
fun. But Nino is under the akuma's influence,
I have to help him. We may never get another chance
like this. Let's have some fun while your dad's away,
then we'll save Nino, capture the akuma, and
everything will be back to
normal. Okay. You're so right. This could actually be
the first day I get to do whatever
I want.
It's just you and me, Bubbler.
Yeah! Hey, nice party! I guess it's because it's
my first party.
Can we get a slow dance? Uh,
isn't it a little early for that?
It's your first slow dance, Adrien. You know what you're doing.
Girl, is it just me or does everyone look a bit
weird? Forget about them, let's just go have
fun. Come on!
Ha! This can't be happening. Lucky
Charm! Huh? A record?
Nice! Dude, who hacked my system? Me, of
course. I better disappear before I turn
back. Spots
off.
Marinette, this was an emergency. Yeah, if by emergency
you mean jealousy. I know what happens
when you use your Lucky Charm. I'll be back to normal
in a few minutes,
I know. But I figured the Bubbler isn't going anywhere.
There's time to get you something to eat
to boost your energy. Then we'll go back,
I promise.
I need to find a place to change quickly. Where was it?
You... I was so scared something had happened to you.
Me too. I'm sure Ladybug and Cat Noir will be here
any minute to save us. They've never
let us down. Come with me, I found
something for you. Oh, I have something to do
first. It's about
Adrien. Okay, Marinette. The Bubbler... Okay,
okay, just a
second.
Look, can you just sign your gift
now? Yeah. Hey, why aren't you having fun?
None of your business. Then I'll make it my
business. With love,
Marinette.
Done. Okay, we're good. Spots on! Marinette, I can't
right now, Alya is here. What did you say? Go on,
I'll meet you in the
yard. No, you were right, Tikki. We shouldn't wait
this long. How are you!
What? Ladybug!
Sorry, Bubbler, but the party's over.
Why do you have to be like this? You made all the
adults disappear, that's why. And now you're locking up
everyone who isn't having fun. You ruined my party!
I guess. Okay, that's enough.
Claws out! Looks like I got here just in time.
I had it under control, but... Thanks.
Catch them! I want those powers, now!
Give me your Miraculous before you run out of air!
In your dreams, Bubbler. Just like adults, you don't know
how to party. Kids need
adults. Kids need freedom and fun,
to relax and live. Adults are
controlling. But adults protect children,
they take care of their kids, they love them. Well,
most adults do. You need to bring the adults
back. No, never! You know what, if you care
so much about adults, why don't you
go hang out with them for a while?
You think the Bubbler was supposed to get their Miraculous? You should have
used Cataclysm!
Couldn't you have told me that 150 meters ago?
I mean, we can't stay here
forever.
Cataclysm!
This time we'll see if you land on your feet.
No, leave it. Your baton over
there. Okay.
Good thing cats aren't afraid of heights. We need to
get to the bubble source, the akuma must be
there.
We better hurry. Where is everyone? Sorry we
burst your bubble on the way to your
party.
Your friends left and they're never coming
back.
I'm about to transform, hurry! Lucky
Charm! Plumbing skills are going to help
us?
You can work a little. Is this all you've
got?
Got it. Cat Noir, cover
me! Keep it up!
Get out of here, you nasty bug! No more evil-doing for you,
little akuma!
Time to de-evilize!
Gotcha! Goodbye, little
butterfly. Miraculous Ladybug!
Oh, man. Pound it! You can't run forever,
Ladybug. And when I catch you, I'll crush you.
I'll destroy you
both.
Nathalie, did my son like his gift? Actually, I was
just about to check, sir.
Good.
Ah, a birthday present! So it's from
your dad. Thank you. I mean, thank my dad
for me, please.
What do you mean, a week? There were no adults to deliver
them yesterday. So what? This is ridiculous,
completely ridiculous!
These are Chloé. She got what she deserved.
Hey, girls. Hey, that's my scarf! He's wearing
my scarf! What's up, buddy? Hey, your scarf is so
cool. It's awesome. Yeah, can you believe my dad
gave me this? It's great. He'd been giving me the
same boring pen for three years,
you know? Wow, I guess people can change.
Adults can surprise you when you least
expect it. Speaking of adults, I know
your dad said I was a bad influence.
It's no big deal, Adrien.
Don't worry. We're friends, always
and forever.
You should tell him you made that scarf. But he was so happy
when he thought it was from his dad, I don't want
to ruin that.
Marinette, you're incredible, you know
that? And one day Adrien will
realize it too, I
promise.
Marinette, you're incredible, you know that? And one day
Adrien will realize it too, I promise.