Don't go anywhere, because we're in Paris right now.
Everyone, I'd like to present our famous Uğur Böceği.
What's that?
Uğur Böceği in action.
Hold on tight, we're about to take flight.
Unbelievable.
This isn't just any ordinary book.
This is a 10th grade history textbook.
I know because I have the same book.
Or is our dear Uğur Böceği a scholar?
Could that be?
I told you from day one, Tikki.
I'm a total klutz.
What's done is done.
There's nothing we can do about it.
We'd better look forward.
Alya must never find out who I am.
You know how much she cares about that blog she writes about Uğur Böceği, don't you?
But how?
Maybe I'm just not cut out for this kind of thing.
You're the chosen one, Marinette.
Everything will work out.
Trust me.
Everyone learns something from their past.
And that's the reason.
The Louvre Museum exhibition?
Pharaoh Tutankhamun?
What does that have to do with the book and Alya?
You have to make sure Alya comes there and brings her book with her.
You can tell her you know something about Uğur Böceği.
To the museum?
You'll see.
But how do I convince Alya to come to an ancient Egyptian exhibition?
Without making it obvious that I'm not Uğur Böceği?
This will really interest her.
And you too, of course.
I promise.
Can you believe it?
Once I find out who this history book belongs to, the mission is complete.
We're going to find out Uğur Böceği's real identity.
I've gotten so close this time.
So you think you can find Uğur Böceği with a book that every high school student has?
Yes.
Because only our school uses this book.
I need to find out which girl in 10th grade lost her book last week.
Not counting myself, there are only 43 girls.
42.
Don't count yourself.
Or me.
In class yesterday, someone forgot to bring their book.
What?
I forgot it at home.
You know how forgetful I am.
I'm just teasing you, Marinette.
But I can't overlook you either until you bring your book to history class.
Nothing happened.
I'm fine too.
It's no problem at all.
Sorry about that.
You're in the same class as Alix, right?
I'm her older brother.
Jalil Kubdel.
Are you also passionate about Tutankhamun?
Dad!
Strange.
Look, let me ask again.
Why are we here?
Does this exhibition have anything to do with Uğur Böceği?
I'm serious.
Well... Huh?
Yes.
Right there.
Hold on tight.
We're about to take flight.
Oh, unbelievable.
This isn't just any ordinary book.
This is a 10th grade history textbook.
I know because I have the same book.
Or is our dear Uğur Böceği a scholar?
Could that be?
This is crazy.
How is it that we use the same book?
Maybe we even go to the same school.
Then you must know each other.
Why would I bother with girls when there's food?
First of all, girls smell a thousand times better than that cheese.
Besides, they're really pretty.
Suit yourself.
No problem.
My only problem is losing my appetite.
Come on, just tell me who it is.
No way, no way.
Otherwise it won't be a surprise.
It would spoil the fun.
I'm very serious, Dad.
Somewhere in the hieroglyphics.
Excuse me.
As you know, the one holding the scepter is the pharaoh Tutankhamun.
And facing him is Princess Nefertiti.
Behind them are exactly one hundred mummies.
She died a few years before the king.
And the sun god Ra made her a goddess.
Yes, I know all of that.
Because I'm the director of this exhibition.
If you recall.
Then you also know that Tutankhamun wanted to bring the princess back to life.
He offered Ra a new deal.
This paragraph depicts the ritual performed.
No one had fully deciphered these hieroglyphics.
I did.
To complete this ritual, a magical incantation must be spoken.
I'm sure of it.
There was someone else with such ridiculous ideas... You.
You may find my ideas about Uğur Böceği ridiculous.
But watch closely.
Because you will be wrong.
Jalil, what these illustrations depict is just a legend.
There's a reason for that.
Everyone thinks that, but I'm sure it's real.
I can prove it.
Oh, really?
And how exactly are you going to prove it?
By holding Tutankhamun's scepter and speaking the words.
Are you serious?
Don't even think about touching it, understand?
I'll lose my job the moment it's noticed.
That's a priceless historical artifact.
It's not a toy.
Don't do this, Dad. We need to test this magic.
What if Tutankhamun found a way to resurrect people?
Jalil, that's enough.
Lift your head up from those papyruses and focus on the real world, okay?
This world.
It's not wrong to get lost in a fantasy.
Especially when you can turn it into reality.
Fly away, my little akuma.
Go and take that man's form.
Let him go.
I'm going to show you the secret I found about Uğur Böceği, okay?
Finally.
I hope this blog works too.
Pharaoh, I am Hawk Moth.
I'm endowing you with the magical powers of the ancient gods.
In return, you owe me a debt.
My beloved Nefertiti will come back to life.
My eyes hurt from looking at this.
Look harder, it's written there.
Hey, you!
Stop! Time, stand still!
Alya!
Run!
Get out of here!
Quick!
We have to transform!
Tikki!
Spots on!
Great!
We're back again, Ladyblog fans.
I'm on the scene right now, even before Uğur Böceği and Kara Kedi.
This is incredible!
Wow!
How his face changed!
I think you should try it too.
Time to transform!
Plagg!
Claws out!
You know this is called stealing.
I'm just taking back what already belongs to me.
Maybe if you were the real pharaoh.
But you're not.
Would you look at Uğur Böceği.
If this is a dream, don't wake me up.
Uğur Böceği, you're magnificent, even when you're shaking.
Sekhmet, grant me your power.
How thoughtful of you to hold the door for me.
Sweet dreams.
That was absolutely crazy.
Watch very closely.
Hello.
My face.
Fate has brought you before me.
Come with me.
Put me down. I can walk on my own.
Really?
Let her go.
Are you using a girl as a shield?
You are weak, Pharaoh.
I am much stronger than you.
And don't forget, all the behind-the-scenes footage is on my blog.
Alya is such a brave girl.
If by brave you mean determined, enterprising, and fearless, then yes, that's her.
Let's get out of here, Kara Kedi.
Cataclysm.
How can we find them?
Even Alya is live-streaming from him.
Hello everyone, I'm Alya.
I'm on the shoulders of a terrifying villain.
This is huge.
Don't go away.
You go ahead.
I'll join you when my Miraculous is recharged.
Hurry.
We can only defeat him together.
Now for the second phase.
Anubis, mummies, come forth.
We'll be together again soon, my Nefertiti.
My greatest love.
This is going to be huge.
Excuse me, Pharaoh, but what exactly are we doing right now?
I'm about to perform the sacred magic.
And Nefertiti will return.
I see.
You mean the spell on the papyrus, right?
Correct.
One hundred mummies and a sacrifice.
A sacrifice?
What kind of sacrifice?
I need to give something to Ra to convince him to give back his beloved princess.
A pure soul.
Good luck finding that, buddy.
But I've already found one.
You look so much like her.
What do you mean?
Hang on, Alya.
Oh no, I'm stuck in the time bubble.
I need to get out of here.
It's me, Uğur Böceği. I've learned that Alya is going to be sacrificed to the sun god. Please hurry, please.
Hang on, Alya.
I'm here now.
Are you saying that stuff like the sun god and monkeys are real?
You're so disrespectful.
The batteries are charged enough now.
Plagg, claws out!
Ahhh!
Thanks for waiting for me.
No problem.
We need to find that akuma before the poor girl gets sacrificed.
I can't see the Pharaoh or her.
Look, there.
Hey, wait a minute.
Who's that goddess lady on the black spot?
Look at the papyrus.
Uğur Böceği is my arch-enemy.
She's the one who stopped me from completing my family five thousand years ago.
But this time, she won't stop me from bringing my Nefertiti back to life.
What did you say?
Did you say Uğur Böceği?
Were you talking to me?
Five thousand years ago?
Everyone has a past they can learn from.
I think you're at most three thousand years old.
That's why I'm so much wiser than you.
Great Ra, sun god.
I, the Pharaoh, wish to sacrifice this pure soul to you for Nefertiti.
I offer you my words and my sacrifice.
Together we pray for the return of Princess Nefertiti.
Awaken, Nefertiti, awaken.
We have to save her before he completes the ritual.
Otherwise she'll be gone forever.
What can we do?
You handle the mummies while I deal with the Pharaoh.
Why do I have to deal with these freaks while you get the fun part?
Because I'm the only one who can catch his akuma.
Besides, you're the bravest one of us.
Sure.
I know you don't think that, but I don't care.
Awaken, Nefertiti!
Awaken!
Hello, you bandaged wretches.
Let's get this over with.
Kara Kedi.
Catch them!
Is this really your fastest?
Wait.
This feels like a trap.
Great.
You've just witnessed another incredible move from Uğur Böceği.
Thanks for saving me.
No problem.
But it's not over yet.
First... First, Uğur Böceği needs to destroy the akuma in her earrings and fix everything.
I'm careful.
The earrings.
You thought well.
That was great, Uğur Böceği.
No.
You won't win this time, Uğur Böceği.
Help, Uğur Böceği!
Crush that bug!
Uğur Böceği!
What's this?
Kara Kedi, this way!
We need to save Alya before she reaches the dark circle.
You cannot stop me from bringing Nefertiti back.
I will destroy you.
Bring me my Anubis mummies.
Grant me the wings of Horus.
Kara Kedi, on the earring.
The reading is right there.
Sekhmet, grant me your power.
It's over.
Uğur Böceği, save me!
Ra!
God of the sun!
Accept this humble sacrifice and return my princess to me!
Lucky Charm!
A Uğur Böceği costume?
This is our last resort?
This sacrifice is not enough for Nefertiti.
Hey, thank you.
Too late, Uğur Böceği, the ritual has already begun.
Wait, let Alya go and sacrifice me instead.
Wouldn't that be sweet revenge?
After all, I was the one who took Nefertiti from you five thousand years ago.
You would certainly make a much better sacrifice than this mortal.
Horus, grant me your wings.
What?
Are you serious?
Excuse me.
But she would have been a much better sacrifice than me.
Go ahead, Miraculous.
The earrings.
You win, Pharaoh.
You want my Miraculous?
Here you go.
Catch.
A toy.
You tricked me.
You can't do evil anymore, little akuma.
Let the evil pass.
That's it.
Goodbye, little butterfly.
Miraculous Uğur Böceği.
What happened?
Thanks, Uğur Böceği.
But I'm curious.
Really... How old are you?
I'm too old to be a high school student.
That's for sure.
Aren't you curious about my age?
Don't worry.
I'll be able to figure that out myself soon.
Where have you been?
You won't believe it, I got mummified.
I hope you weren't one of those trying to sacrifice me to Nefertiti.
Terrible.
What?
You were being sacrificed?
If it weren't for you, I'd never have learned that Uğur Böceği is almost 5000 years old.
That's what friendship is all about.
But I still don't understand.
What was she doing with that 10th grade history book?
Maybe she wanted to learn what happened in the last 50 to 100 years that she missed.
You're probably right.
It must be hard to keep up.
Hey!
Uğur Böceği's book is gone!
You may have escaped this time.
But rest assured, one day, wherever you are, I will get your Miraculous.
You will become nothing.
Nothing.
I don't understand.
I know I'm not 5000 years old.
Then who was that Uğur Böceği on the papyrus?
There have always been kwamis like me and Uğur Böcekleri like you, right?
So that wasn't you on the papyrus either?
What did you think?
You don't look 5000 years old.
I'm not.
I'm even older.
Because I'm the only kwami who has seen every Uğur Böceği since the beginning.
So there have been Uğur Böcekleri even clumsier than me, right?
Every Uğur Böceği was different.
Yes, I'm sure they were.
Marinette, you are different.
But you have an interesting difference.
You're full of surprises and brave.
You're very talented.
You learn quickly.
Really?
Yes.
I think it's okay now.
Don't forget, you have your history exam tomorrow.
Oh, right.