Aslan, today your heart will roar.
Wow, that's right.
By the way, Marinette never falls in love with a statue.
You know I'm not good with girls.
This happened all of a sudden, you know.
Should I go over to my friend and play a prank?
Should I give a compliment?
Should I call you to the zoo?
Should I be serious?
Nino, I think you're overthinking it.
A zoo?
Are you serious?
Ah! Yeah. They say there are some really weird animals.
Listen, just be yourself.
Easy for you to say, Mr. Cover Model of Young Fashion Magazine.
I'm not cool.
You're pretty cool yourself, my friend. Trust me.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be my best friend.
The zoo is nice.
He's definitely coming. Trust me.
What if I act like a goofball around you?
She doesn't want me anyway. If they think I'm a loser, it's fine, I'm here for you.
Yeah, totally. Don't you think so too?
I'm not taking him from there.
Let's go to Germany already.
I agree. Okay.
How smart and handsome he is!
Someone who takes care of themselves and is sweet like candy, you know.
Almost all of them. Oh, sorry about that, right Nino?
Sorry. >> Sorryyy. >> Srry.
Sorry about that. How can we make it up to you?
Got any ideas, Nino?
I'm thinking, should we go to the zoo together?
I heard there's a new guy there, and they say there's a panther too.
Great idea. Isn't it?
You really love it.
Oh yeah, I really love animals.
Oh man, what an idiot.
Oh man, what an animal.
Yeah, I like them.
Great. How about 4 o'clock after school?
Is Nino okay with it?
Great. So, 4:00 then.
At 4 o'clock, at 4:00.
Yeah. >> Oh, the kid you're crazy about just asked you out, if you noticed.
Isn't it?
Yeah. Oh wait.
What? No, not today.
No way today.
I haven't washed my hair yet.
I didn't wear my lucky socks.
Alya, help out. I can't do it alone. Please help me.
So, how'd you pull that off, buddy?
Like I said, you bring this on yourself.
Of course, if I can just be myself.
It hadn't worked before anyway.
You're definitely talking nonsense. Of course you can.
Or when you're all alone at the zoo.
So, that doesn't work when we're alone either, buddy.
You should come too.
You can't leave me alone, though. No problem, Nino.
We're friends after all. Just a little test.
Can you hear me?
I can hear it, but I still don't think I can pull it off.
Of course you can. Just be yourself.
You know what happened last time.
Just be yourself, Marinette.
Hey! What are you up to?
Hey guys, can you come out?
Go outside. Alright, now just be yourself and figure out how to get there.
Where are you? My love.
If you can't even talk to her, how's she supposed to be the love of your life?
Just don't show up in the middle of things.
I'll talk to him, you'll see.
I need to talk to him. Yeah, that's totally right.
This is what motivation looks like. Yep, here they come.
Hey Marinette. >> Oh, wrong alarm.
Hey there, I'm Max.
What are you looking for here?
They said a new panther had arrived. I'll see who has better leg muscles.
Would you have come too?
The target is 10 o'clock to the right.
No, thanks, it's not necessary.
I'm waiting for someone. You guys go ahead.
Alright. Maybe we'll catch up later.
Yeah, see you. >> Where's Adrien? >> Don't know.
Hey Nino.
Isn't Adrien with you?
Well, it'd probably be better if I weren't around.
It's better if it doesn't happen.
This trip is turning out to be more fun than I thought.
Turn up the volume. Otherwise, it just won't work.
We can still hang out even if Adrien isn't around, right?
Sure, we can hang out, you goof.
So, wasn't he coming either?
Can't we just wait for him?
Tell him you want to be alone with him.
Not yet. >> What did you say?
Yeah, you're right.
Let's wait. Hey, why are you talking?
Don't wait for me. I'm not coming.
Look, dad, guess what I brought you.
The best for my baby.
Wow, check out how big that piece of meat he's eating is!
Food that animals who can run faster than 100 kilometers per hour always eat.
So, is it like 100 kilometers or what?
Is that all?
I thought panthers were faster.
I'm sure I can beat him.
Impossible. No one can outrun a panther.
Oh yeah? So, what place did the cat you're talking about get in the state track meet?
I came in first.
You can never compare yourself to a panther, kid.
No need. I'm way better looking than him anyway.
Let's see: if wind blows at 2 meters per second behind you and the sun hits at 45 degrees from the northeast...
I don't think you'd be a rotten egg.
You'd become bait for it.
Your friend is right, kid. Now go on.
He wants to be alone while eating.
Don't make him angry. >> Angry, ma'am? We're talking about a panther, a wild animal.
Get lost, or I'll have you kicked out of the zoo.
Come on, Max. Let's leave this poor kitty with his grumpy keeper.
See, release the animal inside you.
I like that idea.
Fly, my little akuma.
Go and capture the zookeeper. Go on.
I don't think he's willing to come.
Huh, I don't think he's coming.
You think? Repeat what I said.
Yes, he'll come, but first there's something you want to say.
And... yes, he'll come, but first there's something I want to tell you.
I actually love you.
I actually love... not you, someone else, but I can't say it.
Hey! What are you doing?
Oh really? Then let me help you.
Would you? >> Are you going to give expert advice on confessing to someone?
I'm really curious.
What? >> Well, I'm really curious about this lucky girl.
Oh yes. It's you, isn't it? >> That's your friend Alya.
What? >> Alya?
That's great. >> No.
No. That's not great at all.
I can set you up if you want.
What did you say? Are you serious?
You didn't even ask me first.
Uh, Nino is like a brother to me.
No, the discussion is closed.
But if you refuse, he'll be really upset.
Did you say something?
I said it would be really sad if you don't tell him.
Keeper, I am Hawk Moth.
I'll give you power in exchange for a little favor.
Yes, Hawk Moth.
Hey, little one, still up for the race?
Don't stop, I'm giving you a head start.
That's mine.
I absolutely refuse to go out with Nino.
Mind control. Get out of here! What is this?
We'd better go.
Alya, why didn't you listen, Marinette?
Ah, I couldn't help myself.
I didn't want Nino to be sad.
We'll sort that out later.
Now you have to transform.
One catch. There's something we have to do.
Black Claws. You lost, kid.
See that? How do you like the panther?
Is that all you've got?
What do you think about ladybugs, then?
And a black cat.
I think I'm higher up the food chain.
Keeper, take their jewels immediately.
Their Miraculouses, then bring them to me.
If you care about yourself, get out of here now.
Cat Noir. The akuma must be in his cuff.
You hold him.
I'll get the akuma.
Attack. We need to put them all in cages.
Oh, really?
I'm sure they won't resist you while you're doing that.
We'd better split up.
Hey! What's this?
Don't move, nothing will happen.
So? What's the news?
Oh, there are too many of them.
We can't hold them all. >> Then what can we do?
Let's go back to Plan A.
If we destroy his cuff, I can catch the akuma and everything will go back to normal.
Sounds like a good plan.
But this won't break... >> Actually.
He didn't break it either.
Then how did he escape? I don't know, but who do we need to find?
I mean, we need to find that kid.
Aha, there he is. >> Ha.
There are only two of us left, kid.
Soon I'll be alone.
You won't get away this time.
Quick, go into the first building you see and hide.
You can't catch me. >> Now we know how he escaped.
Who's where? It's fine.
Little pest. Help, please help.
Uh, nothing's wrong, kid.
Come here now.
Slow down. >> He's safe inside the building.
Panthers can't open doors or get inside.
Maybe not panthers, but if he transforms into a smaller animal, like a mouse or... >> Right.
But we still have an advantage.
We know exactly where to find his prey.
The keeper will sniff him out very soon.
But in the meantime, we'll have time to make a plan.
We have to stop him before he turns Paris into a forest.
Follow me. >> Hello, ma'am.
B-but you're Ladybug.
Oh yes, I am.
We interrupt our broadcast for a special news report.
Animals are taking over Paris.
Police are trying to get the situation under control.
For your safety, stay home and remain calm.
Mayor Bourgeois will address the public shortly. >> You're safe in here.
Can I have this?
Oh, sure. >> Come on, Cat Noir.
Lock all the windows and doors.
We'll handle the rest.
You won't be in danger. >> Thank you, sir.
Thank you. >> You're welcome.
Ladybug. >> That's it.
Hey, what's this?
Air freshener. With this, he won't be able to smell us.
Thanks. I've always wanted to smell like...
Ocean breeze. >> Can't we trap him somewhere inside?
Only if he turns into something big.
Oh! Oh! Is this cage big enough?
Definitely. But how do we get him inside?
He's coming. >> It's working.
Whose scent is he picking up?
Come with me. >> Ladybug, you thought well.
Couldn't it have been a slower animal?
Where's the button for these doors?
Oh! Of course none of them work.
The keys. Get their Miraculouses.
Face to face. He's getting tired from changing so much.
Then let him get even more tired.
We'll be able to catch his akuma easily.
Cat Noir. This doesn't really count as a cage, but it'll work.
I think he absolutely can't stand listening to this sound.
You're unbearable too.
Now let's wait. Ready for the akuma?
It's working. >> Hey!
Let's see if they count as endangered species.
T-Rex may have gone extinct long ago, but technically it's still an animal.
Looks like there will be two more endangered animals soon.
A cat and a ladybug.
Lucky Charm. A hairdryer?
Unfortunately, the keeper doesn't have a flat tire.
His forearms are so small.
Bet he can't shoot hoops well.
What are you trying to say?
If you climb on top of him, he can't grab and push you, and while you distract him, I'll attack.
Sounds like a good plan.
I'm good at this.
It won't be easy. That was really weird.
We didn't need to use it.
I wonder what that means?
I think because we're a good team, we didn't need it.
Cat Noir, wait.
I figured out what we're going to do.
Ladybug... >> Enjoy your meal.
No, you'll pay for this.
You can't do evil anymore, little akuma.
Give up the evil. That's it.
Goodbye, little butterfly.
Miraculous Ladybug.
Pound it! Ladybug, that was pretty tiring.
Oh no! I have to go right away.
See you later. Cat Noir.
What happened to me?
Everything's fine, but check on the animals at the zoo.
You ruined everything, Ladybug.
It wasn't supposed to end like this.
But I promise you, one day I'll be at the top of the food chain and I'll defeat you.
Oh no, I completely forgot about Alya.
She's going to be so mad at me.
And what if she finds out you locked her in a cage with Nino?
Yeah. I think she might actually kill me.
Getting angry is enough. Hey, listen Alya.
I'm sorry about what happened.
I shouldn't have told Nino you could meet up.
I wasn't thinking, but I'll explain everything to him, I mean it.
Don't worry. I promise.
Do you forgive me?
Ha. >> Thank you, Nino.
Do you want one too, Marinette?
What's this doing here?
Today, Ladybug locked both of us in the same cage.
And apparently we actually have a lot in common.
Marinette, remember that girl I liked?
Oh yes. >> Well, it was actually you.
Huh. >> Or so I thought, but after spending all this time with Alya... >> Okay, we don't need to give all the details, do we?
Oh yes, sorry.
The funny thing is, it was actually Adrien who was coaching Nino from the start.
Huh. Adrien was there?
Yes. Great. Here.
He told me you liked someone.
He has no idea who it is.
I promise, because I don't speak for other people.
But if you want, I can arrange something.
Of course, if I know who it is.
Nino. >> Okay. You didn't hear anything.
You can talk to me if you want, Nino.