Welcome to the finals of our Kids Plus contest
Today, one lucky person will be chosen as the new Kids Plus spokesperson
Mireille! Mireille! Mireille!
Hello
Mireille, Mireille, Aurore
Take it easy, take it easy! We started with 5,000 match races, and with our viewers' help, we've narrowed down the contestants
to these two incredible young women
Yes
And now let's invite our wonderful finalists
On my right, Aurore Beauréal, and on my left, Mireille Caquet
Who will be the lucky winner? Find out now
One for Aurore,
two for Mireille. Make your choice, and don't forget, messages are charged
Come on, Manon, give it back
But I want to be a fashion designer too
Manon, please, it's not finished yet, you'll ruin it
Hmph
Ah, ah
I'll vote for Mireille
She's the best
Hey, that's my phone!
Ah
Why did I agree to do this?
It's not like she even noticed
Don't worry, if you can handle Manon one day,
all the future villains will seem easy
Alya, I've got a big job for you
Guess who's shooting in the park?
Ah, right now?
Adrien, in the park,
right now, as we speak
Oh my gosh
So what do I say to him?
The usual stuff
I, uh...
Stop that
And who's this?
No way, I forgot about that little detail
And who is this?
That's Manon, the daughter of one of my mom's friends
I'm watching her this afternoon
No, I can't go out
Wait, let me guess
one more favor you couldn't say no to
No, I just...
couldn't say no
Look, it's okay, I can handle your little detail
Oh thanks, but I'm responsible for her
Besides, I couldn't ask you to... ooh
She's a total angel
Manon, put it down
Come back!
You're such a pushover, Marinette
I've babysat my siblings many times
That makes me an expert at dealing with angels
Who do you think you are, tell me?
I'm a legendary unicorn, transformed into a fabulous human girl in the Miraculous world
a legendary unicorn
I grant wishes, but only the wishes of well-behaved little ones
No, you don't
Or else?
Okay, we're all going to the park
Yay!
Alright
This is the moment we've been waiting for
Our home viewers have made their decision
And the new Kids Plus weather girl
is Mireille!
She totally beat you, Aurore
Next time
What's wrong?
You just lost half a million votes, that's all
The vibrations are so strong
I can feel sudden anger and sadness
My next victim's moment of weakness
will be an easy target for my akumas
I should have won
Talent, star beauty, I've got everything
But she took everything from me
They took everything from me
They... *sob*
You're absolutely right
You should have won, yes
I should have won
Stormy Weather, I am Hawk Moth
I'm giving you the power to fight them as my weather girl
All you have to do is bring me the Miraculous
Can you do that?
Yes
That's my weather girl
Show the whole world who the best weather girl is
Okay, we're going to go over there very calmly
as if we're just passing by
Then, then we'll watch the shoot
Finally, I'll invite her for juice
Then we'll get married, live happily in a nice house
Two... no, no, three kids and a dog
maybe a cat
Oh, forget the cat, I'm allergic anyway
Let's start by walking past her
Let's see if we can get that juice
Awesome
Super
I want to see hunger in your eyes
Remember, stay calm, stay calm
We couldn't be more obvious
Okay, let's start over
She waved at me when she saw this
Yeah, I saw it too
That's totally normal, we're in the same class
Hmm
I am Stormy Weather
the only weather girl who predicts the weather correctly
And lucky for you, a cold front is coming your way
Now
Get me out of here! Help!
Help!
Bravo, that's it!
Your mom brought the spaghetti, give me that smile
Okay, now no, your mom dropped the spaghetti
And now you have to eat it off the floor
Yes, you're so angry, show me that anger
Marinette, I want a balloon that says "Mireille" on it
Can I have one?
Marinette?
Marinette!
Silence!
Come here, little one, I'll get you that balloon
No, I want to go with Marinette
I'll handle it
I'm her babysitter
What about Adrien?
Mireille?
Mireille? Where is Mireille?
I advise those who voted for Mireille to go inside
Because it's about to get very stormy
Wait a minute
Too late
Let's go back
I want to ride the ant
No, no, not now
I have to get back to Adrien
You promised
You're not going to break your promise, are you?
Oh, please! No puppy dog eyes
You know I can't say no to them, don't you?
Ah!
No, no, no, the kid ate too much spaghetti
We need more energy, more romance
What we need is a girl
I need a model
Who, me?
Yes, to pose with Mr. Adrien
I don't think you want me
I'm having an allergic reaction to this apple
Miss Azami Kiki Marble
don't go anywhere, okay?
They need a model to pose with Adrien
What? Are you serious?
Is that boy your boyfriend?
What? No, I mean yes, no...
Just admit it, what are you waiting for?
What about Manon?
You handle the handsome prince
I'll handle the lady unicorn here
You don't know how to control her anyway
Impossible
My flow is Marinette, for once
Trust me
Yeehaw, unicorns unite
Let's go find ourselves some sad peasant kids and grant their wishes
Yeehaa!
Yeehaaa!
Time to transform
Tikki?
Spots on! Yes!
No
Plagg? Plagg!
I'm not here
I'm sleeping
For your information, I can smell Camembert even in my sleep
That's one of my many talents
Great, but there's no time to talk about cheese
Plagg, claws out!
Why did I leave her with him? I shouldn't have done this
No, Alya's right, she's in good hands, I have to trust her
I'll get you out of there
Oh, let's cut that iced cake
Huh? Ah!
Huh!
Or let's not cut it, we're going to Plan B
Huh! Don't worry, everything will be fine
Where's Marinette?
She hasn't forgotten you, Manon
How do you know Adrien?
Marinette told me
She'll be right back, okay?
Hey, Ice Queen
What's all this about?
Why don't you pick on someone your own temperature?
My name is not Ice Queen, kitty cat
It's Stormy Weather
Listen to me
I'm feeling more generous than usual today
So calm down and let's end this here, okay?
I always thought cats landed on their feet
Thank you, Ladybug, but I've got this
No need for boyish charm, Cat Noir
But you're welcome
We're expecting lightning right now, immediately!
Huh!
You won one cat fight
Cat Noir!
Gotcha!
A little Cat Noir will take her wind away
Ah, kitty cat
You should think before you move
Do you have a plan?
Just follow me
Ah, walk away, you two!
Ah, ah!
Ah!
Get out of the ice, hit once
hit twice, and freeze
Hey, that's not fair, you always win, Unicorn!
What was that?
Uh, we...
The Great Goblin King ate too much and his shirt ripped
Do you want to hear a story?
You showed them who the real winner is, my weather girl
But now it's time to do your part of the deal, and here's my plan
Maybe she has unresolved anger issues
Or maybe she failed her stress test
Hello, viewers
Here's the weather forecast for the first day of summer
Looks like Mother Nature changed her plans
Vacation colors? It's all over now
Already?
But I look great in a swimsuit
Cat suit is enough, thanks
At least we know where to find her
Get ready for the worst weather in history
You'll freeze to death before long
This girl reminds me of someone
It must be in that akuma umbrella
Winter Wonderland is happening in Stormy Weather's world, on the last slide
No way
and it's going according to my plan
Soon the Miraculous will be mine
Bring them to me
Stormy Weather is getting away
Did I hear a damsel in distress?
Some of us don't have night vision
No need to be scared, trust me
Then the one-eyed monster took the princess's hand and
"Look into my eye," he said
Then the princess poked her finger into his eye
As soon as she took a bite of the cursed potato,
the poor princess fell into a deep sleep
That's enough!
I think from now on, I'll...
Take this, so we can follow you
Empty heads!
You finally fell into my trap
It's time, bring me the Miraculous
No way out
Party's over, fools
It's only just...
It's only just beginning, Stormy
Lucky Charm!
A few arms?
What am I supposed to do with this?
Great, we're about to be destroyed, but at least we'll stay dry
Just hold on to your whiskers
What's the plan for catching the akuma?
My arms are getting tired
Huh, did you see that sign over there? Take a look
Okay
Disaster
Hey, Cold Spell, is that all you've got to drive someone crazy?
Get out of here, you evil bug!
No more evil for you, little akuma
Time to de-evilize!
Got it
Goodbye, little butterfly
Miraculous Ladybug!
And after defeating the three-headed dragon in taekwondo,
Yes, the princess kissed the prince and
did they live happily ever after?
Yes, until they had a dozen kids who drove them crazy just like you
What am I even doing here?
Just you wait
One day, the Miraculous will be mine
I don't know how many enemies I have to send to win, but
victory will be mine
Hey, photographer! Adrien is waiting for you
Aren't we too late?
Come on, Marinette, you saved Manon and the whole world
Have some fun
What? Yellow?
Ladybug is your best friend
So now you always know what to do with the other one, you know
Can I be a lollipop?
Please, please, please!
No, Manon
I have important work to do
Alya, you'll watch her, right?
I'm ready for the photo shoot
Wait, who's that?
An angel?
Awesome
Perfect
Fabulous
So beautiful
Perfect photos, yes