How about asking him to a movie?
Yeah, Tikki. Can you even imagine this conversation?
"Hey Adrien, would you like to... um..."
Exactly. I can't help it. Every time I
see him, I can't speak and I feel like
I'm going to faint. So basically, in order to
have a normal conversation with him,
you need to be blindfolded.
Almost. There's a very simple solution,
Marinette. It's called a cell phone.
You just need his number. I know who has
his number.
How much longer
do we have to wait? You've outdone yourself this time. This
is an honor for me. And I can't wait
to meet Ladybug. I want her to sign
the photo that inspired the sculpture.
It's almost time. Ladybug and Cat Noir
should have been here by now. Look, we know
the turtleneck isn't your thing. So just
stick to the script. The teachers say I don't
sound natural when I read. Then memorize
it. It's very simple, you can do this.
Just don't improvise. Understand?
Forget it, this isn't going to work. Too late.
It's ringing. Hello, you've reached Adrien's voicemail.
Leave a message. It went to voicemail.
Leave a message. Don't
improvise. Hello, Adrien's voicemail. Um,
it's Marinette. I have a message for you.
Of course, this is your phone.
Uh, call me. Bye. Goodbye.
What? What did you expect me to say? "Hey, hot
stuff, wanna catch a movie together?" I'd like to ask,
but the only way I can talk to you
without turning into a babbling mess is through
this stupid phone. It's so ridiculous,
isn't it? What do you think? To replay your
message, press 1. To delete it, press
2. Press 2, press
2. Your message has been saved. Goodbye.
It's not as bad as you think. Huh,
okay, it's bad. But you had to tell him one of these days,
one way or another. Think of it this way:
there's no secret now. The voicemail recorded
our entire conversation. What does it matter?
I called him "hot stuff." He can't hear that
message, Alya. If he does, I'll die
of embarrassment. Okay, okay, I have an idea.
If Adrien's phone went to voicemail,
it means the guy is busy. Which means
you can get to the message before
he does. I wonder
where he is. Of course, he has fencing
after school, that's why he didn't answer. It ends
in exactly 22.5 minutes.
You're seriously crazy, you know
that,
right?
You have one new message.
I need to get some water, I'll be right
back. Tikki, seriously? You have one new message.
Step aside so I can check my messages.
Hmm, I don't recognize this number. Oh no,
we're too late! Time to transform!
Plagg. Hello everyone, today they're unveiling the statues
of Ladybug and Cat Noir. I completely
forgot about that. I never mentioned
going to the unveiling before. Yes,
I mean, I'm not going. I mean,
I forgot. Listen, how about we go after this
regarding Adrien's cell phone? If we wait
for the ceremony to end, Adrien's
fencing lesson will be over and he'll have
picked up his phone by then. Oh, come on, I need
to watch this for my Ladybug blog. I'm so
sorry, Marinette. Don't worry, I'll
handle it, I think. Are you sure? Yes, yes,
I'm sure. Good. Good luck, and stay out of
trouble. And don't improvise! Oh, dear.
Doesn't Ladybug need to be at the
unveiling too? Yes, but Marinette needs to go to
school first. But this ceremony is in your
honor, and right now my honor is
at stake. I'll be in and out in 5 minutes,
then we can head straight back to the
ceremony. Excuse me, Cat Noir, but Ladybug
isn't here. Don't worry about Ladybug,
I'm sure she'll be here soon. For now,
I can handle things on my own. Besides,
all I wanted was for her to sign this
photo. She's amazing. Brave and smart,
always saving everyone. Maybe we should
start the ceremony, it might bring her here
faster. Please, just one more minute, Mayor
Bourgeois. She'll come here,
I can feel it. Here, buddy. Which one is
his phone? If you call him, his phone might ring. Good
idea, Tikki.
We must show our respect to those who protect
us. Ladybug and
Cat Noir. Can I get a photo?
They're finishing up now,
here.
The locked statues are great. But something's
not right. I'm actually taller than Ladybug. Ladybug
didn't show up. I just wanted to show
my admiration for her and tell her that everything
I have went into her statue. I'm sure
if she spent a little time getting to know me,
she'd realize how much we have in common.
Our dedication to the things we love.
Look, I don't mean to bother you, but Ladybug
and I are, uh... we're... you know.
Really? Yes,
like
that. What does she see in him?
They're coming! Forget the phone, I haven't been able
to delete the message yet. We're out of time and we
need to get to the ceremony. Hurry
up! Wow, that was tough.
Um... You're not even taking the unveiling seriously.
You know what? You don't deserve her.
He's disappointed by Ladybug and jealous
of Cat Noir. The perfect formula
for disaster.
Fly, my little akuma, and evilize
him. Once you get rid of Cat Noir,
you can take his place and Ladybug will
be yours forever. Just the thought
of it makes me purr.
Where is it? Why are you looking at me? I didn't
take it, I swear.
How do I find the messages
on this thing? This is Adrien's phone.
What if he finds out I stole it? I'll get
arrested and spend the rest of my life
in prison. Worst of all, I'll never go to the movies
with Adrien.
Ugh, Marinette, you really need to get
your priorities straight. I know. Sometimes
balancing being Marinette and being Ladybug
seems impossible.
Hello, this is Adrien's voicemail. Leave
a message. He must still be at
the gym. I believe so, right?
This... I need to document
this right away. Don't mind me, I'm just
stealing this painting. You guys carry
on. I can't believe the
exhibition. Unbelievable.
We're coming to you with breaking news. An incredible
heist has occurred at the museum. This picture
shows that the amateur thief is undoubtedly
none other than the famous hero,
Cat Noir. The cat's
meow. The cat's meow?
This guy isn't just a fake, he's a terrible
fake. I'm out. And now the weather.
Of course Adrien has one of these super expensive
smartphones. I don't even know how to
work this thing. Maybe taking off these
stupid gloves would help. And risk leaving
fingerprints?
Impossible. Is the problem solved? Almost,
I haven't deleted the message yet, but I'm working
on it right now. Oh, come on, you stole
the phone? Yes. No, I mean I was planning
to return it. Actually, where are you? I could
use your help. I can't, Alya. I'm waiting for news on the
Cat Noir heist. What? Someone robbed Cat Noir?
No, girl, haven't you heard? Cat Noir showed up
and stole the Mona Lisa in broad daylight. Ladybug
will be here any minute and I don't want to miss
it. Relax, I'll be there soon,
okay? Cat Noir is many things, but he's
not a thief. Time to
transform! Tikki,
spots on!
Hey, take it easy, tigers. You've got the wrong
cat. That thief is an impostor, the real
cat is
me. Let me look at the scene of the crime. I'm
very good at finding tracks. And you know,
animal instincts. Of course, come with me.
Thanks for your
help. Hey, I'm the real Cat Noir. I'm way
smarter than that guy. Kitten
in a cage. I repeat, kitten
in a cage.
Mr. Mayor, this is ridiculous. I'm sure there's a simple
explanation. Kitten
in a cage. Ladybug can't keep him in there
forever. No, no, leave it to the experts, Ladybug.
We've got
this. Thanks for the warm welcome, but I have
to go. So I'm going to say this one more time:
You've got the
wrong
cat. Cat Noir
is escaping. If he's so innocent, why did he run,
huh? If you were thrown in the wrong
jail, wouldn't you run?
Requesting backup. I repeat, requesting
backup. We are currently in pursuit of the
suspect. Cat Noir, what's going on? You know I'm
innocent, don't you, Bugaboo? Stop playing
games, and don't call me "Bugaboo." This is serious.
I'm going to find the real culprit and save
my tail. I
promise. It's all over. Aren't you going to go
after Cat Noir? Ah, I'll leave it to the experts.
Come on, hurry.
Thank goodness. If you're asking me, I'd say the thief
is under the influence of an akuma. I figured that much
out. Do you see the lollipop stick?
On the statue. I couldn't see this kind of jealousy
from a mile away. Yours or
his? Very funny.
Gotcha.
Cat Noir, where are you? I found your location.
Whose copy? Yours, of course. I don't understand.
If you'd come this morning, you'd understand
what I'm talking about. Well, tell me where
you are. No, this is between me and him.
I got myself into this mess, and now
I'm going to get myself
out of it. Cat Noir, Cat
Noir! Is the cat in the
bag?
Catastrophe! I don't see what Ladybug sees
in you. A fool who easily falls
into traps.
Is this what you're looking for? Which one
should I take? Mine or
mine? Ladybug, hurry up! I've got the impostor
at Theo Barbot's workshop. I'll be there in 30
seconds. Don't come here, Ladybug, it's
a trap. Too late, kitty. Good thing Ladybug
showed up, that was my plan all
along. She'd never fall for that, she knows me too
well. I know you well too, and from now
on, she'll love me, not you. Love?
You're right, she does love me. That's why she'll
be able to figure out your true identity,
Copycat. Enough chat, bring me Cat
Noir's Miraculous!
I can't. There you are.
Cat Noir. He really does look like you. Because
he's my akuma. Where is it? In his ring,
of course. Hold
him. Ladybug is doing the work for us.
What a sweet
irony. He even has the same powers as you,
isn't that incredible? If you don't believe I'm the real
Cat Noir, ask him about our love
for each other. Have I ever lied
to you,
Bugaboo?
Hmm. I hope you didn't tell him
about us. What? That weird... You know, we made
a secret promise.
Oh? Yes, of course. We never made any promise,
Copycat.
I love you, Ladybug. I'm so much better than
this cat. Liars
lose. Cat Noir might get on my nerves,
but he's never lied. Thanks for
the proof. I guess.
Finish him off, take his Miraculous. If I can't
have you, no one will.
Cataclysm! Let's end this. Lucky
Charm! A spoon? What am I supposed to do
with this?
Great job, Bugaboo. Where's the akuma?
In the photo in his pocket. Let's finish
this. You'll detransform before me.
He's pretty
good. You didn't have to come at me, I told you
I'm better than him.
But I'm better than both of you.
Hey, you caught me! He's lying, I'm the real
one.
You're both getting on my nerves now.
Show me your ring! How many
lives do you have left,
Cat Noir? Cataclysm!
With pleasure. I love a good
cat fight.
Time to de-evilize!
No more evil-doing for you, little
akuma! Time to
heal!
Gotcha! Goodbye, little butterfly.
Miraculous
Ladybug! Nice catch. I'm so glad you could tell
the real cat from the fake one.
It wasn't very hard after I figured out
which cat was in love with me.
You might want to help a friend whose love was
unrequited.
Actually, both of us...
What am I doing here? Ladybug, I'm sorry
I couldn't make it this morning. Would you sign
this for me? Of course I'll sign it. There's real
artistry here, you've really captured my
essence. Thank you, Ladybug. And don't worry,
I know about you and Cat Noir, it's
no problem.
Ha!
I couldn't find it. To replay your message,
press 1. To delete it, press 2.
Your message has been deleted. I'm going to tell him
I found his phone. That's a good way to start
a conversation, isn't it? Then I'll invite
him to the movies. That's my
girl.
Maybe you dropped it somewhere. He dropped it,
and whoever found it found it in the boys'
locker room.
That figures. I was checking my messages
earlier. I must have looked here. Let's just
relax and
go. Hey guys, can a few more friends
come? Of
course. Yes!