Your last assignment, what you did, pleased me
very much. Some of you stood out and
I thank you for that. Now
our next assignment: Passing
Time. Marinette, I don't know if you're still
in the bathroom? Teacher, tonight I want all of you
to read the first chapter of this year's
"Breathtaking France" volume. Then answer these simple
questions. Can you make sure Marinette
gets her assignment?
Yeah, this is Marinette. Leave a message,
beep.
Marinette! Alya! Have you seen Marinette
anywhere?
Chloé? Ladybug?
Hey Marinette, call me immediately,
we need to talk. Nino, wait! Yes, come with me,
I need your
help. Okay. This is Marinette. Leave a message,
beep. I hate it when she disappears like that.
She's not calling me. Where is that girl,
really? Our Adrien is the same way, but
I guess that's what happens when your dad is
Mr. Control Freak.
Once again, Ladybug and Cat Noir
saved Paris from the clutches
of a villain. Hey, I think I've figured out
who the real Ladybug
is.
Chloé? Chloé? Are you serious? She's too
self-centered to think of anyone but herself,
let alone save the world.
You've lost your mind, girl. I haven't lost it at all,
you'll see.
Time flies when you're saving the world,
the day is already over. And ask me about it, I missed
half the school day and my chance to see Adrien.
Whoever is behind this is keeping us
on our toes. But you don't have
toes,
Alya. Alya left your school bag. Marinette?
Hello, Mom. You seem very forgetful
lately. You need fresh air and extra exercise
for that growing brain,
sweetie. Good idea, Mom, I'll start
tomorrow. Ladybug once again
saved Paris from destruction, but who will save
Marinette from her homework? What's this? "Call me.
I know who the real Ladybug is."
Impossible. Do you think she knows?
I doubt it. Alya always jumps to conclusions
before learning the facts. But just
in case. Don't worry, Tikki, I've
handled it. Come on! No
signal. Sorry, ma'am, cell tower repair.
There will be no signal in the whole neighborhood
for an hour. Come on, Marinette,
you can try again later. Let's go downstairs
and finish your homework.
Hello? Hello? You look fabulous.
No, not you. Hey, Halloween is still
months away. You need to get examined.
If she's the superhero, then I'm
the Wizard of Oz. I'm telling you, she's
Ladybug. Can you prove it?
What time is it? School started
an hour
ago. Don't forget what you have to
say! She's Ladybug! Look, over there!
Huh? What a ridiculous joke! Adrien, I
mean... Didn't you see Ladybug yesterday?
She's amazing. I wonder who she really is? Did you
DJ until late last night, Nino?
Clearly you didn't get your beauty sleep. You,
my dear Chloé. Alya is looking
in your locker. She's lying. I wasn't
looking at all. Hey, give that back
to me! Let's see who the
liar is. She invaded my privacy,
I have proof. What? Really, all I
did was take a photo. Sorry,
Chloé, but there's no school policy regarding
privacy. Then arrest her for breaking and
entering! I didn't break into her locker,
it was already open. And was anything
stolen? Only my soul was stolen. Principal,
my locker is my secret
garden...
Did my ears deceive me? Did I just hear
you give a serious offender only an hour
of detention? Is that true, Principal? Sabrina,
school rules clearly state that any student
found guilty of theft receives a
one-week suspension. Yes, but she
didn't steal anything. I don't think
my father would share the same opinion,
with you, I mean... Chloé, let's not bother
your father, I mean the Mayor,
with a small locker situation.
If you wish... I mean, you are suspended
for one week, Alya.
What? That's totally unfair! I'm going to protest
this on the school blog! For
one thing, the school blog is shut down, okay? She's
not a superhero, she's a super
psychopath! School life, I don't know, an experiment but
a Petri dish for producing secrets, lies,
and betrayal. Fertile ground
for evil akumas.
Fly, my evil akuma, and possess
her. Marinette... leave a message.
Beep. Lady Wifi. I heard you're looking for a masked
Ladybug. I'd like to help. In return
for your help, I will expose the lies
of everyone who hides the truth.
Deal.
Where is she?
Suspended. What? Marinette, if you're going to be late,
could you please do it quietly?
Excuse me. What happened to her? Long story short,
she was accused of going into Chloé's locker.
Ladybug's
locker? That's enough, Marinette. Straight to
the Principal's
office. What are you talking about? Like I said,
dude, I'm telling you, she's lost
it.
I am Lady Wifi.
Sir, I am Lady Wifi. In my first scandal revealing the truth,
your principal has something
he wants to share with you. Is it true
that you suspended a student named Alya
today even though she was innocent?
Yes, it's true. So you were biased, unjust,
and completely unfair? Yes,
I was. No, Alya. Tikki, time to transform.
Are you going to fight your best friend?
No, I'm going to save my best
friend. Tikki, spots on! Yes!
And in my next exposé, I will introduce
you to the girl behind the Ladybug
mask. Stay tuned, everyone!
For your safety, go home immediately. And don't forget
to read chapters 4 and 5!
Don't let it be like she
said. Also, you have a crush on
Adrien,
huh? Claws out!
What? No way! Who is this Chloé,
Cat Ladybug? Oh, come on, you can't
believe she's the real Ladybug.
Yes, of course she isn't. Besides, who
could believe she's the real Ladybug?
She's obviously just a random
fan, a copycat. I mean, yeah.
Hello? Hello there, Ladybug.
We found the Wifi!
Well... Yes, I guess my suspicions were correct.
Everyone thought the girl behind the Ladybug
costume was a little angel.
Think again! The real
Ladybug turns out to be Chloé Bourgeois.
And who are
you? But I thought you were Ladybug.
Sorry for interrupting your news.
Next time, double-check
your evidence. You'll be
sorry, Alya. Alya's connection
was cut off. I am Lady Wifi. Breaking news: Ladybug!
Let's see who
you are. Follow
me. Alright, she gets her power from her phone. Let's take her
to the ground floor where there's no reception.
No phone, no problem. Good thinking, Ladybug,
we need to go
lower. I've got you
now. Get ready! So, Ladybug,
what do you do when you're not
saving Paris? Can't you see we're
busy right
now? She went back to the hotel. She locked all the doors. Hey! Maybe
we know each other in real life.
I doubt it. Closed. She left this one
open. Prepare for an ambush. On three: one, two,
three! We didn't fall for
the ambush! Follow
me! Where is
she hiding? And what's the deal with these phones?
What is this? I thought you were
after her. You can't
catch me! Yes, I can!
No, no, no! Hold on, Ladybug!
Of course, the service
elevator! Ladybug! Who is she? A superhero
or just super weird? Can we trust a girl
we have absolutely no idea about?
We have a right to
know! Why isn't it working? Because
your magic minutes are up, Lady
Wifi. Aw, how romantic! Kitty came
to save his ladybug. I'm not her
lovebug. We'll get back to that
later. Ah!
My ring! It's so cold in here! Where is she? A little
help could be useful. Yes, yes.
What am I going to do with you? Make her use
her talisman, she'll be forced to turn back
to normal. Then she'll reveal her identity
and her Miraculous will be mine. If you don't
get her out soon, your girlfriend will
freeze soon.
Good luck with your ice cat. I have
other things to
do.
Come on! What's up, people? Everyone listen up!
I'm about to present the award-winning news
you've all been waiting for
right now. I'll get you out of there,
Cat Noir. Don't rush! Don't blink,
now Ladybug will reveal her true
identity to you.
I'm unlucky. If only this was a lucky box. Of course!
Microwaves!
I've got it!
I've got it! Come on, microwave, jam the signal!
Come on! Are you okay,
Cat Noir? You've used your talisman, you don't have
much time left. Exactly. Open the kitchen
door! We can't, the microwave is broken.
Here's what we'll do, listen to me.
Got it. What is she doing? Don't let
the Miraculous escape, no matter what. Yes, I'll go
and destroy her wireless antenna. Good luck!
There you are, Kitty!
My butterfly! Nice try, kitty, but I won't let you
cut me off that
easily. Hurry up, Cat Noir!
No!
Ha! I lost the
signal! Give me that
phone! Ah!
No more evil-doing for you, little
akuma! Time to
de-evilize!
Gotcha! Goodbye, little
butterfly. Miraculous Ladybug!
What? Pound it, Ladybug! Wow! And
Cat Noir, can I have a quick
interview? Wait, let me get
my phone. We have to go. I just have
a minute. No! Where did they go?
I won't tell anyone who you are, Kitty.
No one must know who we are. Not
even us... Ugh, that was really close. And ask me
about it.
What were you thinking during that chance
to find out who the love of your life is?
That's the problem, Plagg,
I wasn't thinking. I was following my heart.
One day your mask will fall, Ladybug,
and then you'll have no choice but
to hand over your precious Miraculous.
Is that true? Will you tell her? Is that
what my heart is saying? Sometimes my heart
says something, but a good superhero always
listens to her head.
I found it!
Want to see? It's way, way better
than my old phone.
Huh? What are you doing with those photos?
I mean, with a mask and a costume... Don't you think
he looks a bit like
Cat Noir? Have you lost your mind? He's way
cuter than Cat Noir! Hey! I think Cat Noir
is pretty awesome. Stop taking pictures
of Adrien! Of course, you're not going to give them
to me, right? Give it to me! No! Come on,
Marinette, what if you drop it? Everyone knows
how clumsy you are.