You only have one day to complete your sewing
assignment, and it must be your own design.
In 10 hours, the person evaluating your presentation
will be the fabulous fashion designer
Gabriel Agreste. As you know, his son
Adrien Agreste is at our school. What's more, Adrien
will wear the winning design in a photoshoot.
And now, I'm announcing this year's theme:
The bowler hat.
A bowler hat? Bowler hat? Bowler hat?
Bowler hat? Bowler hat? I don't have a design!
Top hat, cap, even a horned helmet
I could do. How about a beret? If you ask
me, a sombrero? No problem. But
a bowler? Though wait, it won't matter anyway.
Because I'll probably do something clumsy
during the presentation. I'll probably step on the hat
while walking and fall onto Mr. Agreste.
He'll faint because of me, and Adrien will
be turned off. I'll never become a world-famous
designer. My life is ruined. Over a bowler
hat? Let me see that sketchbook,
I'm sure there's something in there.
Forget it, I'm a total disaster. I'll probably
just ruin everything in the end. Oh, Alya,
what are these? These are amazing designs! I didn't know
you were this talented. Uh, thanks
Adrien, but I think you misunderstood. These
designs belong to Marinette. Incredible, aren't
they? You're so talented, Marinette.
You actually have a high chance of winning. Well, uh...
Yeah, I do a little design work.
Uh, should we
go upstairs? I mean, uh...
Thanks. Sure. And good luck. Maybe in my dad's next
photoshoot, I'll wear your
hat. Girl, could you please calm down
a little? But you heard him, right? He thinks
you could win.
He was so impressed by your design.
Okay, I heard. She's going to win? No way.
Once Adrien sees my design, I'll make sure
his father picks me.
Your design will blow everyone's
minds. Yes, of course. But first I need
to get that sketchbook. Only nine hours
left until the big presentation. No, I'm going
to my garden of inspiration. See you
later. I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm
fine. The time has come to find our next
victim. My little akumas, we are putting
an end to Ladybug and Cat Noir.
Then the Miraculous will be
mine. God, it's so hard to be creative under this pressure.
Marinette, you save the world under pressure.
I think designing a hat is
child's play. Hmm, a toy bowler hat? Both
stylish and fun!
Hello, hello! How lovely you are!
Edgar, you beautiful
thing! Magnificent, superb performance! Get out,
you flying rats! How many times do I have to tell you,
Mr. Ramier? Feeding birds is forbidden,
strictly prohibited by law. Because when someone feeds them,
the place ends up a mess. Should my poor
pigeons go hungry? All the park keepers
know you, Mr. Ramier. You've been expelled
from every park in Paris. Now leave,
or I'll call the police.
Stop! I am the police! Go!
I felt so sorry for that poor man. What
an interesting character, he was like a bird-human.
If he wore a feather jacket, then
he'd be all set. A feather
jacket? Have you thought this through?
Tikki. Poor Mr. Ramier. What a huge
injustice. Such easy prey
for my
akumas. Fly, my
akumas, and evilize
him. Mr. Pigeon, I am Hawk Moth. Neither this police
officer, nor any other park keeper, will ever
separate you from your friends.
There is no Paris without the pigeons.
And there are no pigeons without you.
Yes! Now that's how you make a hat. Thanks,
Tikki. We
are amazing. We are? Of course, sorry, you
are amazing. Chloé, when are we... Shh! When are
you going to do yours? And ruin my nails?
I'd never do it. My daddy will just have
someone make it for me.
With his money.
Ah! What are you looking for now? The feather, I can't find
the right feather for the hat. It absolutely
must be a
feather.
Yes! Excuse me, officer! Sir!
Come on, how slow can you be? Sorry for the delay,
there's a traffic problem.
You'd better get off the bus.
This is so strange.
Pigeons have taken over Paris!
According to officials, does this alarm
signal a major disaster?
Yes, according to incoming reports, someone named
Mr. Pigeon is about to make an
announcement. You poor
Parisians, I apologize if your feathers are ruffled.
But from now on, Paris belongs to the pigeons!
Let's help
Paris. Tikki, spots on!
Yes!
Ha! There we go. This is really weird, this many
birds are too much for me.
Achoo! I'm allergic to feathers. Achoo! Just
great. And don't even
ask. The birds are only part of the problem.
Paris park keepers are disappearing
one by one. What? We need to find
Mr. Pigeon immediately. But where? I don't know
where to find him, but I know exactly where
he will find
us. Act natural, or he'll never come.
What's that supposed to mean? I am natural.
There you are, Ladybug and Cat Noir. Congratulations,
my friends. The era of the pigeon
has begun. The greatest
pigeons... Where is it? I was expecting them
by now.
What is this?
Ha! Shh! Where is that bird man? Mr. Pigeon
must be around here somewhere.
If you want Paris to belong entirely
to the pigeons from now on, get rid
of those two disgusting
creatures. Don't think I heard that, but for a moment
I felt like
birdseed. Any bright ideas, Ladybug?
You're the cat boy, don't you eat these things
for breakfast?
Look how wonderful. I'm so cruel, aren't I?
Good. Now get their Miraculous!
You will give me your Miraculous, or you will
face the wrath of my winged
friends. On the count of three, my dear
pigeons will destroy you. If you want to
save your hides, give me
your Miraculous! One, two... Cat Noir!
The railings! Cataclysm!
Well, well, looks like the pigeon turned into
a chicken. Me? I never run, I'm just
killing two birds with one stone, that's all.
Happy Holidays! We're not done with you yet.
I need to get out of here before my secret
identity is revealed. Of course, we wouldn't want
the cat's mask to slip,
never. Very
funny, Ladybug. Cat Noir, there's big trouble.
If my guests leave Paris, I could suffer
significant losses. We'll chase that Pigeon
back into his hole. Sure, we'll chase him, but
before that, I have something important to do. Something
important? I get it, you can use the Royal Suite.
There's toilet paper inside.
But I guess you'd prefer kitty litter,
right? But I don't need litter, just a little
cheese.
Excuse me! Please, it's an emergency!
How do you like your cheese best?
Soft, unpasteurized, farmhouse cheese,
aged for 2 years. Thank
you. How exhausting though. I'm dead tired,
I can't move a muscle. What do you say?
Are you ready,
my precious? Bon appétit, my friend. Ladybug
needs
help. Great, I can see better from up here.
So strange, the pigeons are all flying
in the same direction.
Then let's follow
them. Ready to go, Ladybug? Come on!
So Mr. Pigeon has been hiding the kidnapped
park keepers here.
The Grand Palais radar is going off. Either
there's a problem with his radar, or Mr.
Pigeon has left the park keepers
unguarded. Let's set the cat on the pigeons.
That was too easy.
I have a
plan. Perfect timing. We're ready to greet them,
aren't we? They're going to fall right
into the trap. I'm so close to getting
your Miraculous,
my friend. I can't wait, my dear
Pigeon. If we can stop him from cooing,
we can grab the akuma
too. Okay. Open the window, I'll
grab him and take him to the roof. You take
the bird call and get it away from him.
Let's do this. The early bird catches the
worm, I guess. We won't surprise the pigeon
that much.
I have something to tell you. Come closer,
closer! I'm honored!
Save us,
Ladybug! Lucky
Charm! Money? What am I supposed to do
with this now?
You can't escape!
But Cat Noir...
The moment!
Pigeons! My bird call!
No! Catch Cat Noir!
Yes! No more evil-doing for you, little
akuma! Let go of the
evil!
Gotcha! Goodbye, little butterfly.
Miraculous
Ladybug! What happened? Where am I? Pound
it! Foolish birds, foolish
Ladybug! I will wipe you all off the face of the
earth!
We don't have much time. Less than an hour
left.
Where is that girl? Hello, Mr. Damocles, I'm Mr.
Agreste's chief assistant, Nathalie. Hello,
ma'am. Excuse me, but where is Mr.
Agreste?
I'm right here. Hello Mr. Agreste, welcome to our
school. Yes. Nathalie, proceed.
Ah, look, here comes Mr. Agreste this way.
As you can see, Mr. Agreste, our students have
poured their heart and soul into this project.
Where have you been? Is your hat ready?
Yes,
it's right here. What? But this is exactly like Chloé's! What is this?
Ah! Hello Mr. Agreste, I'm Chloé Bourgeois.
You know my father, André Bourgeois, the
Mayor. You dirty little thief!
Want me to handle this? I think I
can handle it. Turn the tablet towards
Ms. Marinette's
hat. Is this a joke? Unbelievable, Marinette
stole my design! This is a scandal!
How could
you? I apologize for this issue, Mr.
Agreste, but I can prove that the design
of this hat belongs to
me. I'm waiting. Ah, everything on
my hat is handmade,
down to the stitching on the brim, it's all
mine, I sewed it myself. Furthermore, it has
a secret element that only the real
designer would
know: It bears my
signature. Daddykins! An impressive design.
You have the skillful hands of a true
hat designer, Ms.
Marinette. Thank you for the presentation.
Ms. Marinette, you are the winner. Thank you,
thank you, thank you!
Adrien will be wearing
your hat in the next ad campaign.
Great job,
Marinette.
Achoo! Excuse me, I'm allergic to feathers.
Achoo! Ah, bless
you! Achoo!
Thank you.