Help!
Super Nathan, you're my hero!
It was nothing.
I love you!
I love you too, Marinette.
Nathaniel!
Why are you drawing like that?
Well, I mean...
It's because of these art works you're left out of art, kid.
I'm sorry.
You're going to go to the manager's room and show these chicken drawings.
Then you're really, really going to be sorry.
Look, Sabine, he's the superhero.
And look who's saving Marinette.
Obviously, Marinette has eyes on you.
Give it to me!
Enough! Nathaniel, get out!
The artists are so emotional.
I may have fallen in love.
Shoot him, my little acumen.
Take that devil out of our way.
Are you tired of being crushed by the creator's soul?
He's drawing the devil.
I'm your friend and I love art.
I'm here to support you.
But I can't give you such a power for free.
There are two subjects you have to bring.
Tell me what you want.
The next piece of physics presentation group is Nino, Adrian and Alya.
You're so lucky.
Then Sabrina, Chloe and Marinette.
Teacher, can't you add her to another group?
Sabrina and I work better together.
They call this a group presentation, not a double presentation.
Take care of it.
I hate taking care of it.
You don't want to change the group, right?
I'm sorry to deal with that two-headed trouble.
But I promise to talk about you between the piece and physics.
You're great!
Forget it, Sabrina.
I don't have time for a stupid presentation.
Besides, there's Marinette to help you.
Okay, no problem, Chloe.
We'll do it, don't worry.
Is everything okay?
There's nothing, Marinette.
Then why don't you help us in the project?
It's none of your business.
Actually, I'm a part of this group.
It's not a problem, Marinette.
You and I will do the research and write for our project.
And Chloe can present it.
It's all equal.
It's not equal at all.
Is this how you two work?
Yes.
We've been doing this since primary school.
Then I started doing Chloe's homework.
And we've been good friends since then.
Is this a problem for you?
Come on, Sabrina.
Sabrina, Chloe definitely benefits from you.
You don't have to do what she says.
A real close friend doesn't act like this.
I'm not just Sabrina's best friend.
I'm her only friend at the same time.
So it would be good if she did what I said.
Because there's nothing without me.
It's better than being your best friend.
Anyway, there are other things I have to worry about.
She promised to do Jean-Claude's magic in the bathroom.
See you later.
Marinette!
I can't believe Chloe can do this.
This was unbelievable.
Yes.
Friends, what is it for?
You're my friend.
And I'm so excited because I'm going to hang out with you and help the project.
We'll have a great time together.
Then we'll do the presentation and we'll tell the truth about Mrs. Mendeley and Chloe.
What do you think?
Great!
Good luck!
See you at the library, buddy.
What do you mean I can't do your homework, Sabrina?
Marinette is right.
I'm not your slave.
I didn't say that.
But Marinette didn't buy a nice hat from Gabriel.
I bought it.
And maybe I can give it to you as a reward.
I'm sorry, but are you trying to make your friend stay by giving him a bribe?
With a hat.
This is a very very very cute hat.
It would look great on me.
I'm sorry, but you were trying to steal my paid friend from me a little while ago.
Or am I wrong?
My hair!
Please, please help me!
Black Fingers!
No! My hair won't do!
It's time to go back!
Pinky, help me!
No! Stop! Stop!
Run and hide!
I feel like you're being hugged by a hot breeze.
Less hair, more movement!
This guy looks like he has a lot of lines.
Where did he go?
I don't know, but he knows how to make a good mark.
This evil drawing especially targets you, Chloe.
Do you know why?
No, everyone likes me, of course.
Yes, because you're so cute.
Yes!
He said that I was cute.
We definitely need to take a picture together.
This wasn't nice at all.
Of course I look good, but you didn't smile.
Let's take another one.
I'm sorry, I'm not very photogenic.
Someone has a crush on you.
Yes, great!
So what's the matter?
Why are you acting so strange?
You have to admit that this girl has a crush on you.
Really?
I opened it. Let's go.
Are you kidding me?
What if the evil drawing attacks again?
Okay, you stay. See you later.
What do you mean, see you later?
You're the one who wants to protect it.
So you don't need me.
So, see you later.
Give me a message, will you?
Oh! Hey!
I'm so sorry, Tiki.
Chloe is burning my anger.
Calm down, Marinette.
Anger has no use to anyone.
It's hard to stay calm.
Especially at school.
Oh my God! Calm down!
Project!
Uh-oh!
It looks like a new buddy.
It's you in the library.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
Okay.
But why did you attack Chloe?
Because Chloe is ruthless and selfish.
I have nothing to say.
So, will you hurt me?
You? You're Marinette.
You're beautiful and sweet.
And you're perfect. I'll never hurt you.
Wow, that's so nice of you.
I mean, thank you.
You're so kind.
I came to ask you something.
Today is my birthday.
Would you like to come to my party?
Actually, this is not a good time.
I have a presentation to work on.
And I have to call a friend and meet him.
And also...
Please, Marinette.
It's just you and me.
Oh my God, this is...
This is mine.
Do you like it?
I love it so much.
I'll definitely come to your party.
But only on one condition.
Whatever you want, Marinette.
You can't hurt Chloe anymore.
I can't stand violence.
For you, only for you.
Let's meet on the left side of Notur.
In the sunset.
Come on.
What do you think, Marinette?
Poor Netanyahu likes me.
And the secret man will be caught by the devil, Uğur Böce.
Yes, but if you meet him as Marinette...
How can Uğur Böce stop this man later?
I think the black cat has to come to the party too.
Sabrin is acting very selfish by making me do this project.
My brain hurts.
Black cat, are you okay with a piece of physics?
I bought a piece of physics bag for this cat.
Great.
Sit down, kitty.
Yes.
Now do something perfect for my presentation.
What did I do? Did you see?
I made a cat joke.
I can be funny sometimes.
Yes, very funny.
You can't fly from here and then call the cat.
Uğur Böce.
I'm sorry, it wasn't nice at all.
But you can leave Chloe.
You have to protect this girl instead of her.
Her name is Marinette.
It's really cute, isn't it?
The devil falls in love with her.
And he promised Chloe not to hurt her when she comes to Marinette's birthday party.
I want you to catch him while he's distracted.
What about you?
I'm going on a very special and important mission.
I'll see you later.
Can you handle this?
Please, this is very easy.
You're not in danger anymore, so see you.
See you?
What about my presentation?
Sabrina, you scared me.
I'm so sorry.
I was just waiting for you.
Did you get my messages?
Yes, I did.
And I was definitely going to call you.
Were you going to call me?
I knew you were going to call me.
That's why I did the geography mission.
Wow, you didn't have to do this.
Since you're my new friend, I can do this at least.
Thank you, but I can't get this.
Really?
Okay, but only once.
Great.
Do you want to work on your physics project tonight?
I'm so sorry, Sabrina.
There's something very important I need to do, okay?
Something very important?
Really?
That's great.
Do you know who else uses this excuse?
No.
I've started to realize how similar you are.
I'm sure you're waiting for me to do all the work like him.
No, I'm not waiting, really.
I just...
I can't believe I did your geography mission.
Hi.
I thought I had to save you from that girl.
Hey, I didn't even introduce myself.
I'm the black cat.
Yes, I know.
You always save the day.
I'm Marinette.
What are you doing here?
It's a bad news.
But don't worry.
You'll be safe with me.
That relieved me.
But I need some help.
Would you like to help a superhero?
What about the owl?
Weren't you two together?
He has something to do tonight.
So you're my owl tonight.
Me and the black cat?
Are we going to fight a crime?
Unbelievable.
So what am I going to do?
Just get that pen away from him, little lady.
I'll take care of the rest.
You have a nice stage.
But I don't want you to get distracted.
I want Marinette to love me.
And I want the magic.
Take it or not.
Okay, I'll take it.
Happy birthday.
Marinette.
Thanks for accepting my invitation.
Wow, this is beautiful.
Do you like it?
Wait, I'm just getting started.
Come on, this has to be a joke.
Huh?
Sorry, I didn't want to scare you.
I just can't draw properly in the dark.
Hmm.
Voila!
Huh?
You're so talented.
I don't understand why you use your power to harm people.
Not everyone.
Only Chloe.
And I'm not going to do this again.
You finally kept your word.
I'm going to keep my word, too.
I'm actually drawing a little bit.
I'm not as good as you, of course.
I'm sure you're a great artist.
Can I draw something special for your birthday, please?
That would be great.
Marinette, give me my pen back.
I need to draw something.
Now.
No, this will stay with me.
Black cat, now!
Marinette, did you become one with him?
You deceived me.
I thought you liked me.
But you're just like Chloe.
You're messing with me.
Come on, are you serious?
Why is everyone comparing me to Chloe tonight?
And I'm taking my word back.
Chloe will have a lesson she'll never forget.
We're stuck.
Really.
Black cat, put your stick like this.
Then stretch it out, okay?
Good idea.
Yeah, I'm good.
I have to go.
Superhero never ends.
Women in need of help.
Waiting girls.
There are many people to save.
You can thank me later.
Am I going to thank you?
He should thank me.
If I hadn't told him how to do his job,
we would still be there.
While the word is out.
We have to help to save Chloe.
I'm so sorry, teacher.
I couldn't work on my project
after what happened in the library.
It was so traumatic.
Think about what you did to my hair.
Come on.
Who would believe that an idiot
can never make me look ugly
with even a hair dryer?
Black cat, is that you?
Chloe.
Where are you?
Are you hiding?
This is so cute.
You're playing hide and seek.
In the closet?
I won, Chloe.
I found you.
My Schnell dresses.
My bling bling shoes.
You're a monster.
You like to mess with people.
But when someone else messes with you,
you don't like it.
Don't you, Chloe?
Don't you?
Your shoe is broken.
Watch your wrists.
Wow.
Look what your cat brought.
Black cat can't take me anywhere.
I came on my own.
What was this secret mission?
If I told you,
it wouldn't be a secret.
In comic books,
this is called the last fight.
The thing is,
if you knew it,
you wouldn't waste a drop of blood
to save it.
That's the worst part.
That's not true.
Everyone loves me.
Watch out.
Oh, light.
Black cat.
It can't draw in the dark.
I got it.
Cat's Claw.
Take it, cat.
Play with the flang.
Hey.
Jumping ball?
Try to stop me with it,
little lady.
[laughs]
Nice to meet you.
Oh, hurry up.
[speaking Turkish]
Where am I?
- Let's check it out. - Let's check it out.
No!
That miracle was mine.
And it was going to happen.
When I get them all, I'm going to rule the world.
Finally.
What happened when the owl and the black cat came to the scene?
Well, to be honest, they did worse.
They just got lost and started to break everything.
They threw plastic balls in my room.
Plastic balls?
I hope you had a good time doing that important thing last night.
I'm so sorry, Sabrina.
We can meet at the library today and work on the project.
- What do you say? - It's too late.
Chloe and I will do the project together.
- So, are you going to do the project? - Of course.
I mean, after all the things we've been through.
This is a nice hat.
I know, right? Chloe gave it to me.
He's my real buddy.
Chloe, your geography homework is ready.
Hello.
I heard your adventure with the black cat yesterday.
Were you scared?
Me? Scared?
It was like a dream.
I mean, you're a dream.
I mean, I wanted to say you could see in your dream.
Oh, this must be a nightmare.
Okay.
So, what do you think about the black cat?
Isn't she great?
I mean, of course.
Yes, but she's not as great as you.
Who could it be anyway?
You're the best, right?
So, is this yes?
You just realized how great Adriana is, right?
It touched my shoulder.
I'm never going to wash this jacket again.
Honey, I think you should control your emotions better.