Don't tell me you're back to spying on Adrian.
You two are together now.
I'm not spying on him, I'm spying on the girl he's running with.
Sublime?
Yeah, I want to know more about her.
Why don't you just ask Adrian?
Already did.
And?
And nothing.
What do you mean, nothing?
I said, surely you two tell things to each other when you're running together every
morning.
You're practically holding hands.
And what did he say?
Nothing.
They run, but they don't say anything to each other.
Not a word.
But it's impossible to be silent next to someone for that long.
They must be hiding something.
There, there!
Oh!
She said something!
Oh, wait!
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
She just sneezed.
Could it be that you're a little jealous?
Me?
Jealous?
Ha!
No way.
See?
Since Sublime is now friends with Adrian, I should become friends with Sublime.
Are you following?
It just makes sense!
The friends of my boyfriend, who aren't yet my friends, are my future friends.
Meaning, I can't get this wrong, except the target isn't just anyone.
Sublime Barlet was born in Belgium, according to the website of the city Mucron, where she
grew up.
She was, and I quote, "the pride of the city."
And for good reasons.
She won the first prize at the conservatoire.
She plays the harp and the flute.
She speaks five languages.
Her parents settled in Paris after their divorce.
And even though she hasn't been in Paris for long, Sublime has already joined several
associations and clubs.
She also won gold in the para-athletics 100 and 400 meter, and is currently training for
the upcoming world championship by running every day, every morning with Adrian, supposedly
without speaking.
I'll never measure up to a girl like that, Alia!
I'll never be as Sublime as she is!
You're putting too much pressure on yourself, girl.
If you want to get to know her, just go talk to her.
Too risky.
You have one chance to make a good first impression.
Okay, so what are you going to do?
I'm going to show her that I can measure up, because that's what it means to be a friend.
It's showing that you're here, always, and that you're resourceful in any and all situations.
Okay, well, my dear resourceful friend, I'll leave you to your mess-making, and we'll catch
up later.
Hey, wait, Alia, aren't you going to stop her from making a mess of things?
You know Marinette.
Once she's made up her mind, it's hard to convince her that she's wrong.
Besides, mistakes are just learning opportunities.
And Marinette loves to learn.
Still, keep an eye on it, Tiki.
In the daytime, I'm Marinette, just a normal girl, with a normal life.
But there's something about me that no one knows yet, because I've got a secret.
Miraculous, simply the best, after the death when things go wrong.
Miraculous, the lucky ends, the powers are always so strong.
Miraculous, Miraculous.
Marinette, are you sure this is the best way to become friends with Sublime?
Of course, Tiki, everyone loves having a friend unexpectedly show up to help.
Now's my chance!
You ate it all up, my little baby birds.
This is a chance I can't miss.
I know where to get chopsticks.
Friends, I know how stressful city life can be.
Which is why I'll play a little harp piece for you all.
I just need a little luck.
Like, if one of her harp strings could break, then I'd find a replacement for it.
It would be so moved, it would signal the beginning of our friendship and-
I'm sorry, major string emergency.
I'll be waiting for you by the entrance.
I'm so proud of you, sweetie.
Okay, dad, I'll see you soon.
The trial is starting earlier.
Would you mind picking up my homework assignments for me?
Not at all.
Don't turn around.
There's a girl with ponytails behind you, hiding behind a plant.
Could she be your girlfriend by any chance?
Yeah, that description sounds fitting.
He's talking to her, she's talking to him, which means they're talking!
Could Adrian have lied to me?
Maybe it's because they're in the same class!
Ancient Greek class!
Oh no!
They're gonna speak in code so that no one can understand them!
Do you know why your girlfriend has been following me around all morning?
Oh, don't worry about that.
I think she just wants to be friends and get to know you, but it's not always that easy
for her.
How unique!
That's Marinette for you.
How about arranging something for the three of us to meet?
That's a great idea.
I'll go ask her.
Great.
I have to go.
See you tomorrow.
Good luck with the trial.
Thank you!
I've been caught!
Oh no!
She's only following her!
Now she's furious and decided to stop being friends with Adrian and to leave the school!
Are you really sure about any of this, Marinette?
Yes.
But I'm going to fix my mistake!
Because if Sublime is no longer friends with Adrian because of me, then Adrian won't love
me anymore!
This will be the end of our relationship and the end of everything!
Sublime!
Forgive me!
I've been the worst friend ever!
Adrian let her manage on her own!
What?
I'm just giving her a little help, that's all.
If you really want what's good for her, then stop helping her every time she's faced with
a challenge.
Or she'll never learn to get by on her own.
She's been in there for at least twenty minutes, hasn't she?
Maybe she's encountered a problem?
Yes, yes!
She probably needs help from a friend!
I'm going in!
Wait, Marinette!
What is it?
We don't even know why we're here!
I was right from the beginning.
I'll talk to her.
Hi, Tiki!
Where did she go?
If you agree to sponsor my daughter, you won't be disappointed, Mr. Roth.
What's your daughter's marketing strength?
She's the fastest runner.
Look, Sublime won gold in one hundred and four hundred meter at the Regional Parathletics.
Gold?
Yeah, right.
More like junk.
It's symbolic!
Symbolic?
Ha!
Symbolic money is worth nothing.
I told you, Caroline, finding a sponsor isn't easy, but it's okay.
Sublime has time.
She's young.
Mr. Roth, wait!
At the World Championship, it'll be a real gold medal, one hundred percent pure gold!
Ah!
This changes everything!
In that case, if I do sponsor her and she wins, I keep the medal.
Consider this an advance payment.
I don't like the way he operates.
Without a sponsor, Sublime won't be allowed to enter the World Championship.
Is that what you want for your daughter?
For her to fail again and again like her father?
We accept your offer, Mr. Roth.
Easy, easy.
I'm not offering anything yet.
I want to see what your daughter's worth on the track first.
Ha!
Anaconda has villain disintegrated Sublime, leaving only her prostheses behind!
Tiki!
Marinette, maybe there's a more logical explanation.
Marinette!
Surely you're not going to disturb her right now?
You're right.
Yes.
I'll wait.
Huh?
I know you're in here.
I know you're hiding, lurking in the shadows, ready to leap out and stop me from winning.
But I won't let you!
When you come, I will be ready, and I will overcome you.
No one can stop me from getting what I want, especially not you!
She hates me because she can't have what she wants.
What does it mean?
She's in love with Adrian!
My water bottle!
She's coming back to overcome me!
I'm Soapinator, and not at all, Marinette Dupain-Chang!
I hate dirt and clean everything in my path!
Listen Marinette, or Soapinator, I'll happily have a chat with you after my trial, okay?
I really don't have time now.
So wait for me here.
Do not move, and do not follow me.
I no longer have a choice.
Tiki!
Wait, what are you going to do?
I can feel that she didn't fall for my costume, but if I become Ladybug, she'll be convinced
that I was akumatized for real!
Marinette, this is a-
Hold tight sweetheart, I have to do a final adjustment on your right prosthesis.
If you find it too difficult you have the right to give up.
You know I'll always love you.
It's okay to be afraid, and it's okay not to succeed all the time.
Thanks, Dad.
Don't listen to your loser of a father.
I know it's in here, fear is always ready to leap out and stop you from winning, but
you're ready.
You just need to overcome that fear and turn it into a strength that will make you soar.
Remember, no one can stop you from getting what you want.
You're my champion, you're sublime.
On your mark, get set, go!
Where is the akumatized villain?
Where is Sofina?
Don't go Mr. Roth!
Everything's okay, Ladybug.
It's just Marinette Dupain-Cheng.
Marinette Dupain-Cheng?
Yeah, she's a girl from my school.
She pretended to be akumatized and disguised herself as soap, bucket eater, or something.
My friend Adrienne explained that whenever she likes someone, she starts to act peculiar,
which means she likes me I guess.
So there's no danger, I'm not hurt.
Everything is... fine.
This is a disaster, we've just lost months of work.
We've done it once, we'll do it again, Dad.
Give her another chance, this is just a setback!
Precisely, time is money, and a setback is not money in my wallet!
Hello ma'am.
Forgive my intrusion, but I seem to sense a considerable frustration.
People are letting you down, aren't they?
They're not up to your expectations.
I can't be as sublime as my daughter.
You're right.
The world would be sublime if people could be better versions of themselves.
Like your daughter?
I'd give you the power to make everything better, you know.
Only if you agree, of course.
That'd be the best thing that could happen to me.
And what should I call you?
Sublimation!
I know why you're hiding, but I'm going to help you surpass your fear so you can carry
on with your mission.
Be better!
Yeah, let's resume the race.
Let's go on to the trial.
Well, now someone actually has been akumatized.
Don't worry, I'll protect you.
How dare you pretend you're protecting my daughter when you've destroyed her trial!
Kabaline!
Think you could look at me, sweetheart?
Thanks to sublimation, Ladybug is finally about to become a better superhero!
I'm sincerely sorry.
I'm sorry.
It was unfortunate misunderstanding, but please reject the akuma, and I promise I'll
fix everything.
If you're really as perfect as you pretend to be, why are you so afraid of being sublime?
I don't trust people under the influence of the butterfly morass I told her.
You're wasting my time, Ladybug!
Maybe you don't want to be sublime, but at least fix the problems you have caused!
Can't you see you're scaring everyone?
My dear ex-husband, thanks to me you're finally about to turn into a much better version of
yourself!
Be better!
I know you're strong, and you don't need mine or anyone's help.
You can do this, sweetie.
Now you're talking!
Now all we need is a sponsor for things to be absolutely sublime!
You're not leaving until you've acknowledged my daughter's talent!
Too late!
I already told you!
Time is...
Have you ever heard of generosity, Bob?
Hey!
I will not be insulted!
Ladybug!
You again!
Have you figured out how to fix my daughter's prosthesis that you broke?
No, but I...
I'm sorry.
It was a mistake.
You're keeping my daughter from securing a sponsor, Ladybug!
Is this what superheroes do in Paris?
Your daughter's sublime, someone.
She thanks you, sir.
Come on, it's snack time!
No, it's time to help Ladybug.
And close out!
Drive!
You are not running away.
I'm firing you!
Cat Noir, you too want to stop me from making people better?
What are you talking about?
Supplimation makes people better simply by touching them!
Are you sure she's really a supervillain?
Well, she hasn't destroyed anything so far.
And to be honest, you can't be mad at her for trying to make Bob a better person, right,
Bob?
Your job is to protect the wealthy Parisians like myself.
That's what you pay for!
No, we're being paid, Ladybug!
No, we're not.
We protect everyone!
Then you're being exploited!
No, we're volunteers, Bob!
How ridiculous.
Hide him somewhere, Supplimation won't find him!
You've got it!
Why'd you put me in here?
Maybe it's 'cause your attitude stinks.
Ladybug and Cat Noir can't bear it when someone's better than them.
They're not worthy of their miraculous.
You should seize them.
What do you say?
Supplime idea!
Now it's you against us!
You should be ashamed of protecting a scoundrel like Bob Roth!
I have no right to decipher others' hell!
They should behave!
You're jealous of my power because I can actually turn villains into good people!
Lucky Charm!
You're not worthy of their miraculous.
You should seize them.
What do you say?
Supplimation!
You're not worthy of their miraculous.
You should seize them.
What do you say?
Supplimation!
You're not worthy of their miraculous.
You should seize them.
What do you say?
Supplimation!
You should seize them.
What do you say?
Supplimation!
You should seize them.
What are we going to do about this, lady?
I...
I don't know.
Your power is just like you, Ladybug!
Useless!
Don't listen to her.
She's wrong.
No, I'm not.
Unless her power is to shatter people's dreams like she did my daughter's!
What's she talking about, lady?
It was an accident.
You must be a better version of yourself, Ladybug.
Don't you want to know?
Everyone's allowed to make mistakes.
And honestly, I don't see how there could be a better version of you.
You're not worthy of their miraculous.
You should seize them.
What do you say?
Supplimation!
You're not worthy of their miraculous.
You should seize them.
What do you say?
Supplimation!
You're not worthy of their miraculous.
You should seize them.
And honestly, I don't see how there could be a better version of you, Milady.
Do you really mean it, Cat Noir?
I never lie.
She's powerless against you.
Milady, what are you...?
You're becoming reasonable, Ladybug!
Be better!
You are now sublimed!
Don't forget about their miraculous!
You're not worthy of their miraculous.
You should seize them.
Don't forget about their miraculous!
Wow!
I told you, Milady!
You too are the best version of yourself, Kitty Cat.
I know.
And the most modest.
It's not over!
I lost my powers!
What are these?
Anti-Kuma!
No!
No more evil doing for you, Ultra-Kuma.
Gotcha!
Bye-bye, little butterfly.
What happened?
And now you toss the Lucky Charm into the air and repair the damages caused by the akumatized
villain.
But sublimation hasn't caused any damage.
She was indeed akumatized, but she wasn't the villain the Lucky Charm was pointing at.
It was me, from the very beginning.
I sincerely apologize, sublime.
If I hadn't shown up, you would have finished your race.
Your prostheses would still be intact and your mom would never have been akumatized.
Miraculous Ladybug!
I hope you'll find the best sponsor there is.
Pound it!
Good luck on your trial!
Wow!
Best performance of the year!
Congrats!
Your daughter is going to make me a lot of money.
However, you'll have to figure out a way to add shoes to these or we won't have any sneakers
to sell.
You can't wear shoes with the blades.
Figure it out, then!
Dad, Mom, it's okay.
There must be other sponsors.
Our daughter is right.
We want a relationship with a sponsor based on respect.
Well said, Severin.
Then good luck finding respect and money.
I myself have never come across them together.
I'm sorry, sublime.
I should have just come talk to you, but I was afraid I wasn't good enough.
I hope you'll forgive me.
Apology accepted.
I know what it's like to put pressure on yourself.
Is it true you want to be my friend?
How did you know?
Adrian told me.
Then you two talk while you're running?
Not while we're running.
It impacts the breathing.
But outside of that, of course Adrian and I talk.
You must think I'm ridiculous.
Hardly.
But if we're going to be friends, we'll need to get to know each other.
We'll talk about whatever you want.
But just promise me not to pull my leg.
It's a joke, Marinette.
You can laugh.
It's all good.
Thanks again, Mrs. Tsurugi.
We couldn't have hoped for a better sponsor than you for our sublime.
Don't thank me.
I know what it's like to live with a disability.
Sometimes technology can help us work wonders.
[MUSIC PLAYING]