- Thank you.
- Hi, Jaleel.
Uh, you don't look too good.
- Tomorrow is Alex's birthday.
- Who's Alex?
- A friend of ours, Angelio's younger sister.
- Ladybug chose her to be the holder
of the rabbit miraculous.
- The one that allows you to travel through time
and change the course of history.
By keeping Ladybug from existing, for example.
- That's why you never met Alex.
Her mission is to keep the miraculous safe
out of the new hawknot's reach.
- Until Ladybug and Cat Noir defeat them.
- Which also means if they don't win,
Alex will never come back.
That's horrible.
- They will defeat them.
- Alex will come back.
- I miss her so much.
I can't even wish her a happy birthday.
It's so unfair.
- You're right, that's not fair.
But there must be a way to wish her happy birthday somehow.
We'll figure it out.
- I miss you too, gang.
(beeping)
- Bunnix, I need you.
- Huh?
- In the daytime, I'm Marinette.
Just a normal girl with a normal life.
But there's something about me that no one knows yet.
'Cause I've got a secret.
♪ Miraculous, simply the best ♪
♪ Act on the best when things go wrong ♪
♪ Miraculous, the luckiest ♪
♪ The power of double ways so strong ♪
♪ Miraculous, Miraculous, Miraculous ♪
- We'll post the video on the Zoo Rabbit Forum.
Once it's online, she'll be able to watch it from wherever.
- And whenever.
- Excellent idea, I'm sure Alex will be very moved.
- We're good to go.
- Are you ready, Mr. Coup-D'Al?
Then, action.
(trumpets blaring)
- Hear ye, hear ye, Mr. Coup-D'Al.
- Mr. D'Argencourt.
- Since you have failed to respond to my many missives,
I have no choice but to express my grievances
to you in person.
Out of respect for monarchy and for the Louvre,
the glorious edifice once the home of kings,
I, Armand Louis Charles d'Argencourt,
Count of Caducy and Pedocasque,
hereby demand firstly the dismantling
of the vile glass pyramid that defiles the main courtyard.
- Not now, D'Argencourt.
I'm busy with these young people.
Please come back another time.
- You have not heard the last of me.
Believe me.
(dramatic music)
- My apologies, I'm ready now.
- Then, action.
- Happy birthday, my darling daughter.
You might not be here physically with us today,
but you are in our thoughts.
- We love you.
- We love you! - We love you!
- Happy birthday, little sis.
I, uh, I, ahem, I miss you.
- Happy birthday, Alex!
- Why such a long face, Marinette?
- Because Alex is gonna end up watching it alone.
That's just too sad, and it's all my fault.
If I'd gotten the butterfly miraculous back,
she could have returned to her life here with us,
and all I can come up with for her birthday is a video.
- I'm sure you'll come up with a perfect gift eventually.
- I need a genius idea like now.
Genius idea delivery!
Am I at the right address?
- Huh, but you're Bunnybug, AKA you,
with the added rabbit miraculous.
I figured out a way to celebrate Alex's birthday
with Alex, interested?
- Really?
That'd be amazing!
Alex would be so happy to see everyone again,
even if it's just for a day.
I know we'd come up with a better idea.
First, you're gonna ask Alia to throw a big picnic.
Then you'll call on Alex and ask her
to give you the rabbit miraculous,
and I'll keep it here in the burrow in complete safety.
- Well, Alex enjoys her birthday with everyone.
- Of course.
Great idea, Bunnybug.
It's kind of your idea too, you know?
- Found it!
- Alia, I got a better idea than the video.
I mean, I gave myself a better idea.
I mean, well, anyway, you get everyone to meet up
at the Place de Vosge Square for a picnic.
I'll take care of the rest.
- Don't you think it's a bit risky
to use the rabbit miraculous just for this?
Playing with time is never a good idea, you know?
- No one's playing with time.
I'll just watch Alex's stuff while she goes partying.
Everything will be fine.
- Tiki spots on!
- Hi, Ladybug.
- Bunnix, I need you.
- What's wrong?
Is the universe in danger?
- Uh, not exactly.
Happy birthday!
- Is this why you called me?
- You don't like people wishing you a happy birthday?
- Uh, yeah, I do, but--
- Then you're gonna like this.
- What?
- There's a surprise waiting for you at the Place de Vosge
Square! - But I can't go.
The rabbit miraculous must be kept safe here in the borough.
- I know, and that's why you're gonna give it to me,
and I'll stay here to keep it safe.
- Are you sure that's a good idea?
- Of course, I gave it to me myself.
I mean, I'm gonna give it to me myself,
so it has to be a good idea.
I mean, it will be a good idea.
(laughs)
You get me right.
- Counterclockwise.
You be careful, no playing around
with the timeline while I'm out, okay?
- Of course not, I know the rules by heart.
I am the guardian, you know.
- Cheeky!
Dwa!
Unify!
Off you go now.
- Thanks, bunny bug.
- Happy birthday, Alex! - Happy birthday, Alex!
- I'm so happy to see you.
- It's so cool to have you.
- Good, now one last thing.
I have to give myself this genius idea.
I need a genius idea, like now.
- Genius idea? - I need a delivery.
Am I at the right address?
- But you're-- - Bunny bug, AKA you,
with the Added Rabbit Miraculous.
I figured out a way to celebrate Alex's birthday
with Alex, interested?
- For real?
That'd be amazing!
Alex would be so happy to see everyone again,
even if it's just for a day.
I knew we'd come up with a better idea.
- Happy birthday, my darling daughter.
I'm so happy that you're here in person with us today.
- Me too, this is so cool, and you're all here.
- No, we're not, Marinette's missing, where is she?
- Running late, as usual.
- Classic Marinette.
- No, actually, we spoke on the phone
and she's laid up in bed, feeling super sick.
- She is?
Poor Marinette, I'm gonna go keep her company.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, don't do that.
It's super contagious, you can't go near her.
- I'll at least check in with her.
- No, don't, you'll wake her up.
She hasn't slept all night, she needs to rest.
Sleep is the best medicine, right?
- Okay, I'll just leave her a voice message then,
so she can listen to it when she wakes up.
- Oh, my Adrian's worried about me.
He's the best boyfriend ever.
What is wrong with me?
What was I about to do?
You don't mess with the timeline.
I was just looking nothing else.
- That's great news.
- There, now that's a perfect gift.
- Everything okay, Jaleel?
- I have to go and change.
- But you're gonna miss the party.
- Sorry, little sis, I can't stay like this.
- No, Mr. Dajancourt, we're not burning the painting
of the Liberty Leading the People.
- Oh, no, Jaleel's leaving already?
That's so sad.
But maybe something can be done about this.
Turning a plate a little to the left or to the right
isn't really changing the timeline.
Sorry about that.
There, crisis avoided.
- Whoa. - That looks delicious.
- Ew. - Ew.
- Gross, oh, I can't let that happen.
This won't throw the universe off balance.
- Whoa. - That looks delicious.
- Bye-bye, little pigeon.
Psst, time for cake.
The more we're all waiting for.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Alina ♪
- This was supposed to be perfect.
- Don't sweat it, bunny bug is here
to help you step by step.
Psst, time for cake.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Alex ♪
- Playing with the timeline is not so risky after all.
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
- Okay, I'm not touching anything anymore, for real.
♪ Happy birthday, dear Alex ♪
- This was supposed to be perfect.
- Sorry, Alex, your party is ruined.
Is this for me?
Thanks, Jaleel, that's such a cool photo.
- I look at it when I miss you.
- Things have changed, but we still love each other a lot.
Don't we, big bro?
(phone ringing)
- No, no, no, no, Mr. Dajancourt,
now stop harassing me, or I'll have you banned from the Louvre.
- Looks like things haven't changed that much.
(laughing)
- Okay, looks like things are fine.
I didn't do anything this time.
No, not like this.
This looks more like a ladybug situation.
She must be the one to fix this.
Except I'm not ladybug, I'm bunnybug.
And as holder of the Rabbit Miraculous,
I must not intervene or leave the borough.
It'd be too dangerous, but I can't just let
an akumatized villain roam free in Paris.
That's too dangerous too.
What should I do?
I know, I can go if I leave the Rabbit Miraculous
with someone else like I did with Bunnings.
I just have to find someone I trust 100%.
Like myself.
Tonight's Marinette will be perfect.
Don't tell me you need me to guard the Rabbit Miraculous.
How did you know?
- Well, I am you from the future.
- Of course, that makes sense.
Divide.
Marinette Dupain-Ching, here is the--
- Don't worry, I know the drill, flop clockwise.
- Good luck, this film's gonna be a toughie.
Oh, do you have any tips to make this easier?
- Unfortunately, I'm not allowed to interfere
with the timeline, I know.
I know you'll be all right.
- You can't stay like that, Juleel.
I'll go get something to clean you up.
Sorry, Plagg, picnic's over.
- There wasn't a single piece of cheese anyway.
The picnic might as well not even have started.
- Plagg, claws out!
- M'lady.
- You think they're trying to get in for free?
- I doubt they're fans of art.
- They don't look like fans of ours, either.
- It's nice of you to join this,
but we'll tick the unguided tour.
- Kata? - Careful, Kitty.
You could hurt the Akumatai's villain
if they turn out to be one of them.
- You're right, m'lady.
No one, may I?
- Sure, Kitty.
- Cataclysm.
There's no Ultra Akuma in this one.
- No one in here, either.
- Come on, where's the Akumatai's villain?
(evil laughter)
- You'll never find me!
- Sounds like it's coming from inside.
- Whoever you are, just what are you trying to achieve?
- Doing history justice.
The Louvre must become a fortress, protecting Paris again,
like Philip II of France had wanted.
- You should brush up on your history.
You're forgetting that the French Revolutionaries
want to turn this castle into a museum
so people could have access to art.
- Decadent art that tarnishes the battles of monarchy.
- More like art that upholds the values of democracy.
- There is nothing you can do to stop
the return of monarchy.
- Stop the return of monarchy.
- The Crown Gallery.
- You're right, if the villain thinks he's a monarchy,
he might be in there.
- Try to stop the monarchy, it's above you.
- Why try to keep us from getting in if the room's empty?
- Since you enjoy the museum so much,
how about becoming exhibits yourselves for eternity?
- It's a trap!
- Unleash Charm!
- Cataclysm!
- Come on, we've got to get out of here!
- Okay, so he isn't hiding in the castle.
- He is the castle!
- I am the Dark Castle!
And your magic will be no match for my power,
the noble stone that founded history!
- Milady, we could use some backup, don't you think?
- No need for backup, we can do this on our own, kitty.
- Whoa!
- Your optimism never ceases to amaze me, Milady.
- You'll never get Ladybug and Cat Noir
to rally behind your noble cause, Dark Castle.
- They deserve the fate reserved for traitors and rebels.
But first.
- Remember to seize their miraculous.
- Missed me!
- Can't get rid of a Ladybug that easy!
- The museum's closing, please proceed to the nearest exit.
- Cataclysm!
- Milady, I think I found the akumatized object.
- You'll never reduce the monarchy to ashes.
- There!
- Tary-ho!
(panting)
- How are we supposed to know where it'll reappear next?
- You can't, without a great stroke of luck.
- Lucky charm!
- Are you suggesting a picnic, Milady?
- No, I have another plan, a tight-up one.
- You think you can start a revolution
with a puny bit of string, you peasant?
(grunting)
- The day of glory has arrived!
- No more evil doing for you, Ultracouma.
- Time to de-evilize!
Gotcha!
- Bye-bye, little butterfly.
- Miraculous Ladybugs!
(grunting)
- Again with this vile pyramid,
it's defacing this noble building
that was once home to the French sovereigns.
- Mr. Dajancourt, weren't the pyramids
the last homes of the sovereigns of Egypt?
- They were, indeed.
You're right.
- This jewel will remind you
that we shouldn't rewrite past history,
for it helps us to make the right decisions
in shaping our future.
- Thank you, Ladybug.
You know, this pyramid isn't so ugly after all.
- Count it!
- Bunnynut, I'm done.
- Counter-clockwise!
- Good job, Ladybug.
Thanks, Marinette.
Fluff, Tiki, unify!
At last, I can go to bed.
- Thanks for your help.
If you want something done, do it yourself.
- She wasn't there.
It goes to show, but I need to check again
to make sure.
Again, and again, and again.
- So, how was your afternoon in the burrow?
Not too boring?
- No, not for a minute!
Spots and lobs away.
- You didn't miss the whole thing.
I brought you back some cake.
- Sorry about your surprise.
It could have been better if--
- Are you kidding?
It was uber-awesome!
The best birthday of my whole life!
Thank you, Marinette, for real.
- No, thank you for everything you do.
Your mission is such a hard one.
I can't make you do this anymore, Alex.
Becoming bunnocks again, living away from your friends,
just because I couldn't secure the butterfly miraculous,
this isn't fair.
It's my mistake, not yours.
- Okay, you can keep the rabbit miraculous,
but in exchange, you give me the Ladybug.
- Huh, but I'm Ladybug, and I am bunnocks.
And the best one there is.
Happy birthday, bunnocks.
Fluff Clockwise!
- Oh, you told me that you were sick.
I hope it's not too serious.
When you wake up, let me know if you need anything,
and I'll come right over.
- Thanks, Adrian, I just woke up,
and I think I'm still a bit contagious,
but I super appreciate your message,
and I'm sure that thanks to you,
I'll feel 100% tomorrow morning.
- So, how did the picnic go, sweetheart?
- It went great, Dad, and the cake was delicious.
- Ugh, what a day.
Three, two, one, and.
Don't tell me you need me to guard the rabbit miraculous.
- How did you know?
- Well, I am you from the future.
- Of course, makes sense.
Thanks for your help.
If you want something done, do it yourself.
Pound it.
(phone beeps)
See you tomorrow morning, Marinette.
I love you.
- I love you, Adrian.
See you tomorrow morning.