- Milady, look, that boy is saying goodbye to his family.
He's leaving his entire life behind.
- There's no other way, Kitty.
Lukaku Fey knows our secret identities.
- Are we really sure about that?
Has he told you who you are?
- Yes.
- What about me?
Did he tell you who I really am?
- Of course not.
I could never know who you are,
just like you could never know who I am.
- What if he's wrong about me?
(somber piano music)
- Klaus in.
Hey, wait!
Don't go, Luca!
- I have to go.
- Maybe you don't.
You say you know Ladybug and can't know
our secret identities, but how can you be sure?
Maybe you're wrong and you're leaving for Brazil
over nothing.
- If I stay, I'll only make it harder for Monarch
to be defeated by Ladybug and you.
- Hey, you're not allowed to be here.
- Luca, wait!
- I have faith in you both, Adrian.
I'll be back soon.
- In the daytime, I'm Marinette.
Just a normal girl with a normal life.
But there's something about me that no one knows yet.
'Cause I've got a secret.
♪ Miraculous, simply the best ♪
♪ I'm to the best when things go wrong ♪
♪ Miraculous, the luckiest ♪
♪ The power of double waves so strong ♪
♪ Miraculous ♪
- Remember your promise, Marinette.
- Adrian?
- Ladybug, can you explain what really happened?
- Fight took place at the famous fashion designer
Gabriel Agrest in Monarch.
- Marinette?
- You know, you can tell me anything, Marinette.
- I don't know how much longer I can do this.
I lied to everyone, Luca.
I told them that Gabriel Agrest was a hero,
but the truth is, he was the supervillain.
He was Monarch.
- What?
My father was Monarch?
How could you hide this from me, Marinette?
You lied to me!
You and I are over!
- No!
(panting)
- Another nightmare, Marinette?
- Not at all, I slept like a log.
I feel completely evilized.
I mean, energized.
- Are you really sure you're okay?
- It's fine, I'll be fine.
It's all gonna be wrong.
I mean, all right.
- Is everything okay, Adrian?
You only ate the cheese.
- I'm not that hungry, Natalie.
- I understand.
This morning's meeting is bound
to bring up painful memories.
I can go alone if you want.
- Natalie, I'm his son, I have to go.
Besides, Marinette will be there to support me.
- Give Adrian a big kiss from me, okay?
- Sure, and many more from Monarch.
I mean, from me.
Bye mom, de-evilize you later.
- Huh?
- See you later.
Love you.
(door creaking)
- Say hi to Adrian for me.
- Thanks for the chiquette sent to dad.
I mean, Super Dad.
- See you tonight, sweetheart.
- Marinette, maybe you should consider telling Adrian
the truth about his father.
It's eating away at you.
- No, I promised Monarch.
I mean, Gabriel aggressed that I would say nothing.
- If you keep mixing up your words,
you'll end up telling him everything by accident.
- You're right, Tiki, I have to focus.
But don't worry, I got this.
- Knock, knock.
- Who's there?
- Papa.
- Papa who?
- Papa Corn.
- What's wrong, Adrian?
You're as pale as a cannon bear rind.
- And Cat Noir, I was supposed to stop Monarch,
but instead my father sacrificed himself to defeat him.
I can't believe he and the hero who saved the world
are the same person.
It's like I'm missing something key here to understand,
like who he really was.
- Ladybug already told you how it went down, didn't she?
- Yes, but I can feel she's not telling me everything.
If only I'd been there when she faced Monarch.
Hold on, Plagg, you were there.
You can tell me what really happened.
- I was there, I was there.
I was inside the black cat ring in a magical energy state,
kind of like cheese in a fondue pot.
Needless to say, things were a bit blurry.
(knocking)
- Come in.
- Delivery of chouquettes and marinettes.
- Just what I needed.
- Are you talking about me or the chouquettes?
(laughing)
- Are you ready to deceive, I mean, leave?
- I am now that you're here.
- This is the proposal selected by the city of Paris
to replace the vandalized statue honoring Gabriel Agrest.
Similar to the previous proposal,
this statue will be financed by Mrs. Tsurugi
and Theo Barbeau will be in charge
of creating the sculpture.
- Upon reconsideration, the first statue
at the Place de Vaux Square didn't do justice
to your father's presence.
This one will be erected right outside City Hall
and will be more than 10 meters high.
- 10 meters?
That sounds pretty high, don't you think?
- Of course not.
Nothing's too high to illustrate
the greatness of your father, Adrian,
a man who was able to combine talent, presence, and courage.
- You knew my father?
- Of course.
I worked with him on several occasions.
He was like a mentor to me,
a man who defeated evil and poor taste
with his nimble fingers, a man who--
- Who tried to stop me from loving Marinette.
- Sorry?
My father might have been a hero,
but I think you're seeing him as greater
than he really was.
- Your moth--
Dad, your dad did save Ladybug.
- Don't you remember the taste of his pancakes, Marinette?
As dry and rigid as him.
- Are you telling me that he was also a good cook?
Such a model father.
- I'm sorry, I need to think about it.
- What about my statue, all good?
You agree to it?
- We will get back to you with our answer.
- Wait up!
Adrian, what's going on?
- Marinette, you knew my father.
Can you believe that he could have been
both the man who saved Paris and the man
who tried to keep us from loving each other?
- I'm sure he loved you in his own way.
- Even though I loved him too,
I can't just forget the harm he caused us.
And now hearing the way everyone talks about him,
I feel like they're talking about someone else.
I refuse to see him the way everyone else does.
Does that make me a bad son?
- No, of course not.
You've done nothing wrong.
- If only I'd been there, maybe I could have saved him.
- There's nothing you could have done.
- How do you know that?
Neither of us were there.
- Adrian, I think-- - Let's go home, Adrian.
- If you want, I can cancel my lyre lesson.
I mean, guitar lesson.
- No, no, go ahead.
Say hi to Luca for me.
- I can't take it anymore.
We have to tell Adrian the truth.
- Have you lost your mind?
You want to tell him that you're Ladybug.
- What do you mean?
- Only Ladybug would know that Gabriel Agrest
was a monarch, not Marinette Dupain Chang.
- Well, I could tell him everything as Ladybug.
- And let him figure out that I was monarch's accomplice?
We have determined a truth.
We're sticking to it.
You need to grin and bear it, Marinette.
It's too late to go back.
- Everything okay, Natalie?
- Yes, Marinette simply thought
she lost the keys to her scooter.
- Try strumming the strings with your fingers, Marinette.
You don't need to hit them.
- I swear I sounded better when I practiced yesterday.
I'll akumatize again.
Try again.
I'll try again.
- Bon dia, Marinette.
How are you?
- Hey, Rupay.
Todo bien.
Things are great.
Why wouldn't they be?
(laughing)
- I'm going for a swim.
- You two make such a cute couple.
There's clearly a monarch.
- Monarch?
- A spark.
I meant there's a spark.
- You can talk to me if something's wrong,
you know, Marinette.
- No, that's the thing.
I can't tell you.
Unless, of course, I can totally tell you.
I'll be right there.
- What?
Like now, in Brazil?
- Yes, I'll be there in an hour and 14 minutes.
Don't go anywhere.
I'm on my way.
- Shall we get breakfast?
I could go for a big açaí bowl.
- No, thank you.
I'd rather be alone for a while.
- Luca, I agreed to be your pretend girlfriend
to put up the pretense, but if it's hurting you,
don't you think it would be easier
if you just told Marinette the truth?
- I already tried.
- And how did it go?
- I'm sorry, I can't accept it.
- What, but you're the only one I can entrust with it.
- I'm heading back to Brazil, Marinette.
- But monarch's been defeated.
There's no need to go to--
- There's a new butterfly villain.
I don't want to risk being akumatized
and revealing your and Cat Noir's secret identities.
- This is crazy.
Why would you get akumatized?
- Sass, scales, slither.
- What are you doing?
- Marinette, the truth is I'm not leaving
because of the new butterfly villain.
- But then why are you leaving?
- You and Adrienne finally listened to your inner melodies
and today they're forming a beautiful symphony.
I'm happy for you two,
but I'm still in love with you, Marinette.
You're so radiant, so strong.
How could I stop loving you?
If I stay, I'm scared this pain will turn the joy
I feel about seeing you together into jealousy
and ruin our friendship.
That's why I'm leaving.
- Luca.
- It's gonna be hard being away from you.
- Please stay.
Adrienne and I will make sure not to be too close
when you're around.
Just please don't go.
- I apologize in advance for what I'm about to do.
- What are you about to do?
- I'm about to lie to you for the good of the three of us.
- No, don't do that.
(glass shattering)
Then why are you leaving?
- Because I've met an awesome girl in Brazil.
- You have?
That's amazing.
- I'll be your friend forever, Marinette.
You can always count on me.
- Luca, what did you tell Marinette?
- I couldn't bring myself to tell her anything.
- I'm sure you'll get there eventually.
- Natalie, I've thought about it
and I think I'd feel more comfortable
if there were no statue.
- Understood, I'll take care of it, Adrienne.
Hello, Madam Mayor?
- Power down.
- Did something bad happen, Guardian?
- No, Sass, I just need you to lend me
your miraculous for a moment, Luca, please.
Tiki, Sass, unify.
- Marinette, tell me what's going on.
- Luca, I lied to the entire world.
Adrienne's father wasn't a hero.
He was a monarch.
He made me swear that I wouldn't say a thing
so that Adrienne would think well of him
in order to protect him, but now because of that,
I'm having to lie to everyone.
- Why did you do that?
- Because I love Adrienne more than anything
and he'd be in so much pain if he ever found out.
He could get akumatized
by the new holder of the Butterfly Miraculous
and I'll never, ever, ever let anyone hurt him.
I have to keep this promise and hide the truth from him,
even if it burns my lips and my heart every day
until the end of time.
Do you think I did the right thing?
- I don't know, Marinette, I'm gonna ask you something
you'll probably find very strange with.
Please let me borrow your miraculous.
- What, why?
- I know things that you don't
and I'm probably the only one who can fix this.
Give me your earrings.
- No, no, tell me what you're gonna do
and I'll take care of it myself.
- Marinette, I love you.
You're the strongest person I've ever met,
but this time I'm the one who needs to protect you.
You have to trust me.
- I'm sorry, I never should have told you any of this.
- No, Marinette, you don't understand.
Give me your.
Marinette, tell me what's going on.
- Divide.
Be happy with Irube, please.
- You came all the way here just to tell me that?
- Yes, and that you must never worry about me, okay?
- What, but how can he refuse to have a statue
of his own father, a worldwide hero?
- He probably isn't ready yet.
We need to give him time to grieve.
- Such an unworthy son.
He doesn't recognize his own father's talent.
He doesn't recognize his legacy.
(dramatic music)
- Hello, forgive my intrusion,
but your anger was so great that it called out to me.
Is someone keeping you from honoring the great man
Gabriel Agrest?
- Yes, his ungrateful son, Adrian.
- I propose we teach Adrian a valuable lesson.
- It would be my honor.
And what should I call you?
- I have something in mind, but I wouldn't dare.
- Please do.
In that case, call me Mr. Agrest.
- Adrian!
- I win!
(laughing)
- Adrian!
- Correct me if I'm wrong,
but didn't you just turn down the building of this statue?
Time to say the magic words, don't you think?
- Adrian, get to safety.
- Adrian, I'm bringing you back to City Hall.
You're going to agree to the building of my statue
and recognize my brilliance.
- Natalie!
- Natalie's in danger.
Plagg, claws out!
Cataclysm!
- Adrian is still inside.
- I'll take care of him.
Get to safety.
- Seize Cat Noir's miraculous.
- You bring it back to me
and I'll explain how you can use it
to make a wish to bring Gabriel Agrest back, for example.
- What?
I can do that?
- You want to stop me from playing my role as a father, Cat?
- You're, you're no one's father!
Cataclysm!
- You're just a giant talking statue.
- Who are you to judge me, you tiny insignificant creature?
Cataclysm!
- No, no, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to cataclysm you.
- Did you just try to destroy me, huh?
- It really is just a statue.
Whoever this akumatized villain is,
he's hiding inside.
Cataclysm!
- If you want to be spared, help me find the Agrest's son.
- Never.
- I could really use a helping paw right now, m'lady.
(grunting)
- No one will stand between me and my son.
Cataclysm!
- Now, seize his miraculous.
(hissing)
- No!
- Clear away the rumble.
I want to see who was hiding beneath the mask.
- Mr. Agrest?
- Put the miraculous somewhere safe.
- What did you do to Cat Noir?
- She's vulnerable without a partner.
This is your chance.
(upbeat music)
(hissing)
- Is he invincible or something?
Lucky charm!
What am I supposed to do with all these?
- Go ahead, take off your earrings.
I want to see who Ladybug is.
- Oh no, no!
- Leave her alone!
- Hadrian!
- Who cares, seize Ladybug's earrings now!
- First, I have to talk some sense
into this unworthy son.
- Education first, I understand.
- But remember that we have a deal.
- You are such a good father,
then why didn't you want me to have any friends?
- Huh, you don't know what you're saying,
you ungrateful son.
- Of course, how did I not figure it out sooner?
Hadrian Agrest, use the megaphone on the ground!
- Why did you want to control my every move?
- What are you talking about?
- Why were you always traveling around the world
instead of staying with mom while she was sick?
Why didn't you want me to meet my grandparents?
- I, I didn't, he couldn't be like that.
- Why didn't you want me to go to school
like everyone else?
Why didn't you want me to be in love with Marinette?
- You're lying, you're talking nonsense.
- Why did you stop being popcorn and become this,
a cold, heartless statue?
(screaming)
- Miraculous Ladybug!
- What have I done?
- Sometimes, it's better to put ideas
rather than people on a pedestal.
For you never truly know someone.
This magical charm will help you remember that.
You know what you have to do,
hurry and take it back to Cat Noir.
Thank you, Adrian.
You've shown a great deal of courage
and I wouldn't have made it without you.
- Found it. - Found it.
- Good thing you were there, m'lady.
I wasn't at the top of my game today.
- That's why we're always here for each other, kitty cat.
(grunting)
Claws in.
- At least you got to tell that statue how you feel.
- It won't bring my father back
and it won't help me figure out who he was either.
I guess I'm gonna have to live with unanswered questions.
- Spot's off.
(phone ringing)
- I saw what happened at your place, are you okay?
- Everything's back in order, Marinette, I'm fine, thank you.
- Are you sure?
I mean, seeing your father again, it must have been--
- He was just an akumatized villain.
I'm going to be fine, really.
- Okay, then good night.
- Good night, Marinette.
- At least you're no longer mixing up your words, Marinette.
- I don't have a choice, either I keep it together
or everything will fall apart.
- Natalie was right, it's too late to go back now.
Power down.
- Luca Knows Ladybug?
- Do you think he holds him miraculous?
- I don't know, Manoey,
but Luca definitely loves having secrets.