- There, we can just adjust the length further if you want.
- No, it's perfect.
Oh, how about adding a pink head scarf?
What do you think?
- You're already so beautiful.
I'm not sure my heart could handle the scarf.
- Thank you for always being there for me, Jewel.
- You're gonna need new threads to go with the hair.
- In the daytime, I'm Marinette,
just a normal girl with a normal life.
But there's something about me that no one knows yet
'cause I've got a secret.
♪ Miraculous ♪
♪ Simply the best ♪
♪ I'm done the best when things go wrong ♪
♪ Miraculous ♪
♪ The lucky ends ♪
♪ The power of God always so strong ♪
♪ Miraculous ♪
(chimes tinkling)
- It's way too early for--
- Special delivery from the DuPan Chang Bakery.
I felt like doing something special with Adrian this morning
like having breakfast together, but in a unique way.
- You mean unique like yesterday and the day before and--
- No, no, no, it's not the same thing at all.
Yesterday we had croissants,
the day before was pond de chocolat,
but today I brought shoe cats.
- Not to mention the orange juice is already pressed
and the eggs are already scrambled, and--
- And the alarm clock hasn't gone off yet.
- I've missed you so much.
- I've missed you too.
- You saw each other at school yesterday.
- Actually we saw each other half an hour ago too
on our good morning video call.
- Technically it was 28 minutes and 12 seconds ago.
One of the longest waits of my life.
- (chuckles)
A letter?
For me?
Two movie tickets for a 50th anniversary screening
of "Vampire Horrific Musical Show"?
It was mailed from Roubaix.
- Your grandparents?
- Surprise!
- Told you he'd figure it out on his own.
The kid's a genius.
- It'll be the only screening in the world
for the 50th anniversary of the release
of "Vampire Musical Horrific Show".
- The film has gained a large court following
because the audience participates during the screening.
- You've got squirt guns to make it rain
when it's raining in the film.
- You throw paper planes around when bats are flying.
- You kiss when the two heroes
declare their love to each other.
- That's how we share our first kiss.
- Those are lovely fangs you've got.
- Oh, bite me, Tinder.
- We're going to Paris for the occasion
and we thought you two lovebirds could join us.
Like family bonding, you know?
- Wait, it's a horror movie?
- (laughs)
But with songs, amazing, no?
- You'll need costumes.
You don't go see the "Vampire Horrific Musical Show"
without dressing up like a vampire, it's tradition.
- You know the movie, Natalie?
- I've heard of it.
- Well, thank you, Grandma, Grandpa,
but Marinette doesn't really enjoy horror movies.
- What?
No, old Marinette didn't like those movies,
but new Marinette, aka Adrienne's girlfriend,
is not afraid of anything, especially horror movies.
(laughs)
- Magnifique, we'll pick you up at 6 p.m.
- Do you really like horror movies now?
- Um, don't you?
- You said that?
- I did!
- And what did he say?
- I don't know, Marinette.
I've never even watched a horror movie,
but it sounds like fun.
I'm curious to find out with you.
- Now I'm done for.
- That's right, you have to go see the movie with Adrienne
or you can kiss your relationship goodbye.
- See, I told you!
- Stop talking nonsense, Trick.
- Listen, girl, you definitely do not have to go see
this horror flick if you're not feeling up to it.
- But what if Adrienne likes the film?
He'll think that we don't have the same taste,
that we don't like the same things,
and he won't love me anymore!
- Marinette, couples don't have to do everything together
or like the same exact thing.
- Do you and Nino like the same things?
- Yep.
- And do you always do everything together?
- See?
- Nino and I are Nino and I.
Adrienne and you are Adrienne and you.
If horror movies aren't your thing, just tell him.
- You're right.
Adrienne and I are going to the vampire
musical horrific show tonight and it's gonna be amazing!
- Oh, you're so lucky.
I wanted to take Julica to see it for the first time,
but the tickets sold out a minute after they went on sale.
- What a shame.
If only there was someone who had tickets
but didn't want to go see it.
I don't know anyone quite like that.
Do you, Marinette?
- Nope.
(laughs)
Can't think of anyone.
(door slams)
- Hm?
(upbeat music)
- Ah, there's Pram, amazing!
♪ My friend, seeing you's the best ♪
♪ Your friendship is the honey to my breakfast ♪
♪ Princess Nora, mercy and I see ♪
♪ The shoe cats and green teas at breakfast for free ♪
♪ Vis-a-toi, vis-a-toi, ah, vis-a-toi, vis-a-toi ♪
♪ Prince Mark, merci, merci ♪
♪ For lending me the book that had me totally shook ♪
♪ Prince Adrinette, merci, merci ♪
♪ It took time to blossom, now your love is awesome ♪
♪ Vis-a-toi, vis-a-toi, ah, vis-a-toi ♪
♪ Vis-a-toi ♪
♪ Princess Rose, merci, merci ♪
♪ You and I truly share the same energy ♪
♪ Have unites and friends and crew ♪
♪ And again, thank you, thank you ♪
- What's the good news today, friends?
- Marinette and Adrien got tickets
for the Vampire Horrific Musical Show.
- How lucky!
I so wish I could have gone.
- Me too, it's my absolute favorite movie.
- Those are lovely fangs you got.
- Bite me tender!
- Let me show you something.
- Oh, just like in the Vampire Horrific Musical Show.
- A vampire origami, for you, Princess Rose.
- He gives presents to Rose because he loves her.
- Yes, I love Princess Rose.
I love her as a friend, a sweet, kind friend.
- That's not what we're seeing.
- Then what are you seeing?
- That she seems to be more than just a sweet, kind friend.
- Leave Prem alone!
- Stop it!
- Feeling like a rebel, are we?
Cockroach.
- You three are truly heartless.
- It's okay, Princess Marinette.
They can destroy all the origami in the world,
but they'll never destroy how I feel about Princess Rose
or the people closest to me.
Love always meant the heart.
- We're nice, but we're not as nice as Prem.
- (laughs) And what are you gonna do?
- We're gonna stop you from bullying other people.
- You should be ashamed of yourselves.
- (laughs) Pathetic, absolutely pathetic.
- No, no, hold on, Ray, they're right.
Let's admit that maybe we've gone too far
and messed up school unity.
- Are you making fun of us, Nelson?
- Of course not, I really mean it.
What do you say?
- First, you should apologize.
- And we paid Prem for what you've done.
- Have you gone completely bananas?
You wanna give a gift to that loser, Prem?
- More than that, Loic.
I mean, one gift would be generous,
but two gifts could turn poisonous.
- What are you talking about?
- Ray, you can get ahold of anything you want, right?
- Obviously.
- Perfect.
- Two tickets for the vampire horrific musical show.
- And now, watch and learn.
- Whoa, but how did you do it?
They were all sold out.
- There's always a spot for someone
who wants to redeem themselves, isn't there?
- Prince Nelson, thank you, thank you.
I'm thrilled that you've opened your heart to love
like a sunflower in the morning sun.
I'll sing your praises to everyone.
- Oh, that's not why I did it.
A good deed is a reward in itself.
Let's keep this between us.
- You really are so generous and so humble.
- Enjoy the movie with a friend.
What am I saying, with the princess of your choosing.
- Woohoo! (laughs)
- Princess Rose, Princess Rose, look what I just got.
- Two tickets for the vampire horrific musical show?
- Who gave you those, Prim?
- Love has Marinette, I told you, love mends the heart.
Will you go to the movies with me, Princess Rose?
- Oh, yes.
- This is amazing, now we can all go together.
- Hm, hm, as he steps out of the forest.
- The vampire places his hands on Jenny's shoulders.
- And everyone in the theater must grab the shoulders
of the person sitting in front of them.
- That's so thrilling.
- Sounds like fun.
- Right, fun.
That's the exact word I was about to use.
- Wait, Julica, what are we gonna do about Julica?
There are only two tickets.
- Showtime.
- Oh, right, Princess Rose,
you can't go without your princess.
- Here, Princess Julica, have my tickets.
- No, no, you two go together.
- You look sad, Jul.
- No, I'm not.
As long as you're happy, so am I.
You're gonna need makeup, I can do it if you want.
- The seed of jealousy has been sown in the soil of love.
I didn't get any of that, your sentences are way too wordy.
- You said they were about to break up, duh.
- It's not really a horror movie
since it's also a musical, and everyone knows that music
soothes the soul, I'm sure it can't be that scary.
- Whoa, amazing. - Whoa, amazing.
- Are you sure?
- Princess Marinette, you look horrifyingly beautiful.
- My turn.
- Adrian, are you done?
I'd like to use the mirror.
- I am ready.
(Marinette screaming)
- What's up, cute?
- Marinette, are you okay?
(Marinette panting)
(Marinette screaming)
- Marinette, are you sure you wanna go?
- Of course, I'm not being scared, screaming, yelling,
running away, and seeing your faces with horrifying makeup.
- Now let's go, kids.
- Whoa, we'll miss the start of the movie.
- Have fun.
- Thanks, Jewel, I'll call you as soon as we're done
and tell you all about it.
- Great, I can't wait.
(Marinette giggling)
- You can't let Rose and Prem be alone together.
Come on, get up.
We're going to the movie so you can tell them
how you really feel.
Be a fighter.
- Hey, Julica.
What's wrong, sis?
- Why aren't you here anymore?
- Of course I'm here, see?
- No, you're no longer here beside me.
Now that there's an ocean between us,
nothing's the same anymore.
We used to be able to tell each other everything
all the time, now I'm all alone.
- You have Rose.
- What if she left me someday like you did?
What if she found someone better than me?
Someone who's like her,
someone she can share everything with?
- Stop it, Jewel, I'm sure you're getting worried
over nothing.
- You don't know that, you're not here.
There's only one person I can count on anyway, myself.
- Yeah, things are always better with action.
- No need to grab my shoulders during the movie, okay?
It's not going to scare me.
- If you fold it along z-dotted lines,
you get a paper bath.
- Then you can throw it at the right time during the movie.
- Shoot, sorry, I'm sorry.
I forgot to turn it off.
- Luca?
- Did something happen between you and Julica?
- No, things are good, why?
- Horrific evening, everyone.
And welcome to this special screening
of the vampire horrific musical show.
For the first time in France,
you're about to watch an extended, unreleased version
with exclusive and even more terrifying footage.
30 additional minutes of thrill, anguish,
horror, terror, fear, freight.
- I would have been fine stopping at anguish.
- You can leave if you want to, Marinette.
- Oh, no nonsense, I love it when my heart
jumps out of my chest.
Horror movies are the best.
- Where are you going, Princess Rose?
- Julica's not okay, and it's my fault.
She's always there for me, and tonight I'm not there for her.
I didn't realize she'd be so sad
if I went to this movie without her.
- I'll go with Rose.
- No, you stay, I'll go.
- No, no, no, this is an important moment
for you and your grandparents.
- You're gonna miss the movie.
- It's okay, I already hate it anyway.
- But--
- Adrian, you were right all along.
I still don't like horror movies,
but I was afraid not coming with you
would drive us away from each other,
that you'd be disappointed in me,
that you'd love me less.
- Marinette, the only thing that could disappoint me
is if you feel you can't be honest with me
and you force yourself to do something
you don't want to just to please me.
- The blame falls upon me.
I'm the one who caused such distress
between Rose and Julica.
I need something horrific.
I'm horrific, I'm horrific.
(gasps)
- Hello, forgive my intrusion,
but I sensed a great deal of guilt.
- Get out of my head, evil supervillain.
I've done enough harm as it is today.
If I listen to you, I'll make someone else brokenhearted.
- You're wrong about my intentions, dear Prem.
People think I'm an evil person, like the former Hawk Moth,
when really, I only want to help my fellow humans.
- Why should I believe you?
- Because I'm offering you the power of your choosing
and I'm not asking for anything in return.
Not even Ladybug and Cat Noir's miraculous.
What more do you need to believe I'm acting selflessly?
- You're not tricking me?
- Of course not.
Just tell me what I should call you and see for yourself.
- Fine.
Then call me Count Vampigami.
(upbeat music)
- If Princess Rose and Julica can't come to the movie,
the movie will come to the princesses.
- Go, I think we should get out of here.
- I'm not Prem, I'm Count Vampigami.
- What's happening?
- Come on, Hunter.
- Be quiet, Marinette.
Don't say a word and whatever you do, do not transform.
There's a video camera above.
Unlike Kwamis, you can be filmed and recorded,
so just act like you're afraid of the akumatized villain
and you've come here to hide.
(dramatic music)
- Plagg, claws out.
- Trataclystal.
- Princess Rose, stay, stay.
Vampigami and his friends will go get Julica for you.
- If leading that girl alone is beyond your skills,
then you're the worst vampire friend there is.
- I'm not in the mood for jokes, fuzzbucket.
Step aside or get ready to express regret.
- Okay, so I guess we won't be premiering
our duet and concert.
- Too bad.
- Cataclysm, cataclysm, cataclysm.
Cataclysm.
(panting)
- A super ladybug would give me wings,
provided that her phone rings.
- Locked doors at the theater, a camera in the bathroom,
it's like someone knew that there'd be
an akumatization there today.
- It could be a trap from the new holder,
the Butterfly Miraculous.
- I don't know, but we're gonna have to be extra careful.
Tiki, spots on.
(beeping)
- Got your message.
On my way, kitty cat.
- Why prevent love from prevailing?
Join the ranks, Cat Noir, or the ranks will join you.
- For now, I'll be the one joining him.
Keep away from the kitty vampire.
- Oh, my lady, so glad to see you.
- Yeah, same, I'm super glad I love scary vampires.
(grunting)
- And these ones sing, too.
Bappa got me over there, she's the one running the show.
- Does it look terrifying at all?
(laughing)
- Is that noise coming from you?
- No, what noise?
Oh, right, it's my fingers, I can't help it.
Whenever I hear music, I have to snap my fingers.
(laughing)
- This music does make you wanna sing and clap your hands.
- Bappa got me, on the other hand,
must be stopped for clapping his hands.
- Well spotted, lady, when he claps his hands,
his soma dancers get new bat origamis.
- Hi, friend.
- Pigelle, purple tigress,
you're right on time for the vampire dance.
- Cat Noir, get the party started with your cataclysms.
I've got you covered, let's do charm!
- Cataclysm!
Superheroes always make the best games,
so you zombies can put away your things.
- Purple tigress, you're up.
- Gladly.
- Clout!
- Out!
- Pigelle, you're next!
Get!
(dramatic music)
- No more evil doing for you, Ultracouma.
Time to de-evilize!
Gotcha!
I buy a little butterfly.
Miraculous ladybug!
(dramatic music)
- Ladybug, what did I do?
- This magical charm will help you remember
that you can dance on your own,
or with another person, or even in a group,
but that some people may just not wanna dance,
and that's okay too.
- Pounded!
- Cat Noir, the new holder of the Miraculous
is not trying to defeat us
by using their akumatized villains to fight us.
They wanna defeat us by figuring out who we really are.
They're spying on us.
I already had a feeling, but it was confirmed today.
We've gotta stay alert.
- You can count on me.
I'm sorry, Princess Julica.
I never wanted to form rain clouds
in the blue sky of your relationship with Princess Rose,
or upset you.
If this is going to bring you sadness,
I'd rather not see the movie with Princess Rose.
You go with her.
- I'm not upset with you, Prem.
I'm upset with myself,
because I felt like since you and Rose liked the same movie,
you were meant for each other more than Rose and me.
- No way, Jul.
It's nothing like that.
- I'm so scared of losing you,
but I'm gonna try to overcome that fear.
- Just because we don't do everything together
doesn't mean that we don't love each other very much,
and there's no one I love more than you, Jul.
- Go see the movie together.
I'll be fine.
- Or you go.
You can have my ticket if you want.
- Have mine.
I hate horror movies anyway.
- Are you sure?
- Rose is right.
Just because you don't do everything together
doesn't mean that you love each other less.
- Hey kids, time to go.
- Oh, we'll miss this start of the movie.
- I love you. - I love you.
- Gag me.
More couples just means more fun breaking them up.
(Rose squealing)
- It has to be her.
It's the only logical explanation.
- If it were her, she would have transformed
right there and then, but she didn't.
- I'm missing something.
- It's not possible.
It has to be her.
- You have to explore other avenues, Lila.
- Tatsu, drive me home.