Everything in London is incredibly more incredible than in Paris.
All I need now is a minion to manicure my nails.
The last one turned out to be more than disappointing.
She totally betrayed me.
So, if you're interested and above all loyal, apply now.
You should stop watching these videos of Chloe.
She's really not a good person.
You're right, Mark.
Are you sure we can't ride together like we used to?
No, thanks, Daddy dear.
If someone was bothering you at school, you'd tell me, right?
Everything's fine, Dad.
Some girlfriends are waiting for me at the bus stop.
We're going to head to school together.
I'm really glad you made new friends.
Have fun, sweetheart.
In the daytime, I'm Marinette, just a normal girl with a normal life, but there's something
about me that no one knows yet, because I've got a secret.
Marinette, I don't understand, why does this dinner absolutely have to take place tonight,
otherwise it'll be a disaster?
Because Tiki, tonight the Ho-Tin Star will be in conjunction with Jupiter.
And what does that mean exactly?
Well, according to Mom, it brings good luck.
That's why I invited Adrian over tonight.
Besides, since we've been going out, we've kissed exactly 99 times, so if we kiss for
the hundredth time tonight, our love story is bound to last forever.
So you don't intend to kiss Adrian until this evening?
I got special authorization from the mayor of Paris, Mrs. Boussier, for Fire Captain
Hessempi to put on a fireworks display, especially for the occasion.
Wow, you really thought of everything.
That's right.
Love requires planning.
Speaking of which, I've got just enough time to put tonight's meal in the fridge and make
it to school on time.
Oh no, this is a disaster!
But tomorrow will be too late, Mr. Mechanic, if you don't fix it now, it'll all be a disaster!
If I don't get tonight's meal in the fridge in time, it'll go bad and then I won't have
anything for my evening with Adrian, which means I'll have to cancel.
And I'll miss this once-in-a-lifetime-tonight-only-lucky-conjunction!
Our hundredth kiss won't happen and my future love life will be ruined forever!
Bark, on the hunt.
That's why you have to get my scooter right now!
Hello?
Hello, citizen.
I couldn't help but notice that your electric vehicle is immobilized because of a breakdown.
I shall take it to the auto repair shop.
Our scooter problems are fixed.
And now, time to get these in the fridge.
Tiki, spots on!
Hello, sir, I need a vehicle repaired.
Fetch!
Hello?
Now let's take care of your car- where did she go?
Lay down.
Spots off!
Thanks to Miss Hand, you won't be late for school.
You're right, Tiki.
Sabrina used to be on Chloe's side doing evil things, and today she's acting for the greater
good, helping others!
With Sabrina, I finally succeeded where I failed with Chloe.
You were right to entrust her with Bark's Miraculous, that was a fitting choice.
Fitting!
I completely forgot to take Adrian's measurements for his suit!
My tape measure, I need my tape measure!
I made bento dinners for tonight.
I brought fruit tea.
Great!
That'll be so much better than the sugary soda we had last time.
I found the DVD for Misumi Yuki's movie, Lone Tigress and Cub.
Can't wait to see that movie after what you told us, Kagami.
This is going to be the best movie night ever!
Sorry!
Oh, yeah, excuse me.
Here comes Hurricane Marinette.
Sorry!
I need to borrow him for a minute.
Hello, Marinette.
No!
This morning we're kissing on the cheek.
Okay.
But why?
It's for a surprise.
For our surprise evening!
I guess this is for a surprise too, isn't it?
There's no hiding anything from you.
Ready for tonight, girl?
How?
How did you know?
Marinette, our girls' movie night is every first Wednesday of the month.
Of course we know about it.
And since it's at your place, there's no chance of you being late this time.
Tonight?
Our movie night?
Yeah, of course!
Duh!
You totally forgot, didn't you?
Not at all!
I'll see you girls later.
I have things to work out with Adrian.
She totally forgot.
Marinette.
Don't wait for me.
I have something to do.
Did you forget about movie night with your friends?
No!
Not at all!
It was all part of the plan.
It's a surprise, actually.
It's a new concept.
You might choose between BFFs and boyfriends when you can enjoy both at the same time.
It'll be our very first romantic friendly evening, like a couple group thing.
Surprise!
I'm not coming, Marinette.
What?
Everything okay, Sabrina?
If you need to talk.
It's just that I've lost my only friend, even though I know Chloe didn't really care about
me.
Now I'm trying to make new ones, but I just can't seem to.
When I see all of you, it's clear to me that I don't belong in your group, and why would
I?
I was so mean to everyone.
Deep down, I always knew none of it was right, but I genuinely love Chloe.
I thought she'd change eventually.
I know it took me too long to find the courage to stand up to her, and now I'm paying the
price.
You girls will always see me as Chloe Bourgeois' minion.
Maybe I should leave, go to a different school, just like she did.
There's no way you're changing school, Sabrina.
You're not Chloe's minion anymore.
I know how much courage it took.
I can see that.
Would you like to come to a movie night at Marinette's?
Marinette would never want me there.
She was Chloe's favorite victim.
We bullied her for years.
Marinette is a great girl.
Trust me, she'll say yes.
Are you sure?
Here, you want one?
Thanks.
What do you mean you're not coming?
When you decide to do things with people, it's to spend time with just them.
I'm not sure your girls' movie night would feel special to them if I was there for a
romantic evening at the same time.
That's why I'm not coming.
You can focus on being with just them.
We'll have our special evening together some other time.
Don't worry.
No.
No kiss.
Not now.
Sorry?
Sorry.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Oh no!
This is an absolute disaster!
If Adrian doesn't come over tonight, there will never be a hundredth kiss conjunction,
or a wedding, or house, or hamsters named Marinette!
No!
It took so long to get here.
It could not end like this.
I have to find a way to convince them to come over tonight despite the girls being there.
Of course!
If they were okay with this, I'm sure I could change Adrian's mind.
Hey girls, I was thinking about tonight.
Would you mind if we invited one more person over?
Totally.
Expanding our group is a cool idea.
I was actually thinking of inviting Hagley one of these days.
And Sublime too.
And on Dean.
Awesome!
Then I'll invite Sabrina.
I mean, there's already a lot of us and Marinette's room is so tiny.
Should we have enough beds?
And honestly, after everything she and Chloe did to us...
Girls, Chloe was the problem.
Well, Sabrina was her hench-girl.
But without her, we wouldn't be free from Chloe today.
And now she's all alone.
Yeah, I don't know.
Ask Marinette.
It's her place after all.
Fair enough.
Marinette!
Perfect timing!
I wanted to ask you, did you see Sabrina this morning?
Sabrina?
Yes, Sabrina.
She's blossoming.
Very independent.
That's great.
Actually, I'd like us to do something for her.
Definitely.
For sure.
Say girls, do you mind if we have an unexpected guest joining us tonight?
I mean, I know it's a bit awkward.
A different sort of person who doesn't quite fit the definition of our girlfriend's group.
Sure.
No problem, Marinette.
Really?
Thank you!
This is such a relief.
You always care about others.
That's your greatest quality!
You're the best!
Oh, stop it!
You girls are the best!
See you tonight!
Ta-da!
Good news!
You're officially invited to our girls' movie night!
Thank you, Zoe!
You have no idea what this means to me!
I told you Marinette was a great girl.
You're a great girl too.
Okay, you're right.
It doesn't make sense to go back and forth between the patio and the room.
I'll just stay with you and watch the movie on my phone.
Marinette, this thirty-seventh idea isn't going to change my mind either.
But the girls agreed.
No matter how you plan it, you won't really be with your girlfriends or with me.
Let's just see each other tomorrow.
It's no big deal.
Enjoy your evening with your friends.
Thank you, Marinette!
Uh, you're welcome.
Hurry, Dad!
I've got to get my PJs, my toothbrush, my eye drops, and Toot Toot whistle.
I've been invited to Marinette's house tonight.
That's great news, sweetheart.
You can count on your daddy to be on time.
I just don't get the connection between these petals and Japanese cinema.
Everything doesn't add up.
Still no sign of Adrian.
What's poppin', Marinette?
Nothing!
Nothing is poppin'.
Then why aren't you with us already?
Ha!
He told me he wasn't coming, but he did anyway!
He wanted to surprise me!
I knew it!
Sabrina?!
What are you doing here?
I'm here for movie night?
But who invited you?
You did.
What?
No, I invited Adrian, you didn't see him in the stairway, did you?
No, it's just me.
This is a disaster!
Sorry Marinette, I probably should go then.
Something can be done.
Do you know how to make the Hoatan star return to Jupiter another day?
Then no, nothing can be done.
Dad, can you please come get me?
Weren't you supposed to be sleeping at your friend's house?
There's no place for me.
Not at Marinette's house, not at the school, not in this city!
Don't move sweetheart, I'm coming right now!
Wait, wait, wait.
You invited Adrian to our sleepover?
The hundredth kiss, the fireworks, the stars, it could only happen tonight!
Without asking us?
But I did!
I told you about it earlier, you only agreed to it, but it looks like you didn't change
his mind and now everything is ruined.
I don't get it.
If Adrian was the surprise guest, but it wasn't him at the door, then who was?
Sabrina!
Hello!
Forgive my intrusion, but I sense a great deal of guilt preventing you from making friends.
No!
I'm coming sweetheart!
Hello!
Forgive my intrusion, but I sense the pain of a father helpless in the face of his daughter's
sorrow.
If you wish, I can give you the power to allow people to see your daughter the way you see
her.
What do you think?
I must fix this miscarriage of justice.
And what should I call you?
Daddy Kong!
Sabrina!
Come back!
This is a misunderstanding!
You!
Freeze!
In the name of love, I'm arresting you for moral damage to my daughter!
No, Dad!
It wasn't their fault!
You're finally going to see my Sabrina as I see her, through the eyes of love!
You only love me because you were forced to!
Sabrina!
Oh no!
This is a major disaster for real!
Tiki!
Spots on!
More!
More love for my daughter!
Sabrina!
We love you!
No!
Leave me alone!
Give me back my daughter right now!
Emergency evacuation service!
Sabrina!
We love you!
I feel for you.
I have the same problem with my fan club.
Give her back!
Candelar!
Create a diversion while I get Sabrina to safety!
I love being a distraction.
Power up!
Tanaquism!
Sabrina Rinconpria, I'm going to need Ms. Hound's help.
Ladybug, I don't deserve that Miraculous.
I'm an awful person.
I'm not worthy of being part of the Miraculars.
It's like I'm not worthy of having friends.
Sabrina, the reason I gave you the dog Miraculous is because I know you're a good person.
You've already changed.
You just can't see it yourself yet.
Visualize the Sabrina you've become.
The one you want everyone to see.
That's incredible!
You're incredible.
I'm enforcing the law!
You better get new glasses or learn how to aim, Daddy Cop.
I'll take care of him if you will.
Turn around.
But I'll crash into him.
Just trust me.
It's time for you to seize Cat Noir's Miraculous, dear Daddy Cop.
Lucky charm!
Thank you, m'lady.
Go recharge and then head to the Mulah Auto Repair Shop.
We're going to organize a little surprise for Daddy Cop.
Where's my daughter, you outlaw?
What have you done with her?
You'll have to catch me if you want to know.
Guess this game's gonna have to wait.
Whoa, awesome new get-up, Miss Hound.
Hinks, Cosmo Bug is going to need us.
Are you ready?
In position!
Now!
Cataclysm!
Retrogradation!
No more evil doing for you, little Akuma.
Time to de-evilize!
Gotcha!
Miraculous Linneybug!
It's great that you want to look after your daughter's well-being, Officer, but you don't
have to worry anymore.
Sabrina has it in her to make it on her own.
Probably because she has such a great dad.
Found it!
Dark Wings Baw.
Are you sure this is all really necessary?
Silence!
I ordered you not to address me, Kwami.
Now let's start again.
Are you sure everything's okay?
Don't worry, Mr. Register.
We'll take good care of her.
Have a nice evening, Daddy dear.
Thank you again for inviting me, Marinette.
I want to take this time to apologize to all of you.
I know I wasn't always nice to you girls, but I've changed.
And if you'll accept me, of course I'd be happy and proud to be your friend.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Besides, you were a victim of Chloe, too.
You were very brave separating yourself from her.
And I, too, want to apologize.
I've been focusing so much on my relationship with Adrien that I forgot to give my attention
to the ones who really needed it.
I promise I'll be more attentive from now on.
Welcome, Sabrina.
Yes, I told you.
I like it, Sabrina.
Wow!
Your new look is awesome!
You think so?
Oh, by the way, I forgot something.
100.
I wanted to save it for our special evening but, Liane, I realized that we don't need
a conjunction or fireworks to love each other.
101.
What's up, Cockroach?
Leave me alone, Ray.
What's the matter?
Are you afraid I'll show your new friends who you really are?
The nice thing about the digital world is that nothing ever disappears.
Just like who you were back in NYC, right, Cockroach?
I'm sorry, Ray.
I'm sorry.