Ladybug is still here. I can feel it. She must have transformed back. She's vulnerable.
Make sure that the others keep looking for Cat Noir. I'm going to give a personal, proper
welcome to Ladybug. Stomp. Your power is now mine.
Gabriel-san, don't put yourself at risk for nothing. Just let the plan unfold and we'll...
Draw. Let me be, Tsurugi-san. I know what I'm doing. Fortunately, I won't be needing
you much longer. Kagami...
Yes? Gabriel has cut me off the system. His obsession
may cause us to lose everything. Go to his mansion. Be my eyes and arms.
In the daytime, I'm Marinette. Just a normal girl with a normal life. But there's something
about that. No one knows it. Because I've got a secret.
Miraculous. Simply the best. After the death, when things go wrong.
Miraculous. The luckiest. The power of devil weighs so strong.
Miraculous. Miraculous.
Have a nice day, sir. Wait. Hello. Sorry, these ones are special. They're
for Adrien. What surprise have you come up with this
time, Marinette? I'll tell you, but only after I'm sure it's
a birdhouse. A bag of seeds. And a bird whistle.
I've got it!
Hello, pretty dove.
Have a good day. I love you, Marinette.
Thanks for the surprise, Marinette. I love you, too.
You really are the superhero of surprises. Marinette is so wonderful. She always does
amazingly creative things for me, like the surprise. Well, the only thing I can do is
send her a voice message. No one expects a cheese maker to be great
at sewing, too. Yet everyone knows that cheese makers are exceptional beings.
Of course. You're right, Plagg. I know.
So, what do you think? When we talked about finding a hiding place,
I thought of a lot of spots, but never this.
Believe me, it's the safest option. I love you, too.
If I had mentioned mechanics, would you have built her a moped?
No, Plagg. I chose knitting because Marinette is passionate about fashion
design, and I'm sure she won't be expecting this surprise.
Oh, it's a towel. A hand towel?
Uh, no, Marinette. Actually, it's a t-shirt.
Oh, right. Of course it's a t-shirt. These bigger holes are for arms.
This is so surprising, Adrian. That's so nice of you. Thank you.
Mother, I'm going out.
What about your ikebana class?
We've discussed this. I'm no longer wasting time making boring flower arrangements.
You'd rather waste your time with that boy?
Felix isn't just a boy.
They love each other, and love won't wait.
After all I've done for you, after everything I've lost,
how can you put your life in the hands of a monster
who could be rid of you with the snap of his fingers?
Felix would never do that. He's helping me find meaning to my life
instead of trying to control it like you always did.
The only monster here isn't Felix or me. It's you.
Insolent girl. Whether you like it or not, you are a tsurugi.
You are not worthy of wearing our family ring.
You'll earn it back again when you respect our values.
Long, break the storm!
Oh!
You're the one who hasn't kept her promise, Mother.
I allowed you to go to school.
And I saved you from humiliation!
You and Monarch's accomplice, remember?
If it weren't for me, Ladybug would have brought you to justice.
But I promised her that you'd change, that she trusted me.
Enough to hide what you and Gabriel Agrest did from the whole world!
Enough to leave me the dragon miraculous knowing I live in the same room as you!
I should stop loving you for everything you've done.
But I can't. Adrian has lost his father forever.
Do you realize how lucky we are to still have each other?
Please don't ruin everything.
Wind Dragon.
I'm not as creative as Marinette.
But this cake is bound to help me measure up.
Do you really want to give a cake to a baker's daughter?
You're right. Why would she want a cake from me when she can have all she wants at home?
The best in Paris.
But then what could make her happy?
I have an idea.
What is he doing with that large hunk of meat?
Are you really sure about this?
Absolutely. Beef rib is a no-brainer when it comes to romance a la Francais.
Hey!
I think I'm gonna need another idea.
Or just another beef rib.
[phone rings]
Tsurugi-san.
Gabriel-san. I knew you'd call for my help eventually.
Lady Bug and Cat Noir are stronger than I anticipated.
Or rather, you are too weak.
There are two of them, and I'm just one.
But with your help, I could repair the Peacock Miraculous. Then Natalie could join me.
That's out of the question. I'm never touching that wretched Miraculous again.
The price I paid to have Kagami using his magic was high enough.
As for you, I thought losing your wife would have brought you to your senses.
Playing supervillains. You're disgracing yourself, Gabriel.
Tamui, if you help me attain Lady Bug and Cat Noir's Miraculous, we'll make the wish together.
I'll get my wife back, and you'll get your eyes back.
That would mean betraying the kingdom.
Are you having qualms? I wasn't aware of such weakness in you.
How can I be sure you won't betray me as well?
What proof of my loyalty do you need?
I have been disappointed by men my entire life.
I want Kagami to grow up to have a prince charming as perfect as she is.
Smart, strong, handsome, and obedient.
Someone like my son.
Perhaps. Let's introduce them first.
If your lineage proves worthy of uniting with mine, I might consider helping you.
[Footsteps]
Perfect.
Kagami.
Yes, Mother?
How would you like to move to Paris?
Hello, Mother.
Forgive my intrusion, but I've sensed your disappointment, so I thought I'd pay you a little visit.
Nuru, dark wings rise.
Kagami was so perfect.
It must be so painful to feel your favorite daughter escape from your grasp.
Luckily, I am here.
What do you want, Laila?
To help you.
It must be hard playing the kind mother.
You know as well as I do that I have no choice if I want my freedom.
Things would be so much easier if Kagami obeyed you again, wouldn't they?
As long as Kagami bears the ring holding the muck that I used to give birth to her,
I cannot control her.
She will do whatever she wants.
You might not be able to control her, but you could control the company she keeps.
Would you like to hear about the plan I've devised?
First, I'll akumatize you.
Once you've become a supervillain, you'll capture Felix.
I'll be waiting for Felix inside your armor.
Since Felix too, like Kagami, is connected to the magic of an amok,
the only thing left for me to do will be to seize the object of control, his signet ring.
From now on, you will be a spy within the Miraculars.
You'll give us all the information we need to seize Ladybug and Cat Noir's Miraculous.
At your command.
Once I've replaced his ring with a forgery, you'll drop me off in a quiet place.
Then you'll pretend you've seen the error of your ways,
and in a final effort you'll reject the Ultrakuma,
unapologized to Kagami, telling her...
I've realized my errors, Kagami.
And from now on, I'll let you live your life with Felix.
Kagami will be happy to be reunited with her boyfriend,
except he will no longer be her Felix, but our Felix.
You can no longer control your daughter, but you'll be able to control her boyfriend.
How do I know you'll stick to your word this time?
I'm only doing what's in your best interest.
It's my mother again.
Something wrong?
Everything's fine now that you're here.
Are you sure Marinette will agree?
Can you imagine Marinette refusing to help someone?
Of course you're right.
What a strange optic, Marinette. What is it for?
It's a special hanger for Adrien's special T-shirt.
This T-shirt would be perfect for someone with four arms.
It's the thought that counts, Tiki.
Ryuko? Argos?
Why do they want to see you?
We're about to find out.
We need you, Marinette.
What's going on?
You know our secret. You know that our mothers carried us like any children,
but since they used the Peacock Miraculous,
our existences are bound by its magic, which makes us especially vulnerable.
Whoever has the Peacock Miraculous has the power of life and death
over every being created by its magic.
Now that I'm the holder, we know for sure no one will use it for evil.
No one can destroy us with the snap of their fingers.
But then what's the problem?
Storm subsides.
The problem, Marinette, is our rings.
The amok holding the magic of the Peacock Miraculous was deposited into them.
If someone were to seize them, we'd have no choice but to obey them.
If they got damaged, we'd become seriously ill.
And if they got destroyed, we'd disappear.
Living with this knowledge is...
I get it. You need me to put them somewhere safe, right?
Yes, Marinette, that's right.
We've considered everything.
Burying them in an isolated place...
But it's risky in case of future excavations or construction.
Locking them in a safe, the bank...
They could be stolen.
Even sending them into space wouldn't be a solution.
Cosmic radiation could damage them.
And since we're also superheroes, we're running the risk of enemies badly enough for them.
But you're here to see me because you already came up with a solution, haven't you?
Yes. Magic.
You're Yo-Yo's magic.
This is very clever! Good job!
Indeed.
Once immersed in the field of possibilities of Ladybug's Yo-Yo,
the rings could return to a Quantic state.
Of course! And the only person in the universe who could access them would be...
Ladybug!
Hold on, hold on! Explain it to me again like I'm five years old!
It means the rings would be stored in the form of magic puree in your Yo-Yo.
And there'd be no risk of turning Kagami and Felix into puree too, right?
There'd be absolutely no risk for them since the rings would still exist,
but in the form of probabilities.
Okay...
And when you're not Ladybug, it'd be completely inaccessible.
No Ladybug, no Yo-Yo, no Yo-Yo, no stealing the rings!
It's a good idea, isn't it?
I don't know.
For a while I kept all the miraculous with me and my Yo-Yo,
but that didn't stop Shadow Moth from stealing them from me.
That wasn't your fault.
There will always be a risk.
But if there's one person who always finds a solution, it's you, Ladybug.
Tiki, spots on!
I'm touched by your trust, even though this is a great responsibility.
You're entrusting me with your lives.
You can decline. We don't want to force your hand.
No, it's okay. I want to help you.
Marinette!
There's a surprise guest for you!
Kagami, Felix, what are you doing here?
We didn't even see you come in!
Where's Marinette?
I'm right here!
Ah, great. I hope you're ready because I have another surprise for you.
Uh, now?
Ta-da! A beef rib!
That's not a beef rib. Those are lamb chops.
I know, but the butcher was out of beef ribs.
Okay...
With some garlic and rosemary, these will be delicious!
I still can't figure out why you're here.
The rings!
What rings?
You tell him!
You know, we have these old family rings, and Kagami and I thought these old rings...
You thought that... that we'd ask Marinette to help us hide them.
Hide them? But why would you want to hide them?
We want to hide them because it's romantic.
Romantic?
Yes. I read it in a manga.
Wanting to give a gift to their future unborn children,
the two sweethearts had cherished objects of theirs together.
Oh, and where did they hide them?
In a... tomb, right?
And that's romantic?
No, not at all. A purée is a terrible hiding place, and that's why Kagami and Felix came to see me.
To come up with a better purée. I mean, a better idea than the one in the manga.
Ah, what's your idea then?
I'll tell you, but first you've got to help us find the rings,
because no rings means no hiding place, and no hiding place means no idea.
Ah! They were right there, look!
The rings!
Watch this, Marinette.
I might not be the best when it comes to knitting or choosing meat, but I can do this.
Magic.
What have you done?
Where are the rings?
I watched a magic tutorial online.
Not bad, huh?
What about my ring?
Felix, open your hand.
Ta-da!
You're being reckless, Adrian. You don't mess with valuables. Give me my ring back!
It's just a magic trick, Felix. No need to panic.
You're right, everything's fine. Why am I worrying?
It's your mother, Kagami.
Mother, that's enough! I don't want to talk to you right now!
That's fine, Kagami. I just needed to know where you were.
Felix Fathom, you are our bad influence! You'll never be anywhere near my daughter again!
Mother, no!
Felix!
And you'll never transform again, either!
This isn't his object of control, it's Kagami's!
Adrian Agrest has Felix's ring!
Adrian Agrest, you too won't be going anywhere near Kagami ever again!
No, no, Mr. Ruby, you're mistaken. Kagami is just a friend. I'm in love with Marinette.
I'm not taking any risks.
Believing in Agrest!
Aren't you two staying for lunch?
Sorry, we have a small emergency.
Where are Kagami and Adrian?
Sabine, I don't think there'll be enough cutlets for everyone.
Don't move. You'll be safe here.
What about you?
I'm going to get my mother away from here.
Wouldn't it be safer if I kept it?
I'd rather you didn't.
Wow, she treats her boyfriend's ring with so much care.
Do you think that's what being romantic looks like?
Plagg, claw them!
Mother, I'm here!
My daughter has Felix's ring now.
Plagg, break the storm!
Water Dragon!
Kagami, get back here!
Kagami and Felix's lives are in danger. Tiki, spots on!
Lucky Charm!
Come to your senses. Prove to your daughter that you've changed!
Not while she's with that boy!
I'm in love with Felix, Mother!
He's not meant for you. He'll end up hurting you, like Adrian, like every other boy!
That's your choice. You want to keep being a supervillain?
When you get out of control, I must get you on track. That's a mother's job.
I don't choose my path or select who's worthy of my love!
I am your mother!
Keep that up and soon I won't be your son!
Not a good girl!
Where's your Ultra Akuma if it's not in there?
Our plan won't work.
Yoksi goes in. Help me escape without being noticed by the superheroes.
Son, you have no feeling at all for me, Mother?
Now!
No! Get out of my hand! You won't fool me again!
I don't want your wretched power anymore!
This is all because I've been akumatized! I'm sorry, Kagami!
You're perfect. Larger than life.
I wouldn't want to lose my one and only daughter for the world. Can you forgive me?
Storm subsides.
I forgive you, Mother.
Miraculous Ladybug!
Kagami?
*sigh*
It's so romantic!
It is, Kitty Cat. And it's perfect this way.
Bound it!
How touching.
Lamb cutlets are a great gift idea.
Yes, very unexpected.
I know it's not as romantic as bearing rings in puree.
I feel like nothing will ever be enough to show Marinette how much I love her.
Oh, that's just too sweet.
When Marinette does it, it's sweet. But when I do it, it's just playing weird.
No, what's weird is when you try to do things my way.
I'm usually the one who does weird things. You're Adrien. You do rational things.
And it's not true that you don't do anything special for Marinette, Adrien.
If it weren't for your cutlets, we wouldn't be sitting at this table together tonight.
You're already a part of the family, kid.
See, Sugarcube? A good meal is always a success.
Connection.
The machine has joined us. We may begin.
Gabriel Agrest was an exceptional diamond.
It is my pleasure to introduce you to the new king of luxury, the new diamond.
The diamond is dead.
Long live the diamond!