What is that?
Help!
Benham!
Don't touch me!
Put me down!
Everything's OK.
It's over.
Let me go!
I'll shut down the subway.
You deal with the villain.
In the daytime, I'm Marinette.
Just a normal girl with a normal life.
But there's something about me that no one knows yet,
because I've got a secret.
(SINGING) Miraculous, simply the best, act on the best when
things go wrong.
Miraculous, the luckiest, the power of doubt always so strong.
Miraculous.
She was scared of Ladybug?
For real?
Yes, I'm telling you.
That's strange, right?
I didn't do anything to her.
[GROANING]
It's nothing ugly, eh?
It's just a nice little Ladybug.
It's going to attack me!
Smells good.
What is it?
Essential oils.
The scent is supposed to repel bugs.
Did it go this way?
No, that way?
There's another one!
I've been like this ever since I got akumatized.
At first, I was only scared of butterflies,
because they reminded me of the akuma that hit me.
And now you're scared of all bugs?
Bees, flies, Ladybugs.
I'm even afraid of Ladybug herself.
But Ladybug isn't scary.
She helps people.
I know, but I can't control myself.
I'm terrified of getting akumatized again.
At least you're safe here.
There won't be any bugs in the classroom.
Need for lunch?
Mm-hmm.
This is all my fault.
If I had the butterfly, Miraculous, people like Aglae
wouldn't be so traumatized.
It's not your fault, Marinette.
You're already doing your best to free the akumatized people
and fix all the damage they cause.
Maybe, but Magic Ladybugs don't fix everything.
It's too hard!
I can't do this!
We can't leave her like this.
I thought I was doing better, but it's actually getting worse.
I'll stay home tomorrow and I'm never going out again
if it means I won't be scared anymore.
No, don't do that.
We can come up with a solution.
I could craft you a, let's say, an anti-bug protection suit.
Or we could look for a more rational solution,
one that would actually help Aglae overcome her fear.
When it comes to phobias or fears,
seeing a specialist is most recommended.
I myself see a psychiatrist because I'm on the autism spectrum.
The autism spectrum?
What's that?
It means I see things in a different way than you do.
Neuro-atypical brains provide new insight into the world.
The problem is that our environment is designed for neurotypical people.
In my case, for example, lateness can be distressing,
as well as misplaced things in unfamiliar places.
That's why I see Dr. Psyka every Thursday at 6.15 p.m.
She helps me overcome my difficulties.
But I'm not on the autism spectrum.
It doesn't matter.
Dr. Psyka can also help people with phobias.
You're scared of butterflies and I was scared of the dark, of germs, mice,
but I talked to her and it helped me.
That sounds so lame. I'd never go.
Too bad, 'cause it can also help senseless and mean people like you.
Don't listen to toxic people with failed socialization, Aglae.
But what will I talk to Dr. Psyka about?
Things you don't always want to tell other people.
And that helps you feel better?
A lot better.
Okay, I'll give it a try.
Thanks for coming with me, friends.
Oh my, Alia, Max, Julika, Milen.
I'm not sure I'll have time to see all of you.
Aglae is your only appointment, Dr. Psyka.
We just came with her.
Your friends came with you.
Quite significant and very kind of you all.
If you're ready, Aglae, you can come with me.
What's with all the models?
Well, life can take many different paths.
So many that you can sometimes feel lost.
But I'm here to help you find your own path
and pick the right vehicle to travel down it with serenity.
You can have the car if you like it.
And you can sit anywhere you want.
I spoke to your dad on the phone.
He told me about some issues you've been having.
But I'd like to hear it in your own words.
What would you like to talk to me about?
I don't know.
Your dad mentioned a problem with, uh, butterflies?
It's because of the day I got akumatized.
It was the first day back at school.
Ladybug had claimed that she defeated super villain Hawk Moth,
so I thought I'd be safe to leave my house again and go back to school.
It had been so long that I didn't know how to act around people anymore.
I'd shake, stammer.
I felt like I had become an alien.
I wanted to be part of the group, but I couldn't do it.
Since it was the first day back at school,
my science teacher, Mrs. Dublecal,
had planned a visit to the butterfly house in the lab there.
I wanted to go with the group,
especially because I used to love butterflies and biodiversity as a whole.
Besides, I thought that all the akumatizations were over,
that I had no reason to be scared anymore.
I couldn't do it.
And yet I really wanted to follow them,
to do like them, to be like them,
but I just couldn't do it.
And that's when they showed up.
Dr. Psyka is awesome.
It helped a lot to talk to her, you know.
Huh? I didn't know you were seeing her too. What for?
Well, let's just say some kind of complicated family issues.
You never told me about that.
I worked it out a long time ago.
I don't even think about it anymore.
Do you think I could talk to Dr. Psyka about my father?
Your father? Why? You can talk to me about him, right?
Yes, of course, you're right.
Talking with Dr. Psyka is different, Marinette.
She's someone from the outside with specific skills to help.
I help him. I'm his girlfriend, you know.
I know, but that's not the point.
How can I put this?
Okay, let's say we're in a video game.
Adrian is trapped in a maze being chased by a ghost.
You can face the ghost and temporarily help Adrian,
but the ghost will always come back.
Until Adrian figures out why he can't face the ghost,
he'll be stuck in the maze.
Dr. Psyka can help him find the exit
by guiding him from the outside.
See what I mean?
I think I do, and I'd like to try.
It doesn't mean you're not helpful.
Adrian can talk to both of you,
but you'll be there to support Adrian
while Dr. Psyka will heal him.
We can stop for now if you feel like you need a break.
No, I want to keep going.
All right, you were saying that's when they showed up.
Who are "they"?
They asked me what was wrong.
I told them I was scared of butterflies.
They said they would help me,
that they'd walk into the greenhouse with me.
They closed the door behind me,
and I was suddenly all alone.
I could have walked back out, but I couldn't think straight.
I don't know why.
I was completely frozen,
and the butterflies were flying towards me,
and among them there was...
There was an ultracouma. Is that it?
Strange voices spoke to me,
and I knew right away that there was a new villain in Paris,
that someone had gotten their hands on the butterfly miraculous
lost by Ladybug,
and that this someone was even scarier than the one before them.
They said that they'd help me show people
who make fun of my fears how dangerous butterflies can be.
I accepted, and I don't remember anything that happened next,
like everyone who's been akumatized.
But people told me, and there are videos online,
so I still have these metal images.
What kind of images?
I saw videos of me where I'm barely recognizable.
I looked like a huge butterfly,
and I was attacking the boys who had made fun of me.
I was told that I called myself Lady Butterfly,
and that I'd trap people inside cocoons,
but I didn't stop at the three boys.
From what I heard, I went after everyone in Paris.
Next, according to witnesses,
Ladybug and the miraculous showed up,
and saved me.
So the whole story didn't end so badly.
Ladybug saved you, and everyone was freed.
Yes, but I could get akumatized again.
I'm so scared all the time,
and I know that makes me even more vulnerable.
This fear, precisely, it's quite significant.
Why were you so scared of getting akumatized
even before it happened to you?
Because of Timebreaker.
What am I supposed to see in this photo?
Me!
But you're not in the photo, Aglai.
I am! She made me disappear!
And how did you feel about that?
As I was disappearing, I completely lost track of time.
I didn't know if seconds or months were passing.
I was scared that soon I would no longer exist,
that I'd never see my friends again, or my family,
that I would no longer be able to do
any of the things I want to do.
But that time, too, Ladybug fixed everything, didn't she?
Yes, and when the magic ladybugs repaired everything,
I thought I'd be able to enjoy life again,
even more than before.
But a few days later, a butterfly landed on me,
and that's when it all started.
I used to love them, but now I was terrified of them.
I went home, and I shot myself in my room.
I was too scared of something bad happening to me.
Thank you for telling me all this, Aglai.
Now, what we're going to try is to, so to speak, de-evilize you,
like Ladybug did when you were akumatized,
except she did it for you.
I'm going to need you to do it for yourself.
What do you mean?
Here's what I propose in our next session.
We'll do an exercise--
Hold on, what next session?
Won't I be healed today?
Oh, I'm afraid not.
Healing depends on the road ahead
and on the vehicle you're traveling in.
Try to have patience.
But that's not possible!
I can't wait.
I can't stay like this.
It's good to be eager, but--
I was told that if I came here and talked,
I would feel better.
Therapy isn't a magic solution.
It requires time.
I suggest that when you feel ready,
we'll go back to the Butterfly House together
so I can help you overcome your fears.
Your friends can come--
No, I need you to help me right now!
You said you would do it like Ladybug!
What I meant was--
What is the point in coming here
and spilling my guts if you won't help me?
You're useless!
I understand you're angry, but come back.
Let's talk about it calmly.
No, I've talked enough already,
and nothing's changed.
I'm never coming back!
Was that Adelaide?
She took the elevator.
Now, forgive my intrusion.
I couldn't help but sense
some kind of frustration in you.
Do you feel guilty that you couldn't help the girl?
No! Get out of my head!
You're trying to use my emotions to manipulate me,
but I'll never help you hurt people!
I understand your reaction.
There are many misunderstandings about me.
Unlike what you'd want to believe,
I'm trying to help people, not hurt them.
Wouldn't you desire a magical solution
that could heal people, for example?
There is no such thing as a magical solution.
And yet that's what Ladybug does, doesn't she?
Magically fixing everything with a swing of her yo-yo?
Thanks to me, you could do the same
and put an end to people's needless suffering.
I can sense your hesitation, and perhaps you're right.
People should find their paths on their own.
Who cares if they suffer for months, sometimes years on end?
I'll leave you be.
No, wait! I...
I'll give it a try.
You will? In that case, what should I call you?
Reckless driver.
Aglaya! Aglaya, what happened?
This was never a good idea.
I can't be healed.
I'm going home and shutting myself away forever.
There's nothing that can be done!
The first session is an unexceptional experience
in seven out of ten cases.
It doesn't mean you should stop.
Aglaya, come back!
I can heal you instantly now, just like you wanted.
No, you've been akumatized!
What are you doing?
I'm going to try to help Aglaya.
I'll be super careful, I promise.
I think it's best to cut Dr. Stika's session short for today.
Tiki, spots on!
Don't tell me you want to play Cat Noir and rescue your girlfriend.
Precisely! Plagg Klauser!
Quite significant.
I know you have a phobia of insects,
and more specifically of these awful butterflies,
but I'll fix it for you.
There, you are now demonized and free from all your fears.
Thanks to Reckless Driver, I'm no longer scared of anything!
Okay, still stay here, it's safer.
There's no danger! She healed me! How amazing!
Yeah, well, she still needs to be de-akumatized.
You must, but it's a shame she's a great superhero too.
I'm on the akumatized villain's track, m'lady.
Two safety measures are better than one.
No need for safety, Cat Noir.
I used to be afraid of cars, but not anymore.
You can't stay here, sir.
Why not? This is where the sun is.
True, but it's also where cars are.
That's okay. Drivers have eyes. They'll avoid me.
I'm sorry, but I can't let you take this kind of risk.
Hey, team. Blast!
Clash!
Are you afraid of me, Ladybug? Quite significant.
Of course I'm not. We just have to stop you.
But you're not sure whether it's the right thing to do.
I am. You can't speed up solutions like this without there being some other price to pay.
Sometimes meaningful help takes time.
Are you sure?
She's going to drive us buggered.
That's quite a significant observation. We could go for some group therapy.
I'd rather go for a...
Lucky charm!
Uh, okay. Not sure this will help.
What in the world is all this?
Those are some awesome illusions, Rena.
Pegasus, we need your portals.
Voyage!
Looks like it's bad time.
The ultracromer must be in the car, kitty cat.
We'll try, milady. Cataclysm!
Cano R, everything okay?
Let's see what you're afraid of, cat.
Oh, of course, revealing your secret identity. Quite significant.
Well, time to de-evilize.
There, you are now de-evilized and free.
What's going on?
It's fine, reckless driver. I'm just helping you.
I've deprived him of his powers. He is at your mercy. You can see he's as miraculous now.
That's not significant at all. I told you I only want to do good.
Precisely. If we got our hands on the cat miraculous, we'd only need the ladybug one.
Then we can make a wish for people to be freed from their fears all across the world.
That would be very significant, wouldn't it?
Milady, am I glad to see you. This akumatized villain is amazing.
Thanks to her, I no longer am afraid of revealing my secret identity. I can finally tell you.
No talking with your mouth full, kitty cat.
Turn!
Holy mouse!
Attack!
Whenever you're ready, purple tigress.
Clutch!
Why hasn't she transformed back?
I don't see an ultracuma, which means it wasn't in the car.
Maybe it was something inside the car.
No more evil doing for you, ultracuma.
Time to de-evilize!
Gotcha!
Bye-bye, little butterfly.
I mean...
Miraculous ladybug!
This magical charm will help you remember that you should believe in yourself.
You're a good therapist. I'm sure you've helped a lot of people.
People who've had family problems, phobias, or communication issues.
You never needed a magical solution because you already know how to de-evilize people.
For good.
Even though it can take a while sometimes.
Thank you, ladybug.
Hound it!
You will tell me your secret in the end, ladybug.
And when you do, it won't be the way you think.
I'm sorry. It's my fault you got akumatized.
No, it's not. I let my own emotions get the better of me.
Besides, it's over now.
But I'm still afraid.
Fear can be a good thing. It teaches us to be cautious and not put ourselves in danger.
But in your case, fear of insects has become a phobia that keeps you from enjoying your life.
That's why we're here with your friends to help you feel better.
Go as far as you want and stop anytime you want, okay?
Do you want to go back out?
Yes.
That's an excellent start, Aglaie.
And now you know no matter how long it takes, you won't be alone to travel your path.
You've found a wonderful vehicle.
Friendship.
Thanks for coming with me and for understanding my need to talk to Dr. Sika.
Of course.
Adrian Agrest?
So what do you need to talk about, Adrian?
There's something strange about my father.