Whoever gets to the temple first win!
What?
Aang, no fair!
Let's get him!
Hurry up!
♪♪ Hi, Nima.
Good morning, Aang.
Oh, hello, Aang.
Oh, perfect timing.
I don't mind giving me a lift.
Gyatso, this isn't the best time.
I'm getting old, you know.
My body doesn't move like it used to.
I'm kind of in the middle of something.
You are so heavy.
Heavy? Me?
I eat nothing but vegetables.
Pie is not a vegetable.
I'm gonna lose the race.
Race? What race?
We finally won!
We won! We won!
Aang, as an air bender, it's important
that you know when to show restraint.
Even if you have the power
to win, you are the Avatar.
A lot of people are going to rely on you.
♪♪ He's gone!
He ran away!
What? I'm here!
Where's the Avatar?
Avatar!
Aang, where are you?
Gyatso, I'm here!
♪♪ I'm right here!
I'm here!
I'm here.
Hi, Momo.
Hi, Appa.
Was I asleep for long?
Ooh! Okay, okay.
I'm awake already.
I know, I know.
We've got a job to finish.
Let's continue our journey.
Back to our old home.
This may not have been our best trip,
but any Airbender relic we
find makes it all worthwhile.
This could be the oldest
piece in our collection.
♪♪ Sonam.
I miss you.
Momo, go outside with Appa.
♪♪ Now!
♪♪ Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
♪♪ Stop.
I don't want to hurt you.
♪♪ Where is it?
No, that's not it.
Where is it?
Hey, those are antiques.
♪♪ Enough!
♪♪ Wait!
I found it!
Sonam, why an after you?
♪♪ ♪♪ Wait!
No, that's 1,000 years old!
Why don't we just talk? Maybe I can help.
We don't need your help, Avatar.
We're done living in a world where benders
have all the power and we have none.
Who are you?
We're the Denied.
The Denied?
Just kill him already!
No! He'll bring the whole place down!
♪♪ You saved me.
Kalik, stop the map! Let's go!
♪♪ ♪♪ Oh, no!
I'm fine.
Momo, I'm fine.
We've got to get to Republic City.
Appa, yip, yip!
♪♪ ♪♪ Water.
Her tribes gather strength from
the moon and flow with the tides.
Earth, a kingdom of unshakable will.
Reliable and strong.
♪♪ Fire.
A nation capable of great
destruction, but also of great warmth.
Air, peaceful nomads with the power of a
hurricane, but the
spirit of a gentle breeze.
For generations, the
Avatar, the one master of
all four elements, kept
the nations in balance.
But when that responsibility
fell to me as a child, I ran away.
I was caught in a deadly storm,
but my Avatar spirit preserved me in a sphere
of energy where I stayed for 100 years.
I woke to discover that
the balance preserved
by the Avatar had been destroyed by war.
The air nomads were gone.
All but one.
Me.
I could no longer run for my
responsibility as the Avatar.
I found allies from every nation.
Benders and non-benders.
Katara taught me how to water bend.
Toph trained me in the
ways of the earthbenders.
Zuko, once my worst enemy,
became my fire bending teacher.
Sokka showed me that bravery is the
most important part of being a leader.
We became a family.
And together, we ended
the Hundred Year War.
Then, we began the hard
work of rebuilding the world.
For so long, the nations
stood apart, alone,
and we all suffered as a result.
But here, on this ancient site,
we created a place where all people are
welcome, bender and non-bender alike,
working together in
peace to build the future.
Though there are still those
who would seek to divide us,
we remain united.
As a council representative,
I am honored to be here today celebrating
the anniversary of Republic City
and the opening of Unity
Tower, a symbol for all people.
♪♪ Yes!
It's the Avatar!
♪♪ Momo!
Appa!
I missed you, too, old friend.
♪♪ Aang!
Katara!
You're hurt.
Take a deep breath.
And exhale.
I've heard the Denied
are growing in numbers,
but they've never done anything like this.
Attacking the Avatar?
Yeah.
They were incredible fighters,
even without bending.
Oops!
Ow!
Breathe through it.
Be honest. You're enjoying this.
Aang, this is serious.
Whatever this map they
took was, if they were willing to
kill the Avatar to get it, what
else are they willing to do?
I don't know.
I'm worried about you.
You're spending more and
more time at the Air Temple, alone.
It's how I hold on to my past.
I know how hard this is for you.
When I was attacked,
all I could think about
was that... this could be it.
I'm the last Airbender.
If I die,
my culture dies with me.
You may be the last Airbender,
but you're not alone.
Aang, none of this would exist without you.
You made the city possible
with your heart and your mind.
Because of you, all of the
nations live here, together.
All except mine.
I know, but the people here
still need your protection.
You're an Airbender,
but you're also the Avatar.
You're right.
Whoever this Sonim person
is, I need to find out more.
♪♪ ♪♪ Aang.
Avatar Roku.
It is good to see you again.
How can I help you?
In your lifetime, did you ever hear of
an ancient Airbender named Sonim?
I have not, but you have
many past lives to call upon.
Perhaps one further back in
the Avatar cycle can help you.
Thank you, Avatar Roku.
-I'm sorry. -I've never heard of Sonim.
-Perhaps earlier. -You must go find him.
Not here. Not here.
[ Indistinct conversation I ♪♪ Um, hello?
Is there anyone here?
Hello?
Two cores upon Avatar Seon's
vast wealth of knowledge.
Oh, hello.
You look like an Avatar from
a time quite distant from mine.
Please, please, tell me about your era.
What are people wearing?
Are sandals still a thing?
Uh, yes.
Why? Why?
After so many years, open toes,
in someone else's crusty cuticles.
Disgusting.
Right.
Anyway, I have come through guidance.
You see, I was attacked.
It was not me, okay? It wasn't me.
I know that.
I think it might have something to
do with an Airbender named Sonim.
Sonim. It sounds familiar.
Sonim. Where have I heard that name before?
Aha! Sonim was the youngest
daughter of the owner of
the possum chicken shop
at the corner marketplace.
Wait. That was my ex, Soniam.
If only she didn't have
those humongous toenails.
Ugh. Disgusting.
This is going nowhere.
Sonim?
Well, thank you for your time.
I must continue my search.
Oh! Sonim!
You're asking about the
legend of the lost Avatar.
Sonim was an Avatar?
Indeed she was.
She was the Avatar in the
golden age of Airbender.
Legend said she had a staff
that could channel the vast energy
of the spirit world, granting
its keeper unlimited power.
Is... Is that even possible?
We'll never know for sure.
Many Avatars have tried
to communicate with her,
but they couldn't.
She disappeared so completely
that it was as if she never existed.
And perhaps it's better that way.
Maybe such a staff was too
dangerous for anyone to possess.
Even the Avatar.
But... But that's exactly
why I need to find it.
The people who attacked
me discovered a map.
It must lead to the staff.
Avatar Shion, please.
You have to tell me where it is.
The legend says that Sonim disappeared
with her staff on the peak of Mount Baihu.
Katara, I'm sorry to leave so suddenly,
but I found out what the Denied are after.
Sonim had a staff of immense power.
And in their hands, it could
be a devastating weapon.
They have a head start.
There's no time to waste.
You take Appa and Momo and
gather up the rest of the team.
We're gonna need some help.
Next on the agenda, a
Fire Nation naval vessel
came into conflict with an extremist
group of non-Benders called the Denied.
They've been robbing
ancient sites... Your Majesty!
An urgent message has
arrived from Republic City.
How impudent.
Can't you see Fire Lord
Zuko is... Chamberlain.
There's only one person
who can send a message
urgent enough to interrupt
the Fire Lord's counsel.
Is it from the Avatar?
Yes, my lord.
Read it to me.
Um...
What are you doing?
Read it quickly.
Uh, y-y-yes, Grand Chamberlain.
Flameo Hartman, house
ruling the Fire Nation.
I hope the boring Chamberlain
you mentioned...
...in your letters isn't still annoying you.
Anywho, to cut to the
chase, I need your help.
Can you please come immediately?
Oh, and don't forget to
bring some firecracker buns.
Allow me to present Sokka Cycle.
Flames launch you into the sky where
you can drop water bombs on your enemies.
Then skis pop out to
help you stick the landing.
Pretty great, right?
Eh, boring.
Why would you need a sled
when you can just water bend?
Oh, oh, oh, like me, like me!
Whee!
Keep in mind, there's still plenty
of folks like me who can't bend.
Why would Avatar Aang
partner with a non-bender?
Ugh. Why?
I'll tell you why.
I saved him from the iceberg.
My boomerang flew by his side while I
carried away enemies with my trusty blade.
I even took down the whole
Fire Nation airship armada.
And on top of all that, I
was more popular than him.
You're such a liar, Sokka.
It's from the Avatar.
Wow!
Really?
Oh, so now you think I'm cool?
All right, metalbenders.
Let's see if any of you tenderfoots
can at least make me use my hands.
I'm still the greatest
earth bender in the world!
And I'm bored.
M-Master Toph, there's a bird on your head.
And?
It looks like it has a message.
Read.
Uh, it's from Avatar Aang.
He needs your help.
It's the Denied?
Where is he?
Mount Bihu.
♪♪ ♪♪ No, no, no!
No.
I love that hat.
♪♪ ♪♪ Sonam?
Could that be you?
♪♪ ♪♪ Who are you?
How did he hold up an entire mountain?
His chi is strong, like
nothing I've ever felt.
Hey, Avatar, you think this guy beat
your record for longest frozen air bender?
Yeah.
How long do you think he was in that ice?
I don't know. His tattoos look ancient.
He's been in there a long time.
He smells good for an old guy.
Ew.
What? My senses tell me
this guy is pretty attractive.
-Tah! -Someone else confirmed.
This is serious.
What does "attractive" even mean?
Just give me a straight confirmation.
Is he attractive?
He's very attractive.
Huh?
What? He is.
It's all in the bone structure.
No.
No!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey.
Easy. You're safe.
♪♪ Earthbender!
No, no, no. We're all friends here.
It's okay.
Someone woke up on the
wrong side of the mountain.
Where is she?
Where is Avatar Sonim?
You knew Sonim?
Who are you?
I don't know how to explain it, but
you've been asleep for a long time.
I'm the Avatar now.
I'm Aang.
If you're the Avatar, then Sonim.
Well, Sonim might be
long gone, but on the
bright side, you woke
up at the perfect time.
Everyone will be amazed
to see another Airbender.
Aang's not the last one anymore.
What do you mean, "last"?
Oh.
The Air Nomads.
They've been wiped out.
There's only me.
No.
Sonim Staff, do you have it?
It's our only hope now.
What do you mean?
I thought it was a weapon.
The staff is no weapon.
It is a gift.
With it, Sonim was able to channel
the vast power of the spirit world.
It was this power that
allowed Jirana to flourish.
The greatest city in the
world, an Air Nomad utopia,
where Sonim presided
over a golden age of balance,
and where I devoted
my life to serving her.
In return, she raised me
up and used her staff to give
me, a lowly non-Bender,
the power to bend the air.
I was the first, but I would not be the last.
She filled the skies with
Airbenders, and we flew
by her side, spreading
peace across the world.
Aang, are you okay?
Sonim used the staff to
give people Airbending.
If we found it,
I could bring Airbending back to the world.
This is incredible.
There haven't been Airbenders
for over a hundred years.
This is everything you ever wanted, Aang.
We could heal the greatest atrocity
my nation committed in the war.
This could be the final
step to rebuilding the world.
Not if the Denied get there first.
They have the map.
Who are the Denied?
A group of violent non-Benders.
They... they must be after the staff
to give themselves Airbending.
Then there's no time to waste.
There's only one place it could be.
Ready your bison.
We'll need to travel
across the endless ocean.
On the other side of the world?
But there's nothing out there.
There's an island.
The journey will not be easy,
but we can make it.
Then let's get going.
The skies are no place for a water child.
Water child?
Um, I know you just
woke up after thousands
of years, but we do
these things together.
Trust me, we're stronger this way.
Welcome to Team Avatar.
What's your name?
Taga. My name is Taga.
Just think of it as a big metal air bison.
We will travel ancient
paths through the sky,
ones that our people
learned by following the great
air bison herds that long
ago taught us Airbending.
Air currents known only to us,
encircling the great sphere of existence,
allowing us to travel where we wish,
giving us our name, the Air Nomads.
What's he doing?
He's really feeling that air.
He's navigating by instinct.
What if his instincts are just wrong?
Who needs instincts when
you've got muscles like that?
Or what if his brain is
messed up from being frozen?
Like me?
Uh, no, no!
He was frozen for 5,000 years, okay?
You were frozen for, what, 100?
Okay, that's nothing.
Your brain is... fresh.
Maybe he is a little
old-fashioned, but look at him.
He's so in tune with his
element, he can travel
across the entire ocean
with no map, no instruments.
There's so much I can learn from him.
I'd give anything to be able
to see my air bison again.
And now, to see only one remains.
You said our people were
wiped out, yet you survived.
How?
I had just found out I was the Avatar,
but the responsibility... it was too much.
So I ran away.
And while I was gone,
the Fire Nation attacked.
They were looking for me.
If... If I'd just been there...
Sonam would say,
"Air nomads are formed from the mist.
We walk the world for a moment in time.
Then we return to the eternal wind.
"♪♪
Monkiatsu taught me that.
We carry the same weight,
a grief no one else could
possibly comprehend.
But you and I can heal the past.
Let me show you how powerful our element
can be when airbenders work together.
♪♪ Aah!
What are you doing?!
Aah!
This is how Sonam taught me!
Feel the energy that tethers us.
The bond between us... can you feel it?
Use it!
This is amazing!
Yes, I am!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, yeah!
Human boomerang!
He's actually flying.
So are we.
Whoa! That's my best friend!
That's my best friend!
No, you throw me!
I had no idea this was possible!
This is only the beginning.
I can't believe it.
Airbenders will fill the sky again.
We have been given a great gift...
the chance to redeem ourselves.
You were destined to find
me on that mountain, Aang.
How did you end up there?
The earthbenders had attacked Tirana.
Sonam and I fought
fearlessly, side by side.
We drove them back to Mount Bahu,
and that's the last I remember.
She must have saved your life.
Only an Avatar could
have put you in that sphere.
Aang, can I ask you something?
Of course.
If the Fire Nation
destroyed the Air Nomads,
how can you suffer the
presence of the Fire Lord?
Zuko is a friend and an ally.
He turned against his own
father to help me end the war.
Yet he wears the crown himself now.
Fire, by its nature, burns, Aang.
Our kind have always suffered
at the hands of the other elements.
That's why we built Republic City...
to show the world that
if we listen to each other,
we can all live together in peace.
And once we bring back
airbenders, it'll be complete.
When everyone stuck to their own,
the whole world was nearly torn apart.
And besides, Katara, Sokka, Zuko, Toph,
they're my family now.
I want to live in a world
where we can all be together.
You remind me so much of Sonam.
It's the Avatar.
And this time, he's got
his friends with them.
That's the Fire Lord's airship.
How'd they get ahead of us?
They don't even have the map.
We can't risk him getting to the staff first.
Kill him.
But he spared our lives.
And how many Countless were killed in
the hundred years waiting for his return?
Where was he when
your family was wiped out?
If we want anything to change, we
need what the benders have... power.
Fire!
It's the Denied.
Uh, we are definitely under attack.
Turn up your spreads.
Is he crushing the ship?
Taga?
Taga, stop!
We're here.
The Immortal Storm.
Oh, no.
There has to be another way around.
No. Together, you and I
can clear a path for the ship.
But we have to go now.
Aang, trust me.
Uh, maybe now's a good time to turn back.
I don't think that's an option anymore.
Where are they going?
The engine's out.
We're losing air pressure.
Katara, come with me.
What about me?
Take the wheel.
What? I've only ever
crashed Fire Nation airships.
Okay, let's see. Here's our rudder.
This is the elevator. There's our ballast.
And there's the giant tornado
that's going to kill us all.
Follow my lead.
Work with me.
Just like I showed you.
We can heart it.
Yes! That's it, Aang. Keep going.
Got it.
Zuko! Zuko!
Aang and Taga are destroying
tornadoes, but there's too many!
And they're everywhere!
Just steer the ship. Don't lose Aang.
It's not that easy, especially
when everything is sideways.
Okay, left!
I did it!
Right!
Oh no, we're falling behind!
I'm losing sight of them.
We have to go back.
Trust in your friends. They won't
make it if we don't clear a path.
Zuko, we're going to crash!
Zuko, we're going to crash into the sea!
When I give you the signal,
pull the lever next to the wheel.
We're going to crash! We're going to crash!
Katara?
Give me the signal! Give me the signal!
Whoa!
Sokka, now!
Here we go!
Katara! We did it!
What were you thinking?
I was clearing the
tornadoes to make a path.
The ship almost crashed, Aang.
We could have died.
And what if you got yourself killed?
You're the Avatar.
This is too risky.
We need to turn back now.
No! We're almost there.
We just need to get
to the eye of the storm.
Aang, no!
We need to get to the eye of the storm.
Aang, we need to get
to the eye of the storm.
Aang, no! This is too dangerous.
The staff is out there.
They denied her after it.
Do you really believe that they
could make it through the storm?
We're nearly there.
That staff can bring back my people.
I understand how much you want that, but...
You don't understand. None of you do.
Aang... We push forward.
If we generate enough air,
we can push our way through.
We can push our way through.
Aang!
We're alive?
We made it through. Thank you, Taga.
It was you, Aang.
We're here because of you.
Yeah, we're having a good time, too.
You could have told us we were
flying into the Immortal Storm.
I know it was dangerous,
but we had to risk it.
We? I don't remember
when we took a vote on that.
There wasn't time. I had to make a call.
Friends, please, don't blame Aang.
This is all my fault.
I knew this would be difficult.
But Aang believed in
your strength as a team.
And I'm honored to be a part of it.
I forgive you, Taga.
Everyone, look.
These islands... they were... lion turtles.
Whoa!
It's beautiful.
Long before my time, the lion turtles
granted the gift of bending to humans.
These are their final resting grounds.
This is where Sonim
came to learn their ways.
I am certain that she left her staff here.
Where should we start looking?
Aang, you must connect with her.
But no one can connect with Sonim.
The spiritual power of the lion
turtles is still concentrated here.
Let it guide you.
We'll set out immediately.
Actually, Taga, we could
really use your help here.
If the denied are close
behind, we need to be ready.
Yeah, and we're gonna need more
than Toph's metal bending to fix this.
My bending got us through that storm.
What did you do?
Steered with his feet.
Repairs can wait. Aang needs me.
Taga, please, stay and help my friends.
I'll be okay on my own.
As you wish.
We will begin repairs for our voyage home.
Everyone, I know I've asked
a lot of you on this journey.
But we're about to accomplish
something that will change the world.
Let it guide you.
Sonam?
Oh, this is turning out
to be a nice little vacation.
Aside from all the people trying
to kill us, and the tornadoes.
Um, we're supposed to be fixing the ship?
You're doing great, buddy.
Has anyone seen Taga?
Yes, we've all seen Taga. He's so gorgeous.
Geez, I get it.
Oh, I see what you mean.
He wandered off that way.
No, maybe that way?
Taga?
Where are you going?
Aang needs to be protected.
I agree.
I know my ways may seem unusual to you.
But I assure you, everything
I do, I do for Aang.
For Aang? Or for the staff?
You have no idea all that we've lost.
You've never known a world with airbenders.
I know Aang.
He may be the last of his kind.
But he's the reason this world knows peace.
His values as an air nomad
have brought balance to chaos.
It's because of Aang
that the Water Tribes,
Earth Kingdom, and Fire
Nation now work together.
Striving for harmony.
A peace we once thought unattainable.
You speak of peace.
There will never be
peace among the elements.
There never was.
Your precious Republic
City is built on lies.
It's built on hope.
Do you have hope, Taga?
Saving my people requires
more than just hope.
It requires sacrifice.
I saw you try to crush
the denied's airships.
You were ready to kill them.
I know what kind of air bender Aang is.
But what kind of air bender are you?
Aang did well getting us here.
There is great strength in
him, but weakness as well.
Weakness?
Yes, you.
What the hog monkey?
He trusted you.
No.
Brother.
Taga, it's real.
We can finally bring back air bending.
Let's go tell the others.
We can do this, me and you.
I can't do this without my friends.
Earth killed my people, fire killed yours.
The staff is the only way we
can create a new air empire.
One capable of defending itself.
No, we can build a new future, Taga.
But it has to be for everyone.
The staff doesn't belong to everyone.
It belongs to us.
What have you done?
As long as they were around, you
always put them ahead of our people.
Don't you see?
This is how we redeem ourselves.
It doesn't matter that you ran then.
As long as you stand with me now.
Aang, listen to me.
Katara.
It's the only way.
You're a traitor to your own.
Just like Sono.
I wanted to do this with you by my side.
But if I must build a new
air empire alone, so be it.
There's no way in.
We have to turn back.
No, we keep trying to push through.
Sono's staff.
Denied.
The Avatar is dead.
If you wish to build a new world where
you have the power, I can give it to you.
Appa.
Katara.
They're gone.
It's all my fault.
It's always been my fault.
Ever since I ran away.
No Avatar has ever fallen into such
shame as to join me here in my sorrow.
Why do you grieve so, friend?
Avatar Sono?
Taga murdered my friends.
And now he has the staff.
Taga.
No.
I stopped him.
I hit the staff.
What have you done?
You're the one who gave him air bending.
How could you give power to a monster?
The Taga I gave bending
to was a different man.
It was a different time.
The airbenders were the
peacekeepers of the four elements.
We used our power to mediate
all conflict with nonviolence.
But we were the fewest in numbers.
For many years, we existed in a
beautiful balance of great prosperity.
But the world began to shift.
The earthbenders formed their own kingdom,
separating from the other elemental tribes.
The balance of the world was at risk.
It was my duty to act.
So I learned how to
channel the energy of the
spirit world just as the lion turtles did.
To give people the power of air bending.
My most devout pupil,
Taga, was the first to receive it.
I sent my new peacekeepers out
to help calm the growing unrest.
But they were not prepared for the
brutality of the new earth kingdom.
Taga watched as his brothers
and sisters were all slaughtered.
His heart darkened by the violence of war.
He now saw everyone who
wasn't an air nomad as the enemy.
Taga begged me to
use the staff to create an
army and to kill all
who would do us harm.
I refused.
So he stole it.
When he connected
the staff to the temple,
his energy was so
corrupted by grief and rage
that the power of the
spirit world consumed him.
Taga became something more
than human, too powerful to kill.
It took all my energy
to finally trap him high
above the clouds and
no one would find him.
I reclaimed the staff,
but I was fatally wounded.
Before the earth kingdom
could invade Jirana, I
sent the remaining air
nomads into the mountains.
And I hid my temple in the spirit world
where no one could access its power.
Then I locked the staff away
where only the avatar could find it.
I died hoping that one day
another avatar would create
more airbenders and
restore balance to this world.
And that avatar is you, Aang.
You have to get my staff before
Taga connects it to the temple.
There's still time.
Don't let my regret become yours.
My friends and I fought
hard for this peace.
I won't let him start another war.
Help me find a way back.
Soto?
What's happening?
No! No! Please! I have to fix this!
This can't be it! I can't die yet!
Please! Not yet! No!
- Aang? - Katara?
Come on, Aang! Come on!
Aang! Move up! Aang!
- Katara. - I was so worried.
Aang. Sokka.
I knew you'd pull through, buddy.
- Hey, Aang. - Zuko.
- Momo. - Welcome back, Twinkle Toes.
Toph, you're okay.
I thought you were all dead.
We were, but Katara saved us.
The spiritual power of these waters
strengthened my healing abilities.
You're incredible, Katara.
Where's Appa?
Taga must have taken him.
I'm sorry.
No.
I can't believe I trusted him.
We'll get through this.
So, let me get this straight.
He's pulling Sonam's temple out of
the spirit world to gain unlimited power?
And let me guess, you want us to stop him?
Sure. Only problem is your air bro
crushed our ship and stole your bison.
Also, there's a massive
typhoon surrounding us!
I don't say this very
often, but Sokka's right.
- Thank you. - Yep, we're stuck.
And there aren't enough lion turtles
for all of us to have our own island.
So, I'm calling this one.
I'm naming him Snappy.
- Aw, Snappy is the best one. - I know.
We may not know where
Taga is, but we know
what he's looking for is in the spirit world.
And lucky for us, we're stuck in the most
spiritually charged place on the planet.
So, I may be able to open a portal to get
us there, if I can summon an old friend.
Wow. The ocean spirit.
This portal smells an
awful lot like the fish market.
I'm gonna go check on Snappy.
Face your death with honor.
I'm sorry. I know I got us into
this, but I promise you I'll fix it.
We'll fix it.
Together.
We're gonna die! We're gonna die!
What? Where's my power pony?
Were my hands always this small?
It's baby Tuff! Baby Tuff!
What the hog monkey?
Grand Grand?
That's your sister, you weak head!
Give me Tuff. There, there, Tuff.
Oh no, Zuko!
What happened to your beautiful face?
You look like a dried sea squid.
No, Zuko!
What's going on here?
The spirit world is out of balance.
And so are we.
That's gotta be Taga.
Oh no!
He's pulling Sonim's
temple into our world!
We're running out of time!
Pretty good landing.
Whoa! Humans! I love humans!
Two brothers, their little
sister, and an ugly couple.
Not a couple!
Whoa! Looks like I touched a nerve.
Oh, look at this one! Hello!
Tuff! No! Bad Tuff!
We don't bite strangers.
Great spirit! Excuse me, did you
just come from that temple in the sky?
I certainly did.
It was my favorite hidey hole.
Until that dark, yucky energy
started corrupting this whole place.
Please, we need your help getting up there.
It's my duty to stop this.
I'm the Avatar.
Ooh! The Avatar!
Let me have a squiz at you.
Okay, now with this eye.
And this eye.
Ooh, don't forget this eye.
Can we hurry it up?
I need to have a squiz.
Sniff check!
Ooh, that's Avatar material right there.
Yes, it is. Oh!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
It appears the universe has brought
us together for a very important mission.
To flee!
And be alive!
Wait! Come back!
We're going the wrong way!
Stop!
Please, great spirit, both
of our worlds are in danger.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I am not going back up there.
Hmm, well, when you put it like
that, it does make more sense.
Upon reflection, I've decided I shall
help you and your human-y friends.
What did he say?
Nice work, mama.
Alright, in you go.
By the way, no eating anything you find
in my teeth, as I'm saving that for later.
Ready, set, get steady and rest.
One and the two and
the you know what to do.
Bluff!
I know we haven't known each
other very long, but I love you!
You don't have to say it back.
Hey! You got your hair back!
Why are my eyes cheery? Was I crying?
No way! Look!
What? What is it?
It's Republic City.
We can't let him destroy
everything we've built.
We won't.
Boomerang!
Give me the staff, Taga!
I see I underestimated you, Avatar.
Your friends are stronger than I thought.
But you're too late.
The Denied.
You see, I did what you wanted, Aang.
I returned air bending to the world.
What's the plan?
We'll deal with the Denied.
You have to get the staff.
I will rebuild Geronimo and the ruins
of our enemies, just as they did on ours.
A new air empire will rise. Kill them all.
We have to get these people out of here.
Whoa!
Oh, yeah.
Taga! Give it to me!
This isn't the way. We can use
the staff to bring back the balance.
Peace!
You care so much about your
ideals that you'd let your people die!
I will do anything to
make sure they survive!
You hear that now?
My cabbages! My cabbages!
Don't do this.
You have the power now.
You can decide how to use it.
I'm not like you.
The world hasn't been good to me.
The world is what we make it.
Get away from her!
Taga! Stop!
You betrayed me! You betrayed our culture!
I gave you every chance to see the truth!
Can you be in the Fire Nation?
I'm fighting for the peace of all nations.
Big talk from someone who sits
on a throne built on a century of war!
I'm still the greatest
earth bender in the world!
Oh no! I'm out of water!
We got ya!
And there's no Avatar here to save you.
Suck a cycle!
Let's see if your fancy new bending can
beat some good ol' non-bending know-how!
He comes away!
You just got denied!
Let's go!
Good luck saving your city!
We have to save as many people as we can!
I know your pain.
I know what you've been through.
You don't know.
I watched as all of my brothers
and sisters were slaughtered.
And the Fire Nation burned
the Air Nomads to ash!
Where were you?
You ran!
Taga!
No!
The full power of the Spirit
World flows through me!
This is what strength looks like!
No!
You should've run away like you
did all those years ago, little Avatar.
I... won't... run.
Then at least you'll die knowing
you're not the last Airbender!
No!
We could've been brothers!
We could've done this together!
It didn't have to end like this!
It's Aang. He's got the staff!
Yeah! Kick his butt, Mega Aang!
No! Something's wrong!
The power is corrupting him!
No!
I dreamt of bringing the Air Nomads
back to the world as peacekeepers.
They could've been a beacon
of light for the world to follow.
But you ruined it!
You twisted my grave into a nightmare!
Finally.
You have the power the Air Nomads need.
Maybe there is hope for you after all.
Do it! Use the staff! Show me you have
the strength to bring our people back!
Do it!
Aang...
You will do so many
great things as the Avatar.
But you must be prepared to
do what frightens you the most.
Your people, your home,
we are always with you.
No!
No! My power!
No. No!
You fool! Why? Why did you break it?
We could've fixed everything.
We can't erase the pain of the past.
We couldn't save them.
But it's our duty to protect our people.
Not at the cost of betraying
everything they stood for.
No.
It's time to let go.
You have to forgive yourself.
I have to forgive myself too.
Air Nomads are formed from the best.
We walk the world for a moment in time.
Then we return to the eternal wind.
Aang!
Hey, Katara.
Hey, Aang.
Seriously?
You do realize you're falling, right?
Hey, if you ever get
tired of relying on Appa,
I can hook you up with
one of these babies.
I'll give you the best friend discount!
I don't know if
air bending will ever return.
But I know now that the
true power of the Air Nomads
was never their bending.
It was their values.
And that's a power I can pass on to others.
Avatar Aang, you are the true
embodiment of the Air Nomads.
Thank you for giving up
the power that I could not.
You give me hope for
the future of our culture.
It's amazing, isn't it?
The first new air temple in centuries.
Republic City is finally complete.
A city for all nations,
just like you promised.
I never could have done
this without you, Katara.
Hey, everybody.
Sorry I kept you all waiting.
Are you ready for our big trip?
As my new acolytes,
you'll be helping me preserve
our culture for future generations.
So, who wants to search for artifacts
at an ancient abandoned temple?
Yay.
I'm only going to make sure you don't try
to release another beefy old air bender.
Yeah, I'm done with bad boys.
Avatar Sonam told me about this place,
so it's very possible that no one's
been here in hundreds of years.
Oh, is this an air bender relic?
I think that's just a rock.
But I love the enthusiasm.
Oh.
Keep your eyes open.
You never know what we might discover here.
Oh.
I thought they were extinct.
I can't believe it.
The original airbenders.
Oh, can I have one?
Appa, you get it.