Okay, in algebraic terms, a squared plus b
squared equals c squared, where c is the
hypotenuse, while a and b are the sides
of the triangle.
Got it?
Dash, you have to focus!
I'm doing a thesis on tutoring the untutorable,
and you're disproving my thesis that nobody's untutorable!
You know, you're beautiful when you use the
word uh that...
Whatever that word is.
Hey, Jazz!
Dash!
What are you doing here?
Watch it, Fentonowski!
I'm sorry, I was just, uh, passing through.
Now that Twinkie's out of the way, you're
coming to my party Saturday, right?
It'll be a chance for you to see
me in my rightful setting, King of Casper
High!
And a great place to work on my
thesis on the effects of being mean to
my brother and then asking me out!
Hmm...
I'll go, on one condition.
Hey, Danny!
Check out my latest innovation in ghost-grabbing
technology, the Ghost Weasel!
It collects ambient ghost energy and shoots it
into the ghost zone.
Does it work?
Why wouldn't it?
Only one way to find out.
Darn it!
Better get the Fenton on logic.
Dad, couldn't you just throw it into...
Remorse!
Child!
You have freed me!
Technus, Ghost Master of Science and Electrical Technology!
Oh, no you don't!
You're not going to use the technology in
this lab to take over the world!
What?
That's a great idea!
Have you ever considered tutoring?
You know what?
I've already been dumped on once in my
own house.
And that's enough for one day!
Danny, I'm coming back!
And I can't wait to see the lab
looking exactly as I left it!
Yep, perfect!
DEHŞET SAÇAN İKİNCİ EL PAZARI
So, Saturday night plans.
I say we hit the amusement park.
I hear the new roller coaster has a
free fall that'll take three years off your
life expectancy.
No way.
It costs 40 bucks just to get in
there.
Not to mention food and stuff.
Hey, if you're tapped out, I can lend
you the cash.
Lend means repay and repay is out of
my reach.
Right, Danny?
Danny?
Hello?
Great.
It's the hottest party of the whole school
year and Paulina's going and I'm not, again.
I don't understand what you see in her.
Are you kidding?
She's only, like, perfectly flawless.
Okay, um, let me get the mighty meaty
cheesy melt.
Um, how meaty is that?
That would be mighty meaty.
Well, can I get it a mite less
meaty?
That's one mighty mini meaty cheesy melt.
You're right.
She's a goddess.
Why don't we get invited to the really
cool parties?
We've got style, charm, good looks.
At least I do, anyway.
Dream on.
On the social circuit, we're as invisible as
Danny in his ghost mode.
Not that it'll matter five years from now,
but we love each other, right?
Here.
Your sister made me invite you.
Just you.
Show up, shut it, go home, and nobody
gets hurt.
Hey, Danny.
What's up, Finn?
Party!
See you Saturday, Danny.
I'm...
I'm invited.
I've arrived!
Swell.
Send us a postcard from Popularityville.
I will!
Seriously, Danny.
Ever since you got that invitation, you're all
about the in-crowd.
Come on, Doc.
That's ridiculous.
Juan!
Looking good!
Fenton Meister!
Woo-hoo!
He's right, Danny.
It's like...
Hey, Fenton!
Come here!
We're not even here.
If you're coming to my party, you have
to look the part.
This is what we're all wearing Saturday.
Very high-end, very hip, very dash.
You do have one, right?
Huh?
Yeah.
Oh, sure.
I have two.
That's how hip and high-end I am.
Well, wear one.
I might have had to invite you, but
if you embarrass me, your sister's gonna be
doing her thesis on your bruises.
Oh, man.
This must cost a fortune.
Where am I gonna get the money by
Saturday?
You know, I almost hate to offer...
Hey, Danny!
You wanna hear my new CD?
It's really crunk!
Is crunk good?
It's Paulina.
Crunk's good.
Be right there!
Okay, this is getting really annoying.
Mom, what are you doing?
What are you making?
Hot dogs!
We invented a way to cook them ten
times faster than a microwave.
Great.
You figured out how to put the frank
back in Frankenstein.
Hey, Dad, can you spare me some cash?
I need to buy some clothes for Saturday.
Danny, Danny, Danny.
You know, as inventors, your mother and I
have plenty of money.
But as parents, we understand that you should
understand the value of money.
You want money, you gotta earn it.
You mean, get a job?
That or sell something, like your old comic
books or some other junk you don't need.
Uh, speaking of which, that junk from the
ghost weasel explosion needs to go in the
shed, if there's room.
That old barn hasn't been cleaned up in
years.
This is not junk!
Every single item in this box is of
vital importance to me.
Do you even know what this is?
Not a clue, but I know it's important,
so it's off to the shed.
You know, maybe I should get rid of
this junk.
Ah, well, that's a job for another day.
Saturday's another day.
It's a perfectly good vacuum motor, Mr. Lancer.
Only used once.
Ten bucks.
Looks to be in fine shape.
This should fix my hair hornet very nicely.
Hair hornet?
The crazy vacuum cleaner slash hair clipper they
sell on TV?
Don't you need hair for that?
Good one, Mr. Foley.
I'll remember that on Monday, when I'm grading
tests.
Just sold a toaster.
You know, I'm surprised your dad's letting you
sell off all his stuff.
He's such a pack rat.
Yeah, well, he's been planning on getting rid
of this junk for a long time.
He won't even miss it.
I hope.
I'm pleased with the turnout today.
We're doing a really brisk business.
I'm still 20 bucks short of what I
need for those sweats.
You're still welcome to hang with us tonight.
Mega Movie Marathon at my place.
Your place?
Wow.
You never invited us to your place before.
That's because we're usually fighting ghosts with you.
I figured it's time...
Hey, Fantina!
...for you to totally ignore me for about
the billionth time this week.
Jazz has given me so much extra schoolwork
that my computer's overloaded.
Got anything to make it work?
Oh, sure do.
This motherboard and this portal's XL operating system
will make it work like it's brand new.
Twenty bucks takes it all, and I'll even
throw in this upgrade disk.
Done.
See you tonight.
And just because I can't believe I'm saying
it, I will say it again.
See you tonight.
Twenty bucks!
I'm in!
Oh, geez.
I better get to the mall before the
shop's closed.
You guys don't mind cleaning up for me,
do ya?
Great.
See ya!
So now we're his clean-up crew, too?
See you tonight.
Right.
That's two medium, one pepperoni, and one veggie.
Put it on my tab.
Hey, Tucker!
I hope they hustle.
I'm starved.
Here's your pizza, Sam.
Thanks, Nate.
Ten bucks.
Thanks, Sam.
You tip the guy a ten spot?
Whoops.
Sorry.
I thought it was a one.
Come on.
We're watching movies downstairs.
This is your downstairs?
What?
Too much?
Uh-huh.
I know.
I should've told you and Danny this a
long time ago, but my family's kinda filthy
rich.
Weird, huh?
Whoa.
Time out.
You're loaded?
My great-granddad Izzy was an inventor.
He invented that machine that twirls cellophane around
deli toothpicks.
You're the deli toothpick cellophane-twirling heiress?
No way!
Look, if this is too much for you,
we can do something else.
Are you kidding?
I can't think of a better way to
spend a Saturday night than with a back
-shaving jamboree.
Ooh!
Popularity, here I come!
Way too young to shave!
Going ghost!
Okay, it's a haircut, not a head cut!
Ah!
Huh?
I know I should be concerned, and I
will be.
Right after the party.
Tucker, are we watching movies or not?
Okay, okay.
Just a few more questions.
Could you buy a plane?
Yep.
A yacht?
Um, a bowling alley?
Nope.
There's no place to put a second one.
Yippee!
Boobies hot tonight!
That's weird, because you don't smell stinking rich.
Will you stop it?
That's the whole reason I didn't tell anybody.
But I don't get it.
With all this money, why do you hang
out with me and Danny?
If you flash a little of that bling
-bling, you'd be Miss Popularity.
I don't need popularity, Tucker.
Especially not if I have to buy it.
You should tell that to Danny.
Can you believe people actually spent good money
on that old junk from his parents' shed?
Well, I did snag this really cool remote
for three bucks.
And he did give Dash a pretty good
deal on the computer stuff.
Maybe Fenton's not such a loser after all!
As if.
But this thing runs like a race car!
Whoa!
Getting late!
Better shower and change before the early birds
show up!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Great.
Leftovers.
Well?
Is it the bomb?
Is it fresh?
Is it stupid?
With an O-O.
Oh, it's stupid.
I'll give you that.
You'll change your tune when you see me
at the party.
When are you changing?
Not changing.
Not going.
What?
You're the only reason Dash invited me!
Not caring.
Conrad!
And not staying.
Somebody's raided the junk shed while we were
away.
Danny, did you see anything?
Uh, no, no.
Not a thing.
But we should compare notes once I get
home from the party.
Bye!
Good plan, son.
In the meantime, I'd better secure the lab.
Cover me, boys.
Serpentine!
Okay, this is it.
Don't screw it up.
Look out, world.
Here comes Danny Fenton.
Uh, Dash?
Oh, right, right.
You're not really part of my posse, so
you didn't get the e-mail.
You see, after buying that computer stuff, I
didn't have enough money to buy the sweatsuit,
so I changed the dress code to Loser
Chic.
Oh, swell.
You like it?
It's so horrible, it's cool.
Who dressed you, your mom?
Uh...
Yes, it is time!
Calling all mechanized spirits, come to me, my
minions!
It is time to fulfill my destiny!
Tucker, if you want to watch a part
over again, could you please tell me first?
Me?
You're the one messing with the remote.
I'm not squirting away to the fridge, but
do all your remotes do that?
No.
Well, my toaster does, but it's from Denmark.
That stuff Danny was selling must have been
contaminated with ghost stuff!
What?
Looks bad.
Probably a job for Danny Phantom.
Probably.
And if I wasn't so mad at him,
I'd probably care that it's going to interrupt
his big jock party.
Shall we?
Hi, I'm Danny.
Do you guys...
Hey, aren't you in my fifth period?
What am I doing?
These people aren't my friends.
Even if they all look like them.
Man, I wish Tucker and Sam were here.
It's lonely being popular.
That's odd.
I am Atlas, master of all things mechanical!
And once I complete my construction, you will
all succumb to my power!
To my awesome power!
What is wrong with me?
The upgrade.
Dash still hasn't upgraded the software.
Oh, no.
You're not getting that upgrade disk and making
yourself more powerful.
What?
Another great idea!
To heck with tutoring!
You should be a teacher!
Ghost toast?
Jeez, how many letter jackets does one guy
need?
And these?
I don't even want to know.
You are a formidable opponent, but a little
wet behind the ears.
Perhaps you could use a little drying off?
Ugh.
Fenton, you're a dead man!
Sam, I got the fit and thermies.
You know, Danny's really got to start carrying
this in some sort of lunchbox.
Everything is gravitating here to Dash's house.
Looks like whatever fun Danny's having will be
coming to an end soon.
Hi, Sam.
Hi, Tuck.
Glad you could make it.
I am Tetanus, master of technology and destroyer
of worlds!
Behold my awesome electronic fury!
Hold your daddy!
Guys, help!
Come on, guys!
Guys, come on!
Seriously!
I'm sorry I chose hanging with the popular
kids over you guys.
It was stupid and shallow, and I'll never
do it again!
How can we be of assistance?
He's running an old version of Portal's XL.
That piece of vaporware?
It's the worst software ever.
Keep him busy.
I think I know how you can beat
him.
That I can do.
Get back, you hunk of my dad's junk!
Could mere junk do this?
Give me that!
Tucker!
Anytime!
I'm trying, I'm trying!
What's wrong?
I'm trying to bypass the program, but I
can't.
He must have upgraded.
What do we do?
We need the latest version of Portal's XL.
But where are we going to get it
this time of night?
Leave it to me.
Guys!
Here you go, Sam.
Thanks, Tracy.
Wow, you have access to the latest technology
after hours?
Yep.
What else can you do after hours?
Just sign the voucher, sir.
Uh, excuse me, I'm Sam.
I don't believe I caught your name.
Perhaps you should scream it really loud and
shout out your motive.
Hello, I am Technus, manipulator of machines, lord
of all gadgetry, wizard of integrated psychiatry.
Go on, isn't there more you'd like to
tell me?
Oh, yes.
I am also master of all...
Oh, what's happening?
Portal's XL is happening.
Everybody knows that every new version of Portal's
XL has a gigantic hole in its security
system.
What?
No!
Process this!
Wait!
That doesn't go there!
And for my final trick...
Nice going, Tuck.
Don't thank me, thank lousy software.
So, what's the damage from this weekend?
Did you get in trouble for taking your
folk's stuff?
Not really.
I hauled it all back to the shed
yesterday while they were out.
My dad's checking every piece for government surveillance
devices.
Sounds like you got off pretty easily.
Well, I do have to return those stupid
sweats so I can refund everybody's money.
And I still feel terrible about the way
I treated you guys.
Of all people, I should know how it
feels to be invisible.
So, would you say you've learned a lesson
from all this?
Funtime!
Yep, that one person's trash is another person's
revenge.