So, why exactly are we breaking our backs here, Sam?
Frogs rights.
We have to stop dissecting frogs in our school biology labs.
And at today's assembly, I'm going to demonstrate a humane alternative.
I can't believe it's not a frog could ever?
Please remove my detachable three-chambered hut!
Oh, great. Him again.
I am the backstoast!
And I will have my corrugated cardboard benches!
Gross!
If you guys get to the assembly, I'll get this moron sealed up tight.
Huh. Maybe Sam has a point.
Oops.
Trimble before the bite of the box ghost!
As you are devoured by...
Uh... Oh, yeah.
Costumes and props from the Broadway classic, my fair lady!
Fellow students, something sick and disgusting is taking place right here in our school.
And I'm about to show you what it is!
Ah!
Whoa! Take it off!
No, seriously. You should take it off. That's weird.
37.1
KİŞİLİK BÖLÜNMESİ
Thanks to your little dress-up parade, my save at Frog's presentation was a total bust!
And speaking of bust, did you see Danny in that bra?
Puse is not your color, pal.
Yeah, and now because of that idiot box goes trash, my locker has been assigned a new one.
Locker 724.
Guys, what's wrong?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
Or something really scary that we don't see every single day.
Hello, Locker 724?
How do you not know the legend of Locker 724?
What's the big deal with 724?
You left something behind, Phantom!
Let's see if it fits in your new locker with you inside!
I was going to tell you the locker was cursed, but I think you figured that out.
I'll show you a curse.
Cover me.
Danny!
Relax, Sam!
It's about time to use that Phantom advantage for some ghostly get-back!
Bullies!
So, Danny, what's this I hear about you getting a new locker?
Oh, uh, no big deal, really.
Nothing for you and Mom to get obsessive about.
Why?
Is it haunted?
Don't worry, son. You'll barely even notice us while we're sticking out that locker during normal school hours.
What?
No!
Danny's at a very critical stage in the development of his peer groups.
He's already considered a clumsy nerd.
The last thing he needs is you two confirming it.
Nice defense, jazz.
Total confidence builder.
And the best part is, thanks to the new Ghost Clubs, when that ghost comes out of that locker,
I can spar with it mono a ghost.
Don't worry, maybe girls will talk to you in college.
Hey, tell me the two, uh, nice shake-o. Does it remove air wax, too?
Go on!
I'm so fascinated by AV equipment.
Can you show me how it works?
Bullies...
You know, all of a sudden, this locker door flies open and nails me.
I'm gonna be brushing this stuff out of my hair for a week.
It's like this school is haunted.
Apparently, someone's been busy.
It wasn't me, I swear.
Now that was me.
Danny, I don't think you should be using your powers like...
Lancer. I'll be right back.
Don't listen to her, Danny.
It's about time somebody struck a blow for Sydney Point Dexter.
Sydney, who Dexter? Sydney Point Dexter.
Locker 724 was originally owned by a Point Dexter back in the 50s.
Point Dexter was the victim of more cruel pranks than anyone in the history of Casper High School.
Apparently, picking on him was a graduation requirement.
He got stuffed into his locker so many times,
his believed his spirit still inhabits it to this very day.
Sam, what are you doing?
Nothing.
Certainly not trying to smuggle frogs out of the BioLab while Lancer isn't looking.
Hey guys, what do you say we meet my new locker neighbor?
Easy Danny, take it easy.
You're right, Sam.
Enjoy your sandwich neighbor.
That's it.
Hmm, I wonder how Dash would feel if he had a frog in his throat.
Or 12 in his pants.
Oh no, you're not going to exploit innocent amphibians for some juvenile revenge scheme.
Hey!
Why are you so...
Oh, no!
Hey, I'm free!
Finally, the doorways been opened!
You think that's funny?
Buster?
Huh?
What?
You can see me?
Yeah, that's right, bub.
Now leave that poor kid alone.
What?
Oh, oh, man, that's good.
Man, do you ever have it backwards?
Don't hand me that jazz, Clyde.
You're the bully from where I'm standing.
Uh, floating.
Okay, yeah, floating.
Let's see how you like getting bullied.
I know those frogs were here somewhere.
Great!
Gatsby!
How many times do I have to tell you?
There's nothing weird going on in this school!
Move, Maddie! Move!
Look, you don't understand.
I understand a bully when I see one.
No!
There you go, little fellas.
Put an egg in your shoe and beat it, bully.
I'm Sydney Pointeister.
And wherever there was a single nerd in need,
I shall be there.
Hey, what do you call it, a nerd?
That's the guy who used to have your locker.
In your face, Mr. Skeptic.
In his face?
Well idea.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Oh!
No!
Holy sucks!
You're the halfa!
The whatta?
The halfa!
Everybody in the ghost zone talks about you.
You're halfa boy, halfa ghost, the halfa!
You have all our powers on the human plane.
And you're using your powers for evil.
No!
Look, just listen.
I took over Dash's body because...
Hey, wait.
You can take over a person's body.
Cheepers, creepers.
I would flip if I had your powers.
One.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Giving you a taste of your own medicine, bully.
Listen to me!
No!
Dash!
You let me.
Oh!
You might use your powers to pick on innocent kids.
I sure as sugar won't.
Hey, boy, Dexter.
Oh!
Is it true?
Did you kids just witness a ghost attack?
Oh!
200% freeer haha.
No!
That's lives Ramy Meat like a boo!
That's sorry, what?
No!
I want to take into the mRepublicans as far as I'm excited.
Man?
Get off number three when I'm
Riles Blech.
Dropped in the Grandpa Fittin's ear book.
Hit Point Dexter.
You got a spot on your shirt.
Ha! Made you look!
Yuck!
Have a nice trip, Point Dexter.
See you next fall!
I don't even know there's a dress code, Point Dexter.
Aah!
I gotta get out of here!
Spiff Diddly D, man.
So this is what it's like to have friends.
You sure you're all right, Denny?
Denny?
Oh! Me?
Yeah, right.
I'm right like Mike.
Why does your boy sound so weird?
Uh, puberty?
What happened to Point Dexter?
Oh, that square, he flew the coop.
Per minute like.
Come on, give me my soda!
Hey, let me help you out there, pal.
Thanks, Fenton.
Ah, no problemo.
What, are you going through puberty?
Uh, you know, I'm a little tight on quarters.
I think you can get a few more sodas for me and my pals.
You betcha.
Denny, that's stealing.
I'm sure that poor kid lost more than his fair share of quarters
to the vicious bullies in this school.
It's time somebody even the score.
Hey, everybody!
Ed creams on me!
I don't know what the heck an egg cream is, but thanks.
Well, this is new.
This is how I came in.
We gotta be away back!
Here's Difintan!
Yeah!
What the heck?
Tucker! Sam!
It's me, Denny!
Hey, Fenton, Maester!
We're short one for Touch Football.
Are you in?
Pausoleutly, absetivly.
Pausoleutly?
When did you get a set to humor?
Hey, pointextor!
Which black and blue it can't touch the floor.
I give up.
You!
Ah!
OK, Fenton, after the snap, I'll hand the ball off to you.
We've been wide open for punishment.
All right, let's go.
You have to contact them somehow.
Well, it was nice knowing him.
Think I could have his computer?
Fenton's got game!
Who knew?
There's a ghost in here.
I can feel it in my boots.
And I'm not leaving this campus
till these gloves grab some ghost.
A ghost?
That can't be right.
Looks like we'll be sticking up the school all night.
Don't wait up.
In that case, I need to use the little ghost on his room.
Hold these gloves, son.
Where I'm going, there's no need for that much power.
Party at Fenton's house!
Yay!
Hot dog!
Where does he live?
It's your house, bonehead.
Is he a lairs of what?
Free soda, a touchdown, and the opportunity
to trash a classmate's living room.
How easily the letter jacket and pom-pom set is swayed.
I don't know.
Denny seems a little off.
Although, the residual popularity
effect could work to our advantage.
Oh, Kwan, you simply must wear one of these
Save the Frogs badges.
It's all the rage.
I don't know.
Hey, boss badge.
Can I have one?
Hey, I want one.
Me too.
I can wear it with my old army lime green baby tea.
Give me one, yo.
I started this trend.
Hang on, folks.
Plenty more in my locker where that one came from.
Sam, Tucker in here.
Windexter?
No, it's me, Denny.
Windexter took over my body and sent me
into this bizarro spirit world.
Prove it.
In second grade, Tucker threw up in your lunchbox,
but he told you Ricky Marsh did it.
What?
I kicked him off the monkey bars for that.
It was you?
Denny?
The mirror acts as some kind of portal,
but I can't face through it.
Serves me right.
I'm only in here because I was acting like a bully.
Now I'm in here and I'm going to get bullied
for the rest of eternity.
You might not be able to get out,
but that doesn't mean Poindexter can't get back in.
I doubt he's in a big hurry to go back where he came from.
I know how to get him in here.
Here's what you need to do.
Denny, come quick.
A bully is shoving a poor, defenseless nerd
inside his own locker.
Tucker, I'll save you.
Hey, there's no nerd getting shoved inside his locker.
There is now.
No!
You've had your fun.
Now I want my body and my life back.
Forget you, bully.
You're not going anywhere.
No!
Aha! I'm doing it!
Huh? You may have my powers,
but you sure don't know how to use them?
Of course, I don't know how to use them,
but at least I know how not to use them better than you do.
What?
You wouldn't hit a guy with glasses.
You couldn't hit a guy with glasses.
In fact, you couldn't hit the broad side of a barn.
Hold still.
But I think you're going to kill him.
Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight.
Hey, get a load of poi, Dexter.
He's fighting the half-a.
Yeah, look at him stand up to that weird head, ghost bully.
I'm not a bully!
Now, if you don't mind, I'm going to live it up some more
in your body.
What?
One false move, and I smash your door back to my world.
You wouldn't.
You'd strand us both here.
Try me.
I've got a better idea.
I can make you.
With your powers, I can make you do anything.
That's what I was hoping you'd do.
You!
Oh, yeah!
Huh?
No!
I'll get out of here, Buster Brown.
And when I do, you better watch it.
Hey, nerd.
Nice job standing up to the half-a.
Who'd have thought you had it, did you?
You want to grab an egg cream?
Of course I could hang it for a little bit.
Hey, the heck with the egg cream.
Who's up for a diet soda?
Whatever that is.
Oh!
No, come back!
Oh, dear, whatever we do.
Could win, Danny?
Yeah.
But how do we know you're really Danny?
Because I used my powers for the wrong reason
and became exactly the kind of person I hate.
It got me into a load of trouble,
and I'm not going to do that again.
Now that's the Danny I remember.
Just one more thing to do.
Fenton, that school property.
I can explain.
Actually, I really can't.
I'm holding you responsible for this.
I'm the escaped frogs.
But seeing how outstanding students like Dash Baxter
have made their opinions known,
I'm willing to overlook the frogs.
Miss Manson, you could learn a thing or two from them
about activism.
Still, that leaves the matter of your locker.
I'm going to have to assign you a new one.
Hanging with band geeks, Fenton?
No amount of free soda is going to fix that.
Hi, I'm Lyle.
Wanna help me clean my spit mouth?
My 15 minutes of popularity is up,
and I wasn't even here for it.
Yeah, but at least it wasn't a total loss.
Looks like this baby's going to get some use after all.
I am no longer the box ghost.
I am now the mechanical frog ghost.
I changed my mind.
I am once again the box ghost
who will have nothing to do with mechanical amphibians.
Beware!
Now there's a guy who knows exactly who he is.
You're it.