Finally, one day where I get home on
time without any ghost detours making me miss
my ten o'clock curfew.
Or not.
Going ghost!
You fellows look lost.
Any chance of you staying that way?
Mind your own business, fancy-pants ghost boy.
We've been cycling in this town for hours.
We could have been halfway to Florida by
now.
Ask for directions.
I know where I'm going.
You so do not ask him.
Ask me what?
We are on a search-and-destroy mission.
Can you help us find and peck to
death this guy here?
Dad?
See, I told you he'd know where he
is.
Nice try, kid.
Get him, boys!
Give it your best shot, guys!
I'm a wizard dodgeball!
Okay, technically, it's dodge beak, but who cares?
It's almost ten!
You know that old saying about a bird
in the hand?
Well, neither do I!
And don't go messing any windshields on your
way out of town!
I wonder why those guys were trying to
waste Dad.
Oh, no.
Dad.
You're late again, young man.
sıçtım.
7. BÖLÜM: MEZUNLAR TOPLANTISI
Danny, this is becoming a problem.
You're constantly late coming home.
You're shirking from your chores.
Your grades are slipping.
You already said chores.
I know, but when you don't do them,
I get stuck with them.
Look, I'm under a lot of pressure.
You two have no idea what it's like
to be a kid today.
Come on, Danny.
That's the oldest excuse in the book.
There's nothing you're going through that your father
and I didn't go through when we were
your age.
Yeah?
Well, I beg to differ.
The reason Danny doesn't think you can relate
to him is that you never take the
time to tell him about your childhood.
Jazz.
Have you ever told him how you met?
About your first date?
Jazz.
Where you went to college?
You know, Jasmine, that's a great idea.
It is?
What is?
This is.
You can come with your mother and I
to our college reunion.
I can?
Wisconsin?
Sure.
My old pal Vlad is throwing a huge
shindig there.
We'll take the RV so the whole family
can go together.
You can learn more about your mothers and
my college days and while we drive, I
can blather on about ghosts.
It works.
I can't wait to blather on about that
too.
How does this happen?
You goof up and I have to spend
four days jammed in the Fenton ghost RV?
That's the Fenton family ghost assault vehicle, folks.
Every button in this baby is a ghost's
worst nightmare.
I need some air.
Don't press any buttons.
I'll get you for this.
Get some rest, everybody.
I want the entire Fenton clan bright-eyed
and bushy-tailed when we meet Masters tomorrow.
Wait, wait, wait.
Masters?
As in Vlad Masters, who was named Affluence
Magazine's billionaire of the year?
That's the guy.
In college, he was my best friend.
We were very popular guys.
Roommates, lab partners.
We did everything together until the thick fingers
of fate stuck themselves right in Vlad's eyes.
I'm telling you, Jack, it won't work.
Bogus, V-Man.
It totally will.
This proto-portal is guaranteed to bust open
the wall into the ghost dimension.
Jack, these calculations aren't right.
Bungie!
Who was hospitalized with a horrible case of
ecto-acne.
It devastated him and killed his social life.
We haven't spoken since that day, but the
good news is I think after all these
years, he's finally forgiven me.
Jack and Maddie, you've never looked lovelier, my
dear.
Please, please, come in.
Vladdy, my man, it's good to...
Hello?
What's with the green and gold?
You're a billionaire.
Surely you could afford an interior designer.
Jazz, hello?
Football helmets, jerseys, cheese heads.
He's a Packers fanatic.
Hello?
Oh, fanatic is such a negative word, but
yes.
I don't understand.
You have billions of dollars.
Instead of buying this stuff, why don't you
just buy the team?
Because the Packers are owned by the city
of Green Bay and they won't sell them
to me.
One of two things my wealth has not
as of yet been able to acquire.
Is he hitting on mom?
As long as he's got working toilets and
mom says no, who cares?
I'd better let Jack in.
Whoa, cool.
Indeed.
This ball was autographed by the legendary Ray
Nitschke himself.
It's my prized possession.
Heads up, V-Man.
Ha!
I see you still got the old moves.
Give me that.
I never had any old moves.
All those years in the hospital robbed me
of that.
Yes.
Well, it gave me time to chart out
a course for my life, didn't it?
Make some decisions that helped to make me
very wealthy, but very quickly.
And it never would have happened without you,
Jack.
Uh, yeah.
Maybe we should go.
No, no.
You should stay with me.
That's the whole reason I'm throwing the reunion
here in my castle, previously home to the
legendary Wisconsin Dairy King.
Just so I could reconnect with you, Jack.
I insist you stay.
Well, I don't know.
We do have a really cool RV.
Let's stay here.
Smooth.
You know, Jack, the Dairy King's ghost could
haunt these very halls.
I'll get the bags.
Bathroom.
Oh, great.
Just what I need.
A working vacation.
Hey, Vat Gibbs!
Sweet relief.
Hi, guys.
Remember me?
Okay, that was almost too easy.
Ah, bright boy.
Oh, whatever.
I was aiming for the birds, but you'll
do.
Whoa, fast.
All right, better stop fooling around.
My vultures were supposed to bring the big
idiot to me, but you'll do.
Fanny Phantom.
Right, you...
you know me?
Of course I know you.
You're the ghost boy who uses his powers
for good.
Oh, wait.
Aren't you going to try to shove me
into your ridiculous thermos?
I...
I don't want to fight you.
No.
No, you don't.
Get away!
Ah, an ectoplasmic energy blast.
So, year one.
Tell me, child, can you do this yet?
No, I can't.
How are you doing all this?
Years of practice, which you, unfortunately, have no
time for.
What?
The ghost boy is Jack's son?
Well, what do you know?
No!
Get away!
Huh?
Where am I?
What happened?
I was going to ask you the same
question, young man.
I must have been worn out from the
long car trip.
I'll be okay in the morning.
I'm sorry for the scare.
Oh, what's a little scare between friends, son?
Sleep tight, little badger.
Yes, sleep tight.
Jazz, aren't you coming to the reunion?
What?
And watch a bunch of old fossils pogo
to new wave music?
Pass.
Did you know the Packers won the very
first Super Bowl?
Whatever.
On a snowy day in Lambeau, Bart star
faces Butkus and the Bears.
Hey, Harry!
I'd know that voice anywhere.
Jack!
Maddie!
How nice.
Danny, meet Harriet Chinn.
She's a big shot reporter for the Milwaukee
Journal now, but back in my college days,
she was just Harry.
Harry Chinn!
Get it?
I'm really sorry, Harriet.
Sweetie, you married him.
You should be.
Hey, my song!
Come on, let's pogo!
Okay, I'm officially mortified.
What took so long?
Well, son, you're looking much better.
I was wondering if you could do me
a huge favor.
Oh, sure, Mr. Masters, but call me Danny.
It's sons what my dad calls me.
Oh, yes, yes, of course.
Now, could you go to my lab, second
door on the right, upstairs?
There's a present in there for your father
that I'd like you to bring down.
Okay.
Maddie, that lab accident cost me my youthful
chance at you, but that's all about to
change.
A present?
I don't see a present.
Hey, wait a minute.
Let go!
Those ghosts!
They were two of the first ghosts I
fought!
And they're not alone, pup.
Stalker?
How did you get back in your ectoskeleton?
What are you doing here?
All excellent questions.
Catch!
Hey, I can't phase out of this.
It's disrupting my powers.
Then that's not all it does.
The glowing blade is new.
You like it?
I've had some upgrades.
No.
Enough!
I didn't free you to kill the boy,
Skulker.
Your work is done.
Yes, well, I've got to go to the
library and check out a book on a
gorilla.
Again!
Skulker?
The ectopuses?
I don't understand.
Of course not.
You're what, 14?
Too young to drive and not in college
yet?
I sent those ghosts and others to test
your father's skills.
Imagine my surprise when I find you, the
second ghost hybrid his foolishness created.
Second?
You!
I'm going ghost!
Going ghost!
Why can't I go ghost?
You have a battle cry.
Hilarious.
I, on the other hand, have this.
A spectral energy neutralizer designed by Skulker, paid
for by me.
And as long as you're contained within that
box, you're as human as your idiot father.
Let me out of here!
Why?
So you can go back to stumbling through
your adolescence, desperately trying to get control of
your powers?
Powers, by the way, that I've had for
20 years.
I have experience, my child.
And the money and power I've gained through
using those powers for personal gain, you see.
I could train you, teach you everything I
know, and all you'd have to do is
renounce your idiot father.
Dude, you are one seriously crazed up Froot
Loop.
That is never going to happen.
Yes, well, once your father is out of
the way, we'll see how you feel.
Then I covered the gorilla uprising in Umakistan.
Got an exclusive with the rebel leader that
got raves.
Am I boring you, Jack?
Frankly, yes.
So, what do you say we liven up
this shindig?
Hey!
Jack, what's the matter with you?
Why, Maddie, didn't you always know I'd turn
on you?
That when you chose me, you chose wrong.
Get out.
Get out of me.
I don't know what's come over you, but
when I write about this, I swear...
Ghost!
Overpowering me.
Maddie, run.
He's a ghost?
This is the story of the century.
Come on, we have to get to the
Fenton family ghost assault vehicle.
I mean, the RV.
Well, gosh and golly, it looks like you
could use a speck of help there, don't
you know?
Hey, you're the Dairy King.
Oh, great.
What are you gonna do, suffocate me with
Limburger, strangle me with Swiss, or...
Let me go.
Thank you, but why?
Not all ghosts are evil, right?
Some of us just want to be left
alone there, don't you know?
Hey, will you help me fight Plasmius?
I'm the Dairy King, kiddo.
Kings don't fight.
They send other people to fight farmers.
Royalty 101 there, don't you know?
It's Dairy Fresh...
Jack!
Dad!
So, Maddie, when did you first realize your
husband was a monster bent on destroying his
smarter, more successful, and better-dressed peers?
What are you talking about?
That jumpsuit is incredibly stylish.
I'm guessing we won't be invited back.
If you live to tell the tale, remember
that big, fat Jack Fenton did this to
you?
Yes, again, cheese head.
Nobody uses Jack Fenton as a human meat
puppet.
Daniel, stop.
Think about the things I could show you.
The doors I could open for you.
You, Danny Phantom, and I, Vlad Plasmius, together
we could rule.
Forget it, pal.
Your money can't buy my mom, it can't
buy the Packers, and it can't buy me.
I know who you are.
I'll tell my father.
I'll tell everyone.
And so will I.
Honestly, if you expose me, you expose yourself.
Mind if I cut in?
Let go of me.
Never again, woman.
Oh, great, it's a stick.
And I wasn't going to come to this
thing.
Jack, look out!
The RV!
Sorry, Dad, I've got one shot at this.
Jack, you did it!
It was nothing, Mom.
Uh, Maddie?
Sure, Maddie.
You make sure Harry's okay while I finish
this.
How's it going, V-Man?
Oh, you've overshadowed Jack.
Oh, I'm so scared.
Now, what's next?
A card trick?
Listen to me.
I swear I'll walk out of my dad
right now and expose us both, unless you
agree to a truce.
You're bluffing.
No, I'm not.
My parents will accept me, no matter what.
But if I expose you, well, what would
my mom think of you?
You'll be miserable and alone for the rest
of your life, unless you call a truce.
Using your opponent's weaknesses against him.
I am teaching you something, after all, very
well.
Truce.
Eventually, you will join me by choice, you
and your mother.
But for now...
Curse you, Jack Fenton!
Your world-renowned expertise of all things ghost
has defeated me.
Until next time, son.
World-renowned expertise.
Outstanding.
Jack, I have never seen you like this.
You beat that ghost all the way to
Kenosha.
I did?
Oh, heck, I'm just doing my job.
And mine.
Jack, for all the years I thought you
were a crackpot, I sort of apologize.
Ghosts!
This story will make your career.
And mine.
I can't believe they fired Harry.
Of course they fired her.
She tried to file some crackpot story about
ghosts.
It's the Milwaukee Journal, not the National Enquirer.
I can't believe Harry blames me.
And Vlad was so mad, he didn't even
say goodbye.
And we were all such great chums in
college.
Whatever.
Who cares what you were when you were
younger?
It's who you grew into that makes you
who you are.
You think?
Hey, if you can cause that much damage
in college, and still turn out to be
this cool, ghost-butt-kicking adult, well, maybe
there's hope for me yet.
Thanks, son.
But your curfew is still ten.
Oh, man.