Some people have a lot, and some people
don't.
But everybody's got something.
Me?
I've got charm, good looks, and modesty.
My best friend Danny...
He has something else.
Two for me, two for you?
Sounds fair.
Danny and me have known each other since,
like, forever.
And we share everything.
A genie in a bottle?
I don't think so.
Thanks, anyway.
Please, Mommy!
Can I have some cotton candy?
Please, please, please, please!
I think you've had enough sugar today.
I want it!
And your heart's desire is my command.
We share
everything, except one thing.
I'm going ghost!
Danny's got superpowers.
I am Desiree.
What is your wish?
None of your business, candy pants.
Surely there must be something.
Hey, get away!
What the heck?
What's going on?
Is this a new ghost power?
That was slammin'!
Whatever that was, you've got another power?
I guess.
Man, that's the cool thing about your powers,
man.
There's no downside.
Give me five.
I'm okay!
6. BÖLÜM: NASIL İSTERSEN
So, anyway, I
guess the craziness really started at the game
Saturday night.
I'm sick as a dog and I hate sports
Why am I here?
Because Danny's here and he's got the best
seat in the house. And now everybody, here
they are Your very own Casper High Raven
Fill in for the mascot It'll be fun
You'll meet cheerleaders
This is pathetic Our team's fading fast
Me too,
77.1
I'm out of here, later
77.2
Men,
we should get turn into the kind
of monster who could crush these guys single
-handed
oh no!
it looks like those high-protein breakfasts are
really paying off.
Do you believe this, Danny?
Dash is a beast.
And getting beastier.
Holy Mark McGuire, look at those arms.
I think he's running on ghost power.
I need your help.
To kick some ghost booty?
Sort of.
I'm in.
Fifteen.
Twenty-five.
Three-two.
Whoa, ghost energy's pretty strong, but hopefully ripe
for the picking.
Uh, hike?
Back to the ghost zone for you, pal.
Danny had no problem getting that ghost out
of Dash.
But we lost the game, which was bad
news for the guy filling in for Danny,
who was filling in for the guy who
usually wears the mascot suit, me.
Man, every time Danny goes ghost, I get
the short end of the stick.
Hey, guys!
A raven pinata!
Let's hit him until the candy comes out!
End of the line, gruesome.
Aaaaaah!
Whoa!
Huh?
A-phew!
Who's that?
Somebody out there?
Am I interrupting something that I hope I'm
not?
Your father and I are purifying ourselves of
negative ghost energy.
A-phew!
Ugh.
We're trying to ritually expel any ghost in
our systems with the Fenton Ghost Catcher.
It's like an Indian dream catcher, except it
expunges ghosts and not dreams, you see.
You might just have a cold, you know.
It doesn't have to be a ghost cold.
I remember when I was that naive.
Whoa!
This one actually works.
A little too well.
I'm filing this under a must-avoid.
Even during trying times, one has to remember
a fallen comrade.
Poor Sam was so sick and all cooped
up in her house.
That's the worst.
A-phew!
Oh, I feel like I'm gonna die.
I hate being sick.
A-phew!
Hang in there, Sam.
Tucker and I are gonna come visit you
when we're done at the mall.
You want us to bring you anything?
A-phew!
No, no, please.
Don't bother.
My folks are taking pretty good care of
me.
Guys, it's just a cold.
Claire!
She's gotta be sick if she's missing Dead
Teacher 4.
This time it's personal.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't wait for the Sayonara Pussycat movie.
I want to see it so bad.
Oh, my gosh, I know.
Isn't she so cute?
Sayonara Pussycat is so cute.
Why can't I be that popular?
Hi, everybody.
What do you think of me?
Whoa!
We love you!
We love you, Paulina!
Look at me.
I'm so cute and cuddly and ever so
wonderful.
Don't you think?
We agree!
We love you, Paulina!
Paulina?
Attention, moviegoers.
Google Plexitabuzz has officially declared it Happy Fabulous
Paulina Day!
I don't know what to say.
Why squander my popularity here?
I'm so adorable.
I bet I could become Super Fairy Queen
of all Teenager Dome.
Isn't that luscious?
Yay!
Tucker, I do what you gotta do.
I'll get seats.
Man, I'm coming for Danny.
My movie gets sold out and I gotta
watch this.
I'm tired of being left out all the
time.
Man, I wish I had ghost powers, too.
Your heart's desire is my command.
Huh?
Ah!
Sweet!
Hi, I'm Paulina.
I'm adorable and swell and full of big
-headed anime goodness.
Bye-bye, kitty!
Ah!
Hi!
Isn't everything in the world sweet and wonderful
and...
Ah!
Cool!
It worked!
I can't wait to tell Tucker.
Where am I?
And why do I feel that I'm special
and adorable?
Because I am!
Huh, no Tuck.
He must have taken off.
Oh, sure, that's what he probably thought.
But why would he even suspect?
Huh?
That I was having the time of my
14-year-old life!
Ouch!
Ha ha ha!
Bogus, stupid car.
Huh, I wish you could just fly over,
Steph, so I wouldn't have to sit here.
So you wish it, so shall it be.
What the heck?
Hey, this isn't my station.
Ah!
Geez, lady, don't you ever take a break?
Flying car?
Hey!
Slow down, Jeff Gordon!
You're going over the speed limit!
And the height limit!
Don't sweat this one, Danny.
I'm on it.
Tucker?!
Ah!
Chill, dude.
Tucker Phantom's on the case.
Tucker Phantom?
Okay, ignoring the total originality of that, how
the heck did you get ghost powers anyway?
Who knows?
And more importantly, who cares?
And now, if you'll excuse me, I have
some heroic exploits to attend to.
Tucker, we're too young to drive!
Let go of the wheel!
This is serious!
Ah!
Oh, sure.
Phase the car through the building.
You had to save the day, didn't you?
Uh, yeah, because a car smashing into the
28th floor of anything is bad!
You're just jealous.
Because there's somebody else around to grab the
spotlight now.
Yo hallucinations, okay.
What have I ever grabbed the spotlight?
How about right now for instance?
Yeah, there's a chicken on my head Tucker
please this is stupid.
You're my best friend.
I'm not jealous.
I'm concerned Well, don't be this town's big
enough for more than one ghost kid talk
wait Whoa can't fly that fast is he
getting more powerful So why didn't you guys
see a movie today, uh we got a
little distracted I'm just goofing off by myself
now Mm-hmm What happened Danny have ghost
trouble you might say that so how are
you?
Oh, it's horrible Tucker But somehow I'll muddle
through I didn't want to tell Sam about
my new ghost powers yet What if she
got as jealous as Danny did?
And speaking of Danny I
Nice trick do you do kids parties dude
relax?
I'm just having fun You okay, I may
be catching Sam's cold, but that's not important
right now Tucker look no need you can
keep that superhero Jazz to yourself.
I'm in this for the kicks.
I was afraid of that I hate to
do this pal, but I need to see
what's going on inside of you, and there's
only one way to do that I Don't
ever do that again Get it got it
good.
Okay.
Maybe I was a little rough on Danny,
but nobody likes a party pooper And man
was I having a party?
Excuse me I
There's one little ghost trick I haven't tried
yet the ghost imposed hookup
I Just wanted to let you know I'm
gonna start dating Tucker Foley He's much cooler
than you are so stop chasing me.
Tucker get out of there.
Why don't you make me?
Fine! I will... Tucker you're turning the whole school
upside down how about giving it a break
how about getting off my back and let
me have a Little fun?
because your fun is kind of mean now get out of Paulina
I was here first you go.
No you. - you Baba Zita's genie gave me
these powers, and I'll use them how I want.
But maybe I need to have a
chat with this Baba Zita
Fine, But you and I aren't friends anymore Danny Fenton,
330.1
What?
I never was friends with you.
It was our first argument, and we were
having it over a girl In one actually,
but you get the point That was my
mistake Reminding Danny where the ghost came from
apparently Desiree was a harem girl who had
been promised her heart's desire her own kingdom
Only to be banished by the Sultan's jealous
wife She died of a broken heart and
all day After that her spirit roamed granting
people's deepest desires, but at a great personal
cost Hey If you're trying to snag a
wishing ghost what better place than a wishing
well Dang it I Wish
I had a million bucks So it is
desired so shall it be Oh, no, you
don't dare to interfere with my Listen
Desiree, I want you to take away Tucker's
ghost powers pronto By noon tomorrow your friends
fate will be sealed His jealousy will transform
him forever into the most powerful ghost boy
in the world Tuck he's not that jealous
Is he more than you know?
Tomorrow his jealousy Frustration will cement into rage
and rebellion.
He will be complete You change him back
you dare lay a hand on me Yeah,
how about a fist I
Wish you would disappear inside this If
I weren't a C student I would have
thought of that five days ago now to
find tuck Quarter to noon and no sign
of Tucker Should have guessed Tucker you're changing
your grades.
That's cheating.
I like to think of it as academic
enrichment want me to do yours No way
Tucker.
You're in real danger Take It easy we're
friends remember we're only friends on your terms
But now I make the rules around here
and my first rule is no more Danny
Phantom He's getting more malevolent more ghost like
Tuck please you have to listen to me.
There isn't much time.
You got that right your time is up
You Set the
best you can do Unfortunately, yes, I can't
get through to him, but I know what
can Catch me if you can sucker phantom
That's Tucker Phantom The girls lock around The
girls locker room, so this is what it's
like in here Only five minutes left
you got no game Where
are you where what's the matter?
Can't catch what you can't see He has
to have followed me it's almost noon.
Yeah No, don't throw me into the ghost
zone, please I wasn't going to but that
is a great idea I'm only gonna have
one shot at this Oh Hey cover your
mouth Is that
me No, it's not you tuck not anymore.
Oh Man, Danny.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't control myself Dude, don't worry about
it You were under the genie spell and
you broke it Yeah But none of that
would have happened if I wasn't jealous or
if I had been a little less of
a show-off around you friends the best
Tucker Foley digital journal Saturday, they say be
careful what you wish for to that I'd
like to add a big fat duh, especially
when it comes to best friends cuz I
couldn't wish for a better one Geez do
you guys have to share everything?
You don't know the half of it